Good morning.
Thank you.
Bye.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, that's awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Were you nervous at first?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: But we did fine.
[SPEAKER_13]: We got, like, my little translator stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was a lot like Colorado.
[SPEAKER_13]: Old Colorado that's not populated.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's where I grew up.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, Kevin and I were like... Oh, I'm so glad you guys had a good time.
[SPEAKER_07]: Were you, like, kind of sad to come back?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I was ready to come back.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, you were.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, I think it's probably as serious.
[SPEAKER_12]: Good morning.
[SPEAKER_12]: How are you, sir?
[SPEAKER_12]: Doing all right.
How are you all?
Good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sunshiny.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
It's always a good time.
Okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, I have a little chili.
[SPEAKER_13]: Gosh, it's so sweet.
[SPEAKER_13]: Boy, I get to grill a lot.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've only got a little bit of pregnant over there, so she's hot, and then she's got a cold, real cold, like a dirty needle.
[SPEAKER_12]: extend our commission since it may be all three of us, we can extend that to one o'clock.
[SPEAKER_12]: So that way.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_09]: Good morning, Pastor.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good morning.
[SPEAKER_05]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_09]: Good.
[SPEAKER_09]: How are you doing?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm all right.
[SPEAKER_12]: Two minutes.
[SPEAKER_12]: Two minutes and counting.
[SPEAKER_12]: Thank you, Cindy.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you like it?
[SPEAKER_02]: I do.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's very colorful.
[SPEAKER_12]: It is.
[SPEAKER_12]: I have a lot of confusion.
[SPEAKER_12]: I understand it now.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm not sure that I feel any differently about it now that I understand it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: Good morning, everyone.
[SPEAKER_05]: Father God, as we come before you today, we are grateful for the beautiful weather outside and your encouragement in our lives.
[SPEAKER_05]: We just pray for our county.
[SPEAKER_05]: We pray for the unity of the people of our county.
[SPEAKER_05]: We pray for the future and what you have in store for us.
[SPEAKER_05]: We do pray for all of our elected officials and our workers.
[SPEAKER_05]: We pray that you would watch over them, keep them safe, keep them healthy, just put protection around their families as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: We pray that you give them wisdom and discernment to be able to do the very best of their job they possibly can.
[SPEAKER_05]: And we thank you in advance for how you're going to work in that way.
[SPEAKER_05]: We just pray that you would continue to bless and encourage each one of us in our day ahead and help our lives shine brightly for you.
[SPEAKER_05]: We do continue to pray for Lindsay and her health and the health of that baby and pray you would watch over her and keep her safe and healthy.
It's in Jesus' name we pray.
Amen.
[SPEAKER_09]: Say that again.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_12]: Pastor, thank you.
[SPEAKER_12]: The service downstairs was very nice and those things just don't happen
[SPEAKER_12]: in a blink of an eye.
[SPEAKER_12]: So thank you for your efforts in making that something that Ray can do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for being a part of it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do we have any comments from public?
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just wanted to ask, so I got
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, we, and we did it last year and we're doing it this year.
[SPEAKER_12]: In fact, we already have it scheduled.
[SPEAKER_12]: We do three meetings a year with all the office holders to go through where we are, what issues we're off, and how for next, not quarter, but try, what's it called if you do it three of them?
[SPEAKER_12]: Like, not quarterly.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, we do it every four months.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, we do it January, February, March, April.
[SPEAKER_12]: So we're doing it in May.
[SPEAKER_12]: So we're looking at four months.
[SPEAKER_12]: So we only do it three times.
[SPEAKER_12]: One being the budget process.
[SPEAKER_12]: So we're doing that just to review it, to see where we are and where we were off.
[SPEAKER_12]: And we did that last year also.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's just with the, are you doing it with like, for like Road and Bridge, for example, that was when I was a lot older.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is it like, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: figure that out.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well the reason that we're over is that we hadn't bought any certain equipment and we're looking at we're doing some of that now so that probably wasn't specifically budgeted in that amount but we're trying to catch up that part of the situation so we can better serve the county.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay and then is there a way to get
[SPEAKER_06]: now?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't understand.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, like, I'm assuming for each account you have a budget, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: So how can I get that for each one of those accounts?
[SPEAKER_13]: You send a function request for that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I don't understand what
[SPEAKER_06]: And he's already requested that and he doesn't want to pay for it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that's.
[SPEAKER_12]: Cindy, do you have anything?
[SPEAKER_12]: Not a thing.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, I think we are ready to approve the minutes.
[SPEAKER_12]: We have reviewed them.
[SPEAKER_12]: Do we have a motion?
[SPEAKER_12]: I make a motion to approve the minutes.
[SPEAKER_12]: I second that.
[SPEAKER_12]: All those in favor?
[SPEAKER_12]: Aye.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, the minutes are approved, and we'll sign that for you when you get that ready.
[SPEAKER_12]: We're just initially, so just take it away.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll just take the initiative.
Well, maybe.
I hope I don't smell bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: It smells good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like food good?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Kurt.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think we need that because that's when it comes up.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I think that's, I think that's more important than on the commission's page.
[SPEAKER_12]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's a big topic.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know if you guys are over the road, so I don't know if you have one on your page.
[SPEAKER_09]: We can do one on your page.
[SPEAKER_09]: That sounds great.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think the homepage is great.
[SPEAKER_12]: That sounds good.
[SPEAKER_07]: Lindsay, do you have a baby bump on your head?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, you're getting big.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_02]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, we're very excited.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's it for you guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_09]: I do have one general thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: So my daughter and I were eye surgeons, and they had a bunch of reading glasses, and they were just on their way.
[SPEAKER_09]: So she's like, hey, we can do, like, an outreach opportunity with those things.
[SPEAKER_09]: So do you guys mind if I, like, set up a table outside my door, like, with free reading glasses and announce it to the public if they want to come in and read it for free?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, that's amazing.
[SPEAKER_12]: Is that, that's just a question.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't have a problem with that, no.
[SPEAKER_12]: But isn't it the Kiwanis that does reading glasses, or is it the Lions Club?
[SPEAKER_12]: Do we have, do we still have a Lions Club?
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know if we have a Lions Club.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't think we do.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: I just thought that we might want to be.
[SPEAKER_09]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_12]: Tell your daughter, thanks for thinking of us.
[SPEAKER_12]: Perfect.
[SPEAKER_12]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_11]: And you're going to get this.
[SPEAKER_12]: There seems kind of an oversight.
[SPEAKER_12]: Every time I ask.
Thank you.
[SPEAKER_12]: I believe you do have MTS.
[SPEAKER_12]: We will pass this along to Max and then see when he would like for us to put it on the agenda.
[SPEAKER_12]: So send it to him.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm just going to put it over here for him for when he comes back next week and then we'll decide.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think you have your agenda.
[SPEAKER_13]: When is the Forbis call?
[SPEAKER_13]: 10.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_12]: I look forward to Forbis meetings now because they're simple.
[SPEAKER_12]: I know.
[SPEAKER_12]: They're simple because we're at the end of the line.
[SPEAKER_07]: It looked like you had a great turnout for the Child Abuse Awareness.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was very nice.
[SPEAKER_12]: It was very nice.
[SPEAKER_12]: Beautiful.
[SPEAKER_12]: And we had a pretty good crowd for the prayer service.
[SPEAKER_12]: Good.
[SPEAKER_12]: And the Metro Festival was a big success.
[SPEAKER_12]: So then we, everyone's done a good job of lots of things.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a lot of work.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it is.
[SPEAKER_12]: I guess I was with the chamber for seven years when we did it.
[SPEAKER_12]: But I loved it.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, it was so fun.
[SPEAKER_12]: When it was over, I was always sad and happy at the same time.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, it was a lot of work, but you were...
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, didn't you start planning for the next year, like a week after or something?
[SPEAKER_12]: I do think that, like, the letters go out to all the vendors and stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, just almost as soon as it's over.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, it used to be, and I'm sure it's like that.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's the way most fairs are, fairs and festivals.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_03]: and the weather cooperated.
[SPEAKER_10]: And how many did we have at the car show?
[SPEAKER_12]: To me, that number was...
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, that's significant.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I did hear a lot.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know what that means.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've just seen everybody's dinner out there.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're awfully quiet.
We're awfully quiet.
That should scare you.
What did he say?
[SPEAKER_12]: He's just seeing if everybody was out here behaving, basically.
[SPEAKER_12]: When they get past him, I might want to ask him if he had second thoughts.
[SPEAKER_03]: Did you bring us a check?
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_12]: Almost exactly.
[SPEAKER_12]: by the blessed attention they are going to be talking about.
I mean everything is in pretty you know normal range then there's
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_12]: Bye, then.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, so we're fine with that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wonder how we would find that out.
[SPEAKER_04]: If we're buying
[SPEAKER_12]: Drugs for our inmates.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, medicine for our inmates.
[SPEAKER_12]: Some companies, you can get a manufacturer coupon and the price of it is?
[SPEAKER_04]: $0.05 for a Grunt Network man, almost $1,600, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_12]: For one month?
[SPEAKER_04]: For 30 days.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm going to see about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's no generic.
Because they have that one in Britain.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or there's just not one for it.
[SPEAKER_12]: I found the replacement.
[SPEAKER_12]: It was $300 more.
[SPEAKER_12]: So that wasn't a case.
[SPEAKER_12]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_12]: Thank you.
Okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: Let's just do a little.
[SPEAKER_12]: There was something when we had our insurance
[SPEAKER_12]: mentioned, sometimes they have agreements like manufacturer coupons.
[SPEAKER_12]: What are the coupon codes?
[SPEAKER_07]: There's also a website you can go on and put the exact definition of the prescription, and it will search to see where is the cheapest place to get it, or if there's a coupon code.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: well that's a philippine government contract
Yes, the auditing.
[SPEAKER_12]: consulting group that audits our ARPA funds, like all of our special, the ones that we did for, we have what, four or five different ARPA projects.
[SPEAKER_12]: And they oversee all the money for that, because it's a government, you have to do that to participate.
[SPEAKER_12]: And we're just about, we're on the downhill side.
[SPEAKER_12]: Heather, how much was that all together?
[SPEAKER_12]: Do you remember all those projects that went through?
[SPEAKER_13]: I was just curious at how much we got to do for the county on behalf of those federal funds.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, I was going to say that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Marie, can I have a copy of the agenda for tomorrow?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes, ma'am.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is our jail in a place where they can't serve that out, or do they usually send it away somewhere else?
[SPEAKER_12]: I think it's both.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's both.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I think it's also a certain level of offenders.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, how that happens.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that is one way.
I know he was with this association.
[SPEAKER_11]: I am just wondering that we should ask him to include someone so he can give us some of his, you know, we can hear their and this one person's saying this.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm just wondering that.
[SPEAKER_11]: And, you know, he keeps saying everybody's for this.
Thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you.
Amen.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you.
Thank you.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, perfect.
[SPEAKER_12]: So we will see you tonight.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, thank you.
[SPEAKER_12]: Have a good day.
[SPEAKER_12]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, that was a good call.
[SPEAKER_12]: Was it?
[SPEAKER_12]: He said he's bringing somebody, like the commander or something.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's what they're looking at.
[SPEAKER_13]: $2 million.
[SPEAKER_12]: $2 million of ARPA projects.
[SPEAKER_13]: Can you say that again, please?
[SPEAKER_12]: $2,235,000 of ARPA projects that we did when we received those funds.
[SPEAKER_12]: $2,235,000?
[SPEAKER_12]: And by the way, Brie, you had everything just set good for me.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, good.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: That meeting went great, and I didn't have any problems.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's good.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm so happy to hear that.
[SPEAKER_12]: I kind of felt like I was a technology wizard.
I know.
You feel like that after.
I'm glad that everything was good.
That's good.
[SPEAKER_12]: It did come up a message that said soon you would be asked to change your password.
[SPEAKER_12]: I was just glad it let me do it.
[SPEAKER_12]: I know.
Thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have a good day.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's beautiful out there.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes, I think I'll buy some flowers.
[SPEAKER_12]: I did that last week, and I'm so happy I did.
[SPEAKER_12]: They didn't freeze or anything yet.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I've got mine all in.
[SPEAKER_03]: Goodbye.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_03]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_12]: They talk about commercial insurance, but we don't have insurance for them.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I'll let them know that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think Ray was going to, if he had to talk about it, you know, if he has children out there, he said he'll put it out.
[SPEAKER_07]: As far as changing the speed limit, you can't do that because it's already mandated in 7th, but...
[SPEAKER_09]: And it can only be on their property.
[SPEAKER_12]: We're going to call the next one.
[SPEAKER_12]: There's another.
[SPEAKER_12]: Heather?
[SPEAKER_12]: On our inmates that we have.
[SPEAKER_12]: is all just out of pocket.
[SPEAKER_12]: There is no plans of anything in place to help cover anything for them, right?
[SPEAKER_12]: It's, okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, I'm not for sure on that side because I don't deal with that part, but as far as like medicine and stuff like that, I think they have to pay as long as the judge doesn't make them indigent.
[SPEAKER_13]: Now, if they're indigent, then they don't have to.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, basically, he's reversing us from the state.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't think he
[SPEAKER_09]: But I can tell you, I don't know for sure because I don't even know who this is for, but there's not very many that's...
[SPEAKER_12]: There's probably more indigent than not.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, who can...
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, I can ask him.
[SPEAKER_09]: He really didn't have any issues with it.
[SPEAKER_09]: His only thing was just making sure it was fine.
[SPEAKER_12]: We have to provide it.
[SPEAKER_12]: But there are some things that you can do.
[SPEAKER_12]: I just went online.
[SPEAKER_12]: There's a number.
[SPEAKER_12]: I know.
[SPEAKER_12]: Talk to me.
[SPEAKER_12]: He just told me.
[SPEAKER_09]: Right.
[SPEAKER_09]: They have a place down there that they do.
[SPEAKER_09]: I can talk to him later about it.
[SPEAKER_09]: He's really having an issue with it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know if it's a bad idea.
[SPEAKER_09]: He just wanted me to double check to see if they can do it outside.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a lot of money a year.
[SPEAKER_09]: So as long as it's not in the way of being able to do the roads, it should be fine.
Okay.
May of 21, we have two points.
And then June 22, we have the other two.
[SPEAKER_13]: The first batch that we got in 2021,
[SPEAKER_13]: And then they gave us the other $2 million June of 2020.
[SPEAKER_13]: So it was a total of $4.4 million.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, yeah, thank you so much for letting me know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll have to play here a little while, and I appreciate you doing that.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can do with it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Good.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I felt like I was like, hey, she's listening to my car at that time.
[SPEAKER_12]: Melissa, tell us why the...
[SPEAKER_12]: We have to take him there and then they sign that they're responsible for it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, that's for hospital
[SPEAKER_13]: But I think that, if I'm not mistaken, you might double check with them down there.
[SPEAKER_13]: But they have money in there on their books.
[SPEAKER_13]: Like, is that the commissary or whatever?
[SPEAKER_13]: From the inmate's book.
[SPEAKER_13]: Like, whenever you're in jail and I put $100 on your books for you to buy commissary stuff, if there's money in there, I think they will take it from there.
[SPEAKER_13]: I know they do the doctor business.
[SPEAKER_13]: We have to pay for doctor visits too, but if the inmate has them on their books, then they have to pay for their office visits.
[SPEAKER_12]: I am just guessing.
[SPEAKER_12]: But the amounts that we're paying is not...
[SPEAKER_12]: ever taken care of by that unless they're i mean because we're just we're looking at the cost yeah there are some programs out there to to get that now but i didn't want to call them unless you told me what our situation is and maybe we need to talk to the sheriff's office
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, this one, there is one, and it's $1,500.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, I mean, that's $18,000 a year for one person.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because when you say if they put money in that commissary, that might be
[SPEAKER_12]: So, I'm going to call on that.
[SPEAKER_12]: I will, too.
[SPEAKER_12]: What did you say?
[SPEAKER_12]: It might be a good thing to get arrested.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let me get arrested.
[SPEAKER_02]: I need to pay for it.
[SPEAKER_13]: This is frustrating because with blood pressure medicine, they were probably honest before they got in there.
[SPEAKER_13]: Like, you know, they're afraid that their family or whatever would bring not blood pressure medicine to them.
[SPEAKER_13]: But then some of them, they should have been on medication, but they didn't until they get to the jail.
[SPEAKER_13]: This is killing me.
This is killing me.
[SPEAKER_13]: This is a capital improvement for a rover.
[SPEAKER_13]: This was for replacing the lighting in a freezer room and a storage room in the jail.
[SPEAKER_13]: Do you want that capital improvement or should we get it from buildings and grants?
[SPEAKER_13]: to me it's just, it's maintenance, it's repairing.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, he's putting, it wouldn't even exist in life.
[SPEAKER_13]: I would say this is building some grounds in my capital.
[SPEAKER_12]: And here's another one.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, they just made a writer out of this?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, this would be building some grounds.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: Install writing and sell proxy with one ceiling outlet on the east end of the jail.
[SPEAKER_13]: And then this one, guys, is the security camera system.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, this is victory.
[SPEAKER_13]: This is where they got the security system from.
[SPEAKER_13]: So this is the total amount, our half, and then the judge is paying for half of it for the interior of the building from his specialty.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: And that's what was agreed upon, right?
[SPEAKER_13]: Correct.
[SPEAKER_12]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_12]: Thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_12]: Really, last month was, yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's good.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: I love those reports.
[SPEAKER_13]: Good.
[SPEAKER_13]: Victory Technology and Capital Improvement.
[SPEAKER_12]: And then I presented them with the May sales and use tax report.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you ever look at that road on Waller Road?
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, thank you.
[SPEAKER_11]: Waller Road and Kay?
[SPEAKER_12]: And Clay has that on his list, right?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes, ma'am.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it's not terrible, terrible, but it's interesting.
[SPEAKER_12]: Did you see the wires or whatever it was he was talking about?
[SPEAKER_12]: Not very, very deep.
[SPEAKER_12]: What is the origin of the meeting or the activities?
[SPEAKER_12]: It is going to be on file.
[SPEAKER_12]: Vantage points.
[SPEAKER_12]: which is a one-second graph.
[SPEAKER_12]: So let's do it on... You don't have to do that.
[SPEAKER_12]: So we can do it both days if you want.
[SPEAKER_12]: We need to go for budget.
[SPEAKER_12]: Do we need two days?
[SPEAKER_04]: Some people can have...
this.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's set to an application for the process for a discount, a big discount.
[SPEAKER_12]: It usually takes just one to two weeks.
[SPEAKER_12]: I was kind of wondering if there was, after a commission meeting, if we wanted to do a little work day, just pulling weeds and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: We did that last year.
[SPEAKER_12]: I just think, I mean, an hour of five people would pull a lot of weeds.
[SPEAKER_12]: Unless maybe 4-H would like to come up and do that.
[SPEAKER_12]: They said they wanted to do projects, okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, I think that would be great.
[SPEAKER_12]: I just, maybe we could.
[SPEAKER_12]: I wonder who we would ask in 4-H. Good morning.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good morning.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good morning, how are you?
[SPEAKER_02]: Morning.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good morning.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do y'all remember Darshana?
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_10]: Good to have Robert.
[SPEAKER_00]: Good morning.
[SPEAKER_00]: I remember you, Robert.
[SPEAKER_00]: How's it going?
[SPEAKER_00]: It's going good.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: You get to see me when Travis's calendar gets too full.
[SPEAKER_10]: His calendar's pretty full.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who do we have at the commissioner's office?
[SPEAKER_12]: Just myself, Sheila Tracy, and... Go ahead.
[SPEAKER_12]: Max is out today.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: What have I done?
[SPEAKER_02]: I spoke my mind.
[SPEAKER_13]: Then that's Heather and Melissa?
[SPEAKER_13]: No, Melissa's not in here.
[SPEAKER_13]: These are just citizens.
[SPEAKER_13]: Brianna Rock and Kirk Croy, and then...
Hello, everybody.
[SPEAKER_08]: It looks like we only have one subrecipient standing.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Connie, do you have a thing for us for City Homestead with Great River Engineering?
I do.
Good morning, everyone.
[SPEAKER_01]: Homestead had their bid opening April 15th, and as you know, we had kind of a delay due to the contractor being an hour late.
[SPEAKER_01]: So we have worked through Travis and made sure that we took the right steps to make sure that we followed procurement rules and we were able to have Ray County waived
[SPEAKER_01]: bid on May, let's see, April 29th.
[SPEAKER_01]: Red River reviewed the bid and met with Holstein Village on May 6th.
[SPEAKER_01]: The bid was for $202,000.
[SPEAKER_01]: out of office through yesterday for Mother's Day, so I haven't had a chance to scan it in, but I will give that to everyone within the next few days.
[SPEAKER_01]: So Homestead Village has issued a notice of award, and the contractor is working through their bonding documents, the payment and performance bonds.
[SPEAKER_01]: They said they should have those by Friday.
[SPEAKER_01]: They did only have 10 days from notice of award, so
[SPEAKER_01]: Our aim, our schedule was to get the notice of award processed and going to notice to proceed and have that contract signed no later than May 22nd.
[SPEAKER_01]: The contractor has 120 days in their contract, so that brings us to September 19th.
[SPEAKER_01]: We have an 11-day wiggle room to hit that September 30th deadline.
[SPEAKER_01]: So that's for the treatment facility.
[SPEAKER_01]: In the meantime, the bid was $202,000.
[SPEAKER_01]: So they still have monies.
[SPEAKER_01]: They wanted to use any funds that were not being put on the treatment facility to repair their collection system, which is in dire need of replacement.
[SPEAKER_01]: So they did have a line break Sunday, and they're going to have to pay cash out of pocket to repair that pipe.
[SPEAKER_01]: But for the full run of that pipe, they are getting three quotes, one included from the contractor we already have a contract with to change orders
[SPEAKER_01]: If their quote's too high, we'll compare a few others.
[SPEAKER_01]: But we also have, I'm calling it a piggyback contract, but it's a contract that Mega KC has with, I believe it's Cass County in Missouri and Johnson County Wastewater in Kansas for hourly collection system repairs.
[SPEAKER_01]: clause that that bidding document could be used by other Missouri communities.
[SPEAKER_01]: So we will use that contract to change order in as much as we can in the collection system over the next three months.
[SPEAKER_01]: They are out of compliance on their treatment facility.
[SPEAKER_01]: So it's a balancing act to make sure that the treatment facility
[SPEAKER_01]: is in compliant and installed whether that means they need to you know change order in any issues that arise i need to make sure that they have those funds available and they don't just go spend it all on the collection system so the next six weeks are going to be fun for us as we do our pre-construction meeting and mobilize with the contractor but i'm excited so hopefully
[SPEAKER_01]: as long as things go well and we keep on that contract or we should be doing a substantial walk through early September.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: Any from the commission?
[SPEAKER_10]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_08]: My suggestion, Connie, if the commission agrees, would be to I think Ballpark, you have about 400
[SPEAKER_08]: thousand dollars still remaining to be spent.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a little bit more than that, but about 400,000.
[SPEAKER_08]: So if the contractor is for 202, that still leaves around 200,000.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, let's get those invoices in now.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that lease of 200 is half of it, you know, is spent before we get to that really tight time crunch in September.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sure, absolutely, yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Does that sound okay to you, Sheila?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_12]: For sure.
[SPEAKER_12]: That way we won't be chasing it at the last minute.
[SPEAKER_12]: We'll just have those of you.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's do what we can now so that at least 50% we're not chasing it at the last minute.
[SPEAKER_08]: Right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Perfect.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Connie, I will send you an email.
[SPEAKER_08]: But just to get us started, you know, so that we have everything now, it'll be the, it'll be the interagency agreement for that clause for the wastewater collection.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just so that we have the, that compliance part in place before we look at the invoices.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, I have it on hand.
[SPEAKER_08]: I can submit after this meeting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Perfect.
[SPEAKER_08]: That'd be great.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: It sounds like a plan.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was looking at, I know Melissa's not there, but I did want to say that she did a great job with the ARPA reporting, with her accounting and with having the numbers.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, it's just a pleasure to work with her.
[SPEAKER_08]: She does.
[SPEAKER_12]: She does a great job for us.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Your outstanding awards right now are the Homestead.
[SPEAKER_08]: You have a little bit of a budget for your yearly auditors for the single audit.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then you have a little bit nested for ourselves and for Travis's friend, for their services as well.
[SPEAKER_12]: That is good money well spent because you all have just been great to oversee us and we appreciate that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Amazing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Our next thing is July 8th.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, we'll be ready.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think this is a record.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think so, too.
[SPEAKER_10]: I like it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, thank you, guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you all.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you so much.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you, Connie.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, thank you.
[SPEAKER_10]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_10]: Bye, Robert.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, with that, is there anything else that you want to discuss this morning?
[SPEAKER_04]: Not today.
[SPEAKER_12]: Is there any other business that should come before the commission?
[SPEAKER_12]: No?
[SPEAKER_02]: Motion to adjourn.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let me go pay for sunshine requests.