[SPEAKER_00]: Morning.
Thanks, sir.
I'll be right with you.
Thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think you're going to ask a lot of questions or anything like that.
And he's learning to promote it and try to get more people.
All right, how about you?
Surviving?
We are surviving.
[SPEAKER_06]: Can't decide if it wants to be winters or summer.
[SPEAKER_02]: Letting go all over the place this year.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I left my phone out.
[SPEAKER_06]: I am waiting for a phone call that I may have to take.
[SPEAKER_06]: So if so, you just...
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, when you get old,
[SPEAKER_06]: And it seems like the mushroom festival went well.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, it was.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was really good.
[SPEAKER_03]: A lot of people.
[SPEAKER_06]: A lot of people.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I thought they did a nice job of bringing it.
Oh.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just thought that they.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was on top of that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I couldn't hear something.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Isn't it interesting how things just change?
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, like they struggle getting people to help put together.
[SPEAKER_06]: So there's lots of business issues that people are facing with employees and that kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Good to have you back.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, no, it didn't happen again.
[SPEAKER_06]: and you're supposed to get the same thing, but if no one else in the world says good morning to me, my phone is the one that says good morning.
[SPEAKER_06]: So if everyone else in the world is mad at me, my phone is the one that says good morning.
[SPEAKER_05]: It will, it'll tell you the weather and everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: Boy, the concrete around the courthouse.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, it looks so good.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it's so nice for the, for the, when they pull up with the prisoners, you can, you still have room to get by.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is she happy?
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good.
[SPEAKER_06]: Brie, I'm going to give you information about asphalt companies that we're partnering with the city of Richmond.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: The mayor sent that to me over the weekend, so don't let me get out of here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Without giving that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: He sent it to me, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_06]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_06]: The name of the companies?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: I called the mayor because we had planned on this, and Max said, we don't want to miss the boat, they're here working.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I called him.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, that's a different project, so they haven't started yet on what we're going to piggyback with the city.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's happening right now is water contract, so.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it'll be down the road a little bit, maybe a month or six weeks.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if we'll be able to pull it off or not.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've got your, I will send you, I've got your information.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, let me do that and then.
I'll do it.
I will do it before I do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: This day that you have given us the opportunity to just excel in, we pray that you would keep us focused on what we need to do, what we do to honor you.
[SPEAKER_02]: We pray for our county.
[SPEAKER_02]: We pray for the citizens of our county.
[SPEAKER_02]: Unite us together in a common good.
[SPEAKER_02]: We pray for the elected officials and the workers here in the county, that you would just work through them, put a hedge of protection around their family, keep them safe and healthy in all that they do.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just bless them richly.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you have anything today?
[SPEAKER_06]: And moving on down the agenda, to approve the minutes, Max will be here tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_06]: So why don't we table that till tomorrow?
[SPEAKER_03]: Do we have a motion?
[SPEAKER_06]: I second.
[SPEAKER_06]: All those in favor?
[SPEAKER_03]: Aye.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll do that tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_06]: And we have some invoices to...
Okay.
We're not doing that today.
No, no.
We're doing it tomorrow.
You're not?
Okay.
I'll figure that out.
He just sent an email.
Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Amen.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it would be curious in a couple weeks for us to look at fuel for like the sheriff's
[SPEAKER_06]: the difference i just just curious no i would be curious too yeah we contracted in fact we just did that i think just so we got it we get that but i don't think that that's just for golden bridge that's not for sure i don't think so either
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just curious.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think we talked about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: The only contract we have on fuel is with Red Kill.
[SPEAKER_03]: One through Shell is just, we get a discount, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll tell you what, the accidents on I-7 is just starting to 136, so it is 272.
[SPEAKER_06]: I did.
[SPEAKER_06]: Trying to think.
[SPEAKER_06]: Friday, I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: I came in town and thought about trying to go into the old jail and take some pictures.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, that wasn't a good day because of Mushroom Festival.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I just went up and turned the corner.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it hit me that...
[SPEAKER_06]: last year so I called him and said include that let us know what it is and he said he would and said in my mind I was thinking about somebody put a sign up there with grass so we just wanted to be sure that we did that and Max did that once last year with him maybe when they were in the process he said he just saw Max somewhere and realized it was high and Max told him to go ahead and do it but it was just a one time thing but I told him
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, we've already got this bunch done.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, that's all I have, guys.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, that was easy.
[SPEAKER_07]: I gave them the April balance report.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then one of the society's
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks, Melissa.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you.
I want to ask you a question.
When we work with this, just trying to keep track of that a little bit, this is the capital improvement.
Was that probably for the sidewalks?
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you have a mission for this one?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to go ask Trayden.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was going to show you.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just wanted to kind of watch that.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was the this month, wasn't that in May?
[SPEAKER_06]: So then I'm just trying to keep track in my mind where that was.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, so we have approved birth variables and now we're gonna talk about the day of prayer, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: I need to leave by, it's at one o'clock or is it?
[SPEAKER_06]: And we're going to try to go over after we adjourn session to the Humane Society building to take some pictures for us.
[SPEAKER_06]: a little bit of time, you can jump right in.
[SPEAKER_02]: It would just be, it would be a really good deal for you.
[SPEAKER_03]: So do we have a motion to?
[SPEAKER_06]: that we are recognizing the National Day of Prayer tomorrow here at the courthouse.
[SPEAKER_03]: I made the motion to recognize the National Day of Prayer on May 7th, 2026 here at the courthouse.
[SPEAKER_06]: I second that motion and all those in favor, aye.
[SPEAKER_06]: And we will be reading the resolution tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anything else?
[SPEAKER_06]: Is there anything you want to tell us about?
[SPEAKER_02]: I talked with Mike
[SPEAKER_05]: and then Stacey will be here at 9 today to go pod some ordinances.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think she walked by you in the middle right there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, she kind of has some pain rules.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, she does.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, very good.
[SPEAKER_06]: We kind of went through that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Check, check, check.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a great question.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll be right back.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why are we here?
[SPEAKER_05]: The light in the first row back in the house.
[SPEAKER_05]: Perfect.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I think we are caught up until Stacy gets here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Can you think of, I'm trying to list some things that we need to go back to that maybe we've missed.
[SPEAKER_06]: We've talked about the ankle bracelets.
[SPEAKER_06]: We never did figure anything out with that contract.
[SPEAKER_05]: I did get Judge Walden's receptionist, or not receptionist, I'm so sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Her assistant has said that he will come and let us know when he has availability to come and talk to you guys about that, but I'm not too sure.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, so just making a sticky note.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: The other thing, have you heard, Max, I know we've got a lot of balls in the air, what is happening on the Buffalo Bridge down the garden where they're maybe buying the
[SPEAKER_06]: the tube and we're putting it in or vice versa.
[SPEAKER_06]: Should we know where that is?
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, so that's a question on that.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then some of these other bridge contracts, not bridge contracts, bridge projects that we just kind of need to
[SPEAKER_03]: And he said he'd get back with us.
[SPEAKER_06]: Would you please say anything about that?
[SPEAKER_06]: The need at Waller Road and K, was that it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Waller and K. Is that?
[SPEAKER_06]: I did let him know.
[SPEAKER_06]: You let him know that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I did let him know.
[SPEAKER_06]: The reason I was following up on that, it was someone from the street department in Richmond that must be out there that said...
[SPEAKER_06]: Here was utility wires showing.
[SPEAKER_06]: The rain had washed it, but there was some gravel.
[SPEAKER_03]: So just, well, I thought it was.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was what I told you, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Waller and Cain.
[SPEAKER_03]: Right down to my house.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can check that.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, can you think of anything else we need to follow up on?
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'll send him an email, Clay, today, just more of an update for Rose and what that would be like.
[SPEAKER_01]: You all asked me to wait three months for bringing up that planning and zoning tool that I built three months ago.
[SPEAKER_06]: We can talk about that on other business.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just think right now that we're just – I just don't think we're in a place there.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that was our opinion.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was then and now that we're just not ready to move forward with something new at this point.
[SPEAKER_06]: if you have a different, I mean, that was the way, we have had no discussion, Kurt, about it since then, and that was the thought.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, everyone seemed pretty motivated when I demonstrated it, so that's interesting to see such a change.
[SPEAKER_06]: You mean we were very?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, everyone seemed pretty excited that it would help them.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, we were interested.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was an interesting presentation.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's some other things I think that planning and zoning is doing that, just trying to work through some of those things.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you have a copy of the agenda for tomorrow?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, ma'am.
[SPEAKER_06]: Would you like to have a black one, please?
And there you go.
Right.
Okay.
Perfect.
That's what I wanted to see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you want me to just remind you to put it like that?
[SPEAKER_06]: So maybe it's a big difference.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what I'm sure.
That's all I can figure out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I didn't hear anything.
[SPEAKER_06]: We should receive it.
[SPEAKER_06]: You mean chip and seal and asphalt?
[SPEAKER_02]: When I was a kid, they'd come through and they'd drop oil on the ground, and then they'd come through with a truck and go up the ground.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not sure.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's not chip and seal, is it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Chip and seal, I thought, was already mixed.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, that's a dirty word to me.
[SPEAKER_06]: I go kind of bonkers at that.
And we've got 10 miles of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: That is three years ago that needs one.
[SPEAKER_06]: I am sending you this information.
[SPEAKER_06]: Would you put it on something for Max to see?
[SPEAKER_06]: This is the asphalt company that the cities are using that we need to ask them to put on a Word document.
[SPEAKER_07]: Great.
[SPEAKER_07]: Where are we going to put...
[SPEAKER_06]: the Eagleton battle.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or we can do that any time because of sale.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we can do it tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, ma'am.
Thank you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, you are.
[SPEAKER_04]: They should be up really shortly.
All right, let me know.
All right.
They'll be up in just a second.
How's your day going?
[SPEAKER_06]: Each one of the plants, we also do an ordinance for.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right.
[SPEAKER_04]: After it's reported.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was what I was.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, so this is Valley View.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is Tammy Williams' event venue.
[SPEAKER_04]: They, all of the acreage that was here was tied in with, is that right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, this was a lot itself.
[SPEAKER_04]: The rest of it was tied in over here.
[SPEAKER_04]: They decided to cut this off, make a separate lot, and put this in with the venue so a V2 zoning would follow
The very first time I did it, my thumb, I thought I was going to lose my finger now.
I look good.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, we have here, this was two 10-acre lots.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're taking the bottoms.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, it's two 10-acre lots, and they're just the second 10-acre lot.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're combining some of that with their houses and leaving three acres for their daughter to go.
[SPEAKER_06]: That sounds sad.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a good thing, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: This guy owned property on both sides of the highway.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it just a piece that was sitting there?
[SPEAKER_04]: should be fairly quick then i'm guessing my signature is different
[SPEAKER_04]: I have no idea.
[SPEAKER_04]: Doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, as long as we got approval on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it matters so that I know what the hell I'm talking about.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, there's nothing MoDOT involved on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: off into two lots to sell both of them.
[SPEAKER_04]: And he's got no not approval.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is a repat because the individual that owns this lot paid zero attention to his lot lines and built literally on the middle of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: So contacted them to repat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Same thing happened there too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Both of them were on the wrong spot.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, and City of Excelsior is okay with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just because... Yeah, which we wouldn't change anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'd have to fight them to begin with.
[SPEAKER_04]: In my opinion, I wouldn't have allowed it to, you know, get it going.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love that shirt you have.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's stick around.
[SPEAKER_06]: So when we talk about those resolutions, we do that after they're recorded.
[SPEAKER_06]: Does the recorder get a hold of you all after resolutions on what?
[SPEAKER_06]: Code stuff?
[SPEAKER_06]: Not resolutions, but ordinances.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ordinances that we then sign, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: After the class is recorded, yes, then I do the ordinance or we go in the ordinance and bring it up.
[SPEAKER_04]: the property owner provide us two receipts or they are to obtain two receipts when they go to the reporter's office.
[SPEAKER_04]: They keep one, they give us one.
[SPEAKER_04]: That way we know it had been done with book and page.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just wasn't sure how that process.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, we make them bring us a receipt now because before we had stuff that would
[SPEAKER_04]: property, which is fine as long as they have over 19 acres.
[SPEAKER_04]: They do under nine acres.
[SPEAKER_04]: So they sell move whatever the mobile home isn't supposed to stay with the property.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the other one is a hardships just a temporary so that they can have they can stay in the existing residence while
[SPEAKER_04]: He, apparently it's a mobile home that has a shed built over it, and he's gonna have the mobile home removed out from there so that he can keep the building that is enclosing, that they put around it for storage, so.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it's, where's Tyler?
[SPEAKER_04]: Who are we talking about?
[SPEAKER_04]: Tyler Dunn.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, he is an Excelsior up at 124th.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: The one that's invading the right-of-way?
[SPEAKER_04]: That one?
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that him?
[SPEAKER_04]: It is him.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not my jurisdiction.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good luck with that!
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, so this is a rezoning order to drive a flat from last month.
[SPEAKER_04]: These are all residential.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're all rezoning on flats that were previously approved.
[SPEAKER_05]: How much is the acreage on the one he's selling?
[SPEAKER_04]: a plaque that was tabled they were asking for a b2 zoning on a small portion of the property their first class was a two lot split we had a complaint they tabled it we went out we looked at the property they have a small car lot on the property
[SPEAKER_04]: So we advise them to rezone that portion of the property because you're, how far off of B2 are you?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like less than a quarter of a mile, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, you know, close to the highway, not a big deal, never had any complaints on it, didn't even know it was there.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we advise them to rezone that portion of the property to B2 so they can continue to sell their vehicles.
[SPEAKER_04]: Basically making it a compliance plan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Letters went out saying this is what we're doing.
[SPEAKER_04]: In comes an individual with a complaint.
[SPEAKER_04]: One shows up at the meeting.
[SPEAKER_04]: For whatever reason, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, this has been there for years.
[SPEAKER_04]: How many years you guys been there?
[SPEAKER_07]: Three years.
[SPEAKER_04]: Three years.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nobody's ever said a word.
[SPEAKER_04]: But now here we are.
[SPEAKER_04]: So the board did not approve the B2 zoning for the 0.85 acres.
[SPEAKER_04]: They had concerns about what you do if it spreads beyond the 0.85 acres.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's going to police that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's going to keep an eye on it?
[SPEAKER_04]: And it also opens up that area.
[SPEAKER_04]: especially if there's no septic on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: So a lot of things would require a septic.
[SPEAKER_04]: Their house is right next door.
[SPEAKER_04]: They do mostly internet sales, not a lot of foot traffic.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I, you know, it's things that would be potentially of concern for a permitted use requires a actual permit to be blessed and to be granted.
[SPEAKER_04]: if somebody wanted to do something after the fact in 50 years if they didn't own it.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's not like they're going to be able to do anything if there was another ownership or change in ownership with that zoning.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you guys have like some options?
[SPEAKER_04]: Send it back to the Planning and Zoning Board for further review?
[SPEAKER_04]: recommendation or you can overturn the planning and zoning board's recommendation.
[SPEAKER_04]: So the recommendation is to not approve.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right.
[SPEAKER_04]: They did not approve the B2 zoning.
[SPEAKER_04]: And this is what the walk looks like.
[SPEAKER_04]: Where they have the, this was the plan.
[SPEAKER_04]: So they had like 40 acres.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is being cut out for the sun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: To build a house on.
[SPEAKER_04]: This one I think they had a contract on to sell.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is the one where their house is.
[SPEAKER_04]: The house sits right here.
[SPEAKER_04]: And this is the little lot where the building is with the car sitting on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I asked them to vote on the zoning first because we couldn't approve the plot with that lot.
[SPEAKER_04]: It has to be absorbed into the restaurant.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think they have some concerns and they'd like to visit with you guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why don't you all give us some comments?
[SPEAKER_06]: We know a lot more about this than we do.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I am interested in hearing your perspective.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay, so I believe, so we didn't go, and I missed it, I don't know how I missed it, but we didn't go, but the concern was the property wasn't big enough, is what I hear, is it needed to be bigger, more acreage.
[SPEAKER_00]: We own all the ground around it, so we can
[SPEAKER_00]: rechanged to make it bigger if we have to.
[SPEAKER_00]: We were under the impression that, so there's businesses in the county that, and there are car dealerships and there's other businesses and stuff that, I mean, they consume business, but their property's not commercial, but their building is.
[SPEAKER_00]: That was a concern.
[SPEAKER_00]: of discretion for us because of the acreage.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I don't see that that should be a problem.
[SPEAKER_04]: What he's saying is basically how the real estate assessor assesses these particular places that are clearly in an ag zoning that have been operating a business that we, yeah, forever or that we're just not even aware exist.
[SPEAKER_04]: And when the real estate assessor finds out that a commercial operation of any fashion is being operated there, that building and maybe even a smidge of ground around it is taxed commercially and that it's assessed according to use.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then the remaining portion of the ground is assessed as ag, which is separate from planning.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right, we have zoning.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they assess according to use.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's two completely different mindsets, but I'll go hand in hand.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I really don't think it's that the ground isn't big enough, 0.85A versus 1. whatever it turned out to be.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the fact that if it does get outside,
[SPEAKER_04]: is it going to create problems?
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's keeping an eye on it to make sure it stays what it's supposed to be?
[SPEAKER_04]: That was the big thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or would these types of situations be better to push them through with a conditional use?
[SPEAKER_04]: You can't push it through if it's already in the book as a predetermined
[SPEAKER_04]: because conditional use is non-transferable.
[SPEAKER_04]: It can be revoked, but you can't just do it if there's already the definition and a label for what we're supposed to do with it.
[SPEAKER_03]: What do they need to do to fulfill planning and zoning?
[SPEAKER_03]: Rezoning.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what makes it compliant.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's why I asked for them to go through the rezoning process because it was either that or the business dissolves.
[SPEAKER_07]: What is that?
[SPEAKER_04]: And you're very close to the highway.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it's not like you have to travel, you know, a mile down the gravel to get to it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Not to mention it's not that easy.
[SPEAKER_06]: So the complaint wasn't big enough for the business.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's what we understand from the meeting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Can that be redone?
[SPEAKER_06]: It really isn't about the supply.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, they only...
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess they could go back deeper in the property, but the more area you have, the more, I mean, I feel like the size of the lot is not the issue.
[SPEAKER_04]: I feel like it needs to stay where it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: That way it is minimal.
[SPEAKER_04]: It does limit future things that might come up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right now they don't really have a place to put a septic system.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's not like something else in that zoning that would require a septic, you know, could go in there even if it does get sold off.
[SPEAKER_00]: My father don't want to grow any at all.
[SPEAKER_00]: We just kind of like, just like it is.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's 25, 26 units on there now that's comfortable for us.
[SPEAKER_00]: We don't have to have...
[SPEAKER_04]: It's very clean.
[SPEAKER_04]: They don't buy junk.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tell them how you buy the vehicles.
[SPEAKER_04]: All of our vehicles come from new car trading.
[SPEAKER_04]: All of our vehicles come directly from a new car store.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have a great relationship with them.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've been with them for three years.
[SPEAKER_04]: They don't buy auction vehicles.
[SPEAKER_04]: None of our vehicles are sitting there dearly.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're all, I've moved like 10 units sometimes a week.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're constantly moved.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everything is very uniform.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've done this for years, and he's done it for 40 years.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, this is not new.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess my thought is, again, I go back, this is just me, and then we can discuss however.
[SPEAKER_06]: I do like the processes.
[SPEAKER_06]: But possibly because you missed that meeting, I mean, we're hearing from you, and I, you know,
[SPEAKER_06]: If I were to make a decision, maybe starting from scratch, it might be different than this just coming into us.
[SPEAKER_06]: What if we send it back to so many?
[SPEAKER_04]: I would love for that because typically what happens is the surveyors represent the class.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's why they were not required to be there.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's why they weren't required to be there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Something that could be touchy, we need to just make sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: Any reason people are going to have to be there going forward that...
[SPEAKER_06]: well i just think hearing from you all knowing that you keep a clean you know a clean area and it's it's not like you know you drive down that roads and other places and you know you wouldn't want that in your county but you all have maintained that really well i would just like for us to
[SPEAKER_06]: kind of tell your story and to represent what you all are doing and give this planning and something toward another opportunity here and here every day.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think you're right, but I guess from my perspective, one thing that I would ask is they don't need to be considering who's going to be enforcing
[SPEAKER_01]: anything else, I mean, we've got a lot of stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: We're on a sales that nobody's enforcing those things, so that should be a consideration for the board.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I guess, do we have a motion that on this project or this plan that we give another opportunity and just be sure that you all can schedule that
[SPEAKER_06]: So we're going to give this back to you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, yeah, we can't.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for coming in.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_06]: And actually, it's nice to know you're there.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wasn't aware that you offered that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just thought I just bought my daughter a car, and I wish I would have known that.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a nice meeting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Off of BB.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, Highway BB.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's some good looking trucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just looked at the picture and said my son's going further away for college in August this time of year.
[SPEAKER_04]: So is this a marketing point?
[SPEAKER_04]: Right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I wish.
[SPEAKER_07]: Right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I'll send you guys an email or something so that you can make sure you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
I second that.
All those in favor?