[SPEAKER_04]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks for getting me those.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you know how I can get the rest of those emails?
[SPEAKER_05]: Or who might have them?
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
I can't get along.
I do pretty good with that.
I was wondering.
Turn it around and try to get it past.
So my mother had magnets on all of her.
I have a problem with this.
Thank you.
What about that?
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
Let Brianne know so she can change the agenda.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to hold that following for another week.
[SPEAKER_09]: day to experience your goodness and your grace.
[SPEAKER_09]: We pray your blessing upon our county.
[SPEAKER_09]: We pray that you would continue to work to unite the people of this county for common good and pray for the elected officials and workers representing us, that you would give them wisdom and knowledge to make the best decisions possible, guide and direct their actions, that they would be honorable.
[SPEAKER_09]: We thank you in advance for all you have planned for today and throughout this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: And Lord, we just ask that you would continue to encourage
[SPEAKER_09]: And love on us and help us to love one another.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you, man, for all you do and for your love and your presence here.
In Jesus' name, amen.
Amen.
Thank you so much.
[SPEAKER_08]: And thank everybody for what they've done for the recognition.
[SPEAKER_08]: child abuse today, and that begins at 11.30, so that's why most of us are in blue.
[SPEAKER_08]: That is the color, and Julie's worked really hard decorating the yard, so anyway, thank you so much, Julie.
[SPEAKER_08]: Has everybody signed in that would like to make a comment?
[SPEAKER_04]: The first thing I wanted to ask Max was about the ditch that I've been asking you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who are you talking to and what are you telling them?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I keep seeing them drive up and down my road, but they put a ditch on the opposite side of...
[SPEAKER_04]: I've brought this up multiple times, about Don, I kind of have to hold you accountable since you're my, you're responsible for my side of the county now.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm not getting taken care of.
[SPEAKER_04]: So also, since I've brought this up many times, today I'm releasing f3oads.com, f is for fix, so that people in the county can report issues
[SPEAKER_04]: those will be routed from that website to the appropriate special road districts, and y'all's email address.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then we'll have an open map of all the issues that people have submitted to the county, and if they need to be fixed or not.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: The question I had about the new custodian of record, since the price, I guess, is changing on submitting sunshine requests, are we going to, are y'all going to respect the old rate for issues or sunshine requests that were submitted prior to that change?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Up to
[SPEAKER_04]: If there's sunshine requests that weren't filled before then, should I resubmit them?
[SPEAKER_04]: And is the contact address, email address the same or is it different?
[SPEAKER_04]: What did you have that wasn't completed?
[SPEAKER_04]: There was some other requests that I had made about when you guys go into a closed session and you vote on...
[SPEAKER_04]: like vote on people, like your performance, or not performance, individuals that work in the county, then the votes are supposed to be made public 72 hours later, so that's one, I have some other ones too, but if they weren't responding to you, should I just resubmit those?
[SPEAKER_10]: If you would resubmit those.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: I believe that we're waiting on legal on those.
[SPEAKER_10]: Same at Melville.
[SPEAKER_10]: going forward for the time being yeah it may get a new one but for the time being okay
[SPEAKER_01]: to the problem that's been going on over there.
[SPEAKER_01]: The rock's been dumped on my hill so many times.
[SPEAKER_01]: When it rains, it just washes the rock right off, and it wound up, it plugged up my pipe.
[SPEAKER_01]: I dug it out, and I had a skid loader out there to come out and make sure I could get in and out because it washes so bad.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's been ongoing.
[SPEAKER_01]: I retired out of 101.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm not saying I know it all, but I'm glad I'm motivated for basically 30 years.
[SPEAKER_01]: The guy the other day tried to cut the ditch out.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, you don't want to accelerate the water.
[SPEAKER_01]: You want to slow it down so it doesn't wash in that particular area.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'll buy a new pipe, but I think the county could maybe bring it back over there and put it in for me, and we can come to a resolution of the hill.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've got pictures of it, I can show you.
[SPEAKER_01]: It didn't even need to be cut out.
[SPEAKER_01]: When it rained now, it just put so much water down the hill, I can't even get out of my driveway.
[SPEAKER_01]: And what is your address?
[SPEAKER_01]: 1434 Aikenwood, Raymoor.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's Raymoor and Clevenger.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know my neighbor, I don't know her real well, but I know she may have been a thorn to guys I've talked to on the bedroom, said they're afraid to even look that way when they go by, you know.
[SPEAKER_01]: But that ain't getting anything done.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, and I'm not criticizing them, it's just, it needs to be done.
[SPEAKER_01]: I am, but I kind of work with the roads throughout the county.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's a lot of traffic on that road.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, you have a, you know where you need some discussion for a solution, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had something else.
[SPEAKER_04]: On the Sunshine Request stuff, you're requiring pre-candid for research stuff now, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: If I cannot put, like, can I have an account where I just put, like, $100 on and it's rolled through, or do I have to, like, pay individual requests?
[SPEAKER_10]: Or just individual requests.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'd have to do more accounting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anything else from...
[SPEAKER_00]: Speaking of the road, Lindsay and I actually have been preparing a Google Doc form for you to put on your website.
[SPEAKER_00]: We were going to submit it to you guys for approval.
[SPEAKER_00]: So we feel like if there's a form, it should come from the county, not an individual.
[SPEAKER_00]: So we have that Google Doc form ready for you to review and see if you want to put it on your website so people can turn their road complaints in.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's an actual county approved form.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I think that's what we have to think about if we're getting things from lots of different places.
[SPEAKER_08]: It seems like the overall one that we would be responsible for looking is something that we've initiated.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, I mean, there could be lots of things out there, but I'm just saying I personally feel like that we need something that is county run, that that's our go-to document.
[SPEAKER_00]: So we'll get
[SPEAKER_08]: We have a whole bunch of minutes to approach them.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you.
And seven, eight, nine.
[SPEAKER_05]: How are you doing?
[SPEAKER_05]: Good.
[SPEAKER_05]: How's everything going?
[SPEAKER_07]: Very.
[SPEAKER_07]: Busy?
[SPEAKER_05]: Very happening.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good.
[SPEAKER_05]: Glad for it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you.
Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's that?
Thank you.
Yeah, she'll be over here soon.
Okay.
Who did the board on the west side?
[SPEAKER_07]: The vaulted board out there?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: It looks amazing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Tell her I said that.
[SPEAKER_07]: It looks very nice.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe steps, the museum, the museum roof.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, I've had so many people very excited.
[SPEAKER_10]: It certainly needed it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, it did.
[SPEAKER_08]: By how many years?
[SPEAKER_10]: The best I can find is somebody said it was almost 45 years old.
[SPEAKER_10]: I can't believe some of that wood would do it under there.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was beautiful.
[SPEAKER_10]: A lot of it was beautiful.
[SPEAKER_10]: Some of it was not.
[SPEAKER_10]: Most of it was under there.
[SPEAKER_08]: They don't make it like they used to.
Weather Guard?
On Weather Guard?
I think they sent that over to us.
To my unit.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll just give you a number if you can go on.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who is it?
[SPEAKER_10]: Jamie Sudo.
[SPEAKER_10]: S-U-D-E-A-R-D-O.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then when you do that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I figured it was, but I didn't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's a good question.
[SPEAKER_08]: We would like to say yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't think anybody really knows.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've gone all over the place on that.
[SPEAKER_10]: It kind of depends on what you're talking about.
[SPEAKER_10]: The standard is 30 foot total runway, 15 feet from the center line of the site.
[SPEAKER_10]: It extends past whatever utilities are there.
[SPEAKER_10]: So if you have telephone poles or something, it goes past that.
[SPEAKER_10]: For the purpose of nuclear,
[SPEAKER_10]: So it varies, and in some places, the attorney said it, whatever it is.
[SPEAKER_10]: Beautiful.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it kind of depends on where you're at.
[SPEAKER_10]: I wish I could give you a better answer, but I didn't come up with it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Is there some easement for the owners to get the property behind me?
[SPEAKER_01]: If they have a survey, I know this depends.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's probably 60 feet off the center of the road.
[SPEAKER_01]: My concern is the lady next door can do something to finish my, to fix my body.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, she won't complain if it's on her property or something, you know.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you can stop down in the planning and zoning office on the first floor, when you head out, we can look at it on the aerial and see where you're at.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: Does she have that too?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, because I'm taking it from Capital Group.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: She just needs to enter as a vendor.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what I thought.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: 3-12 and I talked to Gary because Jordan said they weren't ordering from them anymore so they got it set up on the reoccurring
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's something, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: I believe that goes into your... Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: We don't need to...
[SPEAKER_07]: So next time we're gonna be ready for it.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's up there on the Fredericksburg Road, Max.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hiring, you know, I like Herk, Herk, Lane.
[SPEAKER_08]: He put a subdivision in there and built a new road.
[SPEAKER_00]: That'd be nice.
[SPEAKER_00]: They'd have a road name on it, wouldn't it?
[SPEAKER_10]: So we will be maintaining it.
[SPEAKER_00]: But he has to petition the county first.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, he needs to write a letter.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: But when we do, we'll have to alert MoDOT so they add a jury in the jury.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
Yes.
Okay.
I will make a note.
that's when you're going to be able to send us in.
Thank you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think that is everything on payables.
[SPEAKER_08]: We have a motion.
[SPEAKER_08]: First of all, we need to untable the minutes from the 22nd and the 23rd.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, all those in favor?
[SPEAKER_08]: Aye.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then do we have a motion to approve those points?
[SPEAKER_10]: So moved.
[SPEAKER_08]: Aye.
[SPEAKER_08]: Second, and then all of us approve it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Then we also have, we have for 15 and,
[SPEAKER_08]: And Stacey, why don't we skip over to you?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's something I need to leave for.
[SPEAKER_08]: We don't have to leave for it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just excuse me.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just thought you could get back to it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, we're going to skip down to signing a document for planning and zoning.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I'm going to recuse myself from this.
[SPEAKER_08]: I actually mentioned this, hasn't it?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, so it's a plat for Tucker Razors.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess we just need a motion to approve this one.
[SPEAKER_07]: We have a motion to approve that.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: I need to receive a chair.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, Mr. O'Connor.
Thank you.
[SPEAKER_08]: And next we will do the progress report for Myers.
[SPEAKER_07]: Go here.
Start on the back.
All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm working my way forward.
Thank you.
They were all like that.
Yeah.
Oh, I have that right here.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's no signatures for that.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, there's not.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just wanted them to look at it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why don't we hold this and figure it out?
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think, and we'll let you know on this.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, I think we're ready to move on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, your projects.
[SPEAKER_03]: We've got a lot of stuff, and I know you guys have something at 10, so
[SPEAKER_03]: I got just a summary of the items I'm gonna talk to you guys about today.
[SPEAKER_03]: For bridges, next round of bureau applications, and then the first item, qualification-based selection.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know Max and I had a conversation that you guys were looking into.
[SPEAKER_03]: We were just discussing, how do you guys select this in the process of that?
[SPEAKER_03]: A bid process.
[SPEAKER_08]: And this is on which project?
[SPEAKER_03]: This is just in general.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is in general hiring an engineering firm.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's general hiring an engineer.
[SPEAKER_03]: So the Brooks Act at a federal level, when using federal money, you have to use qualification-based selection.
[SPEAKER_03]: How do you guys decide how to do that?
[SPEAKER_03]: Missouri has the mini-Brooks Act, which means it's the same thing, but it applies for both using federal money and not federal money, local money, that you use qualification-based selection.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I provided you guys two summaries, one staple, one not.
[SPEAKER_03]: The unstable one goes over how you can select a consultant for using local funds, just your guys' cash, and how you can use Modots on columnist, which is a qualification-based selection list, to select an engineer off that.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that's going to be like going to Sourcewell where it's already pre-bidded.
[SPEAKER_03]: just if you want to have perfect records, you can look at that list and consider three firms, look at their experience, if you want to give them a call and say, hey, do you do bridges?
[SPEAKER_03]: And then from there, you guys can decide what engineer you want to go with.
[SPEAKER_08]: And this is the MoDOT approved list?
[SPEAKER_03]: This is the MoDOT approved list that we as a company, Great River, have to submit qualifications for to get on that list.
[SPEAKER_03]: for selecting an engineer for a project with federal money.
[SPEAKER_03]: So this is what we did for, this is the process, what we did for Myers Road, where you guys are sitting here.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a process, but this goes into, this comes back to $200,000.
[SPEAKER_03]: If it's under $200,000 contract, you can, again, look at this list, evaluate consultants, and select.
[SPEAKER_03]: If it's over $200,000, you would do a formal request for quality.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then just to, so that is the... And when we're talking about the, just to clarify, we're talking about the $200,000 limit.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're talking about the fees to the engineering firm.
[SPEAKER_10]: Correct, yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Not the entire project.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, not the entire project.
[SPEAKER_10]: The fees to the engineering firm.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, the project is covered because you guys publicly bid that to the lowest responsible, responsible bidder.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so that's covered.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that is, that is the, this is the more robust method of selection.
[SPEAKER_03]: That being said, because the Brooks Act and the Me Brooks Act is not clear, it just says qualification-based selection.
[SPEAKER_03]: The third document, this kind of pamphlet, comes from the American Council of Engineering Companies of Missouri.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's kind of weighted toward Missouri, but their definition of qualification-based selection is, in a situation where you, the owner, have an existing relationship with a design profession, the firm you're working with has technical qualifications
[SPEAKER_03]: a qualification-based selection allows you to continue your current relationship without going after an RFQ process.
[SPEAKER_03]: You guys know we're, I mean, we were already on your guys' book, Doing Bridges.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know We Do Bridges.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you guys knowing we are qualified to do bridges allows you to select this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Honestly, I didn't completely wrap my mind around it until I generated all this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Never heard you go back over it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: So next up, Myers Road.
[SPEAKER_03]: We are still in design, but what I wanted to give you guys an update on, as we finish the superstructure, we decided that we can put a vertical curve on the bridge itself, that way lowering the entrance and exit grades so we can lower the approach roadways.
[SPEAKER_03]: and then a grading contour sheet.
[SPEAKER_03]: So very similar.
[SPEAKER_03]: But we are now, instead of the bridge having to come up, what did I say?
[SPEAKER_03]: Six feet?
[SPEAKER_03]: Six, seven, eight feet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now it's only a little over five, and it comes down a lot faster.
[SPEAKER_03]: So little gains.
[SPEAKER_05]: Still a lot.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is still a lot, but it is not as much.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then we are still in the substructure design.
[SPEAKER_03]: One of the comments was that he's being
[SPEAKER_03]: will go parallel to the railroad corridor.
[SPEAKER_03]: It will be to the driving surface elevation.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then what those will be comprised of is cast in place walls with a pile footing.
[SPEAKER_03]: So the wall will come down to more or less the spread footing if you were bearing directly on rock.
[SPEAKER_03]: But because under there is glacial tilt and not rock,
[SPEAKER_03]: It's hard until water touches it.
[SPEAKER_03]: As soon as water touches it, it dissolves into the ground.
[SPEAKER_03]: So the footing will then support piles that will go down to rock about 20 to 25 feet below that.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it will be a robust foundation system.
[SPEAKER_03]: But that is what we're going through in detail right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: You said rock 45 feet in?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's almost equal distance from the roadway to the rail and then from the rail down to rock.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: I believe we may only have to get temporary construction easements from two property owners, Joni Myers and Sharon Myers, and then Carl Winkle and Mary Van Winkle.
[SPEAKER_03]: I believe we may not need to get any sort of easements from Kristen Winkle.
[SPEAKER_03]: or Lee Snyder or Robin Snyder, as the railroad owns a lot of the property.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the railroad just allows them to be there?
[SPEAKER_03]: We're dealing with something very similar in Clay County right now, and the property owner is very upset to learn that the railroad can just claim property.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, they claimed property 100 years ago whenever they put in a railroad, and there's certainly records of it.
[SPEAKER_10]: We should be keeping the same alignment but What we were standing at that station Yes
[SPEAKER_03]: because it still will come up that one with the long driveway looks like it was still going to be 5 feet so it's still going to be it will be an incline but we'll work with them and see what we can do to make that happen with this situation so now that we're finalizing
[SPEAKER_03]: and if everything is going well, hopefully still being able to submit final plans June, July.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll keep you updated.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll definitely drag it off a little bit.
[SPEAKER_10]: But if that works, then when is construction?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, we'd have to bid it.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'd have to bid it.
[SPEAKER_03]: To get competitive bids, we'd have to give them probably a nine-month window to start.
[SPEAKER_03]: Once they start, they have so many days.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it'd be next spring.
[SPEAKER_03]: So the next one I want to talk to you guys about, so passing that over is the West 216 bridge.
[SPEAKER_03]: is less than 20 feet, the one that we discussed you guys wanted to do first play.
[SPEAKER_03]: Precast boxes.
[SPEAKER_03]: So this is the one that you would be setting?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I think that'd be a contractor.
[SPEAKER_03]: We don't have the equipment to set it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought that you guys would be setting this in place.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, we don't have the equipment to do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, that doesn't change too much.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, we still have the structure.
[SPEAKER_03]: That shouldn't change.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll hire a contractor, and they can just set these quite quickly because it's all pretty simple.
[SPEAKER_03]: So no work.
[SPEAKER_03]: You weren't anticipating any work.
[SPEAKER_03]: county forces you can cover them up yeah we can do that that kind of stuff but putting them in place is going to require somebody else okay does that answer your question it does um we'll probably have a conversation about setting up a contract documents for a
[SPEAKER_03]: It's been a while.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just from contract signing or going after the BROs?
[SPEAKER_08]: Just from when the whole process started.
[SPEAKER_10]: Probably more than a year before we got seen.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know I've talked to Modot, and they're concerned with the repair items, but I know that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Have you guys been going back and forth?
[SPEAKER_02]: We talked to the railroad.
[SPEAKER_02]: They came in and patched a couple of boards in it, so the holes aren't there anymore.
[SPEAKER_02]: But we're going to have to switch to a – they said if we keep it there, we'd have to switch to a yearly inspection instead of a two-year inspection.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what Modot said?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: We should be able to do this under contract and move it forward soon.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I think when I talked to Jerry Yost, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_03]: When I talked to Jerry, I informed him that this is under contract and this is in design.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I think that would alleviate his concerns.
[SPEAKER_03]: But he was pretty concerned that if there was no plans for it, then yeah, it's...
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll follow up with him.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm glad the railroad came in and patched those.
[SPEAKER_03]: But for the West 216 boxes, what we're proposing is two 12-foot lanes, and then the inlet and outlet would be a headwall, which would support
[SPEAKER_03]: If you're going to bid it, it's probably going to be Collins and Herman.
[SPEAKER_03]: One contractor would do it.
[SPEAKER_03]: They
[SPEAKER_03]: Especially if it's one contractor, then the contractor is ultimately responsible for hiring the sons that would install this and put the whole thing together.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the other thing, I know we were discussing right away, I want to bring up here on your guys' GIS map, it shows a 60-foot corridor right away.
[SPEAKER_03]: The structure would just fall within the 60-foot.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because you're hiring a contractor, I don't know if you guys have relationships with the property owners up and down the stream.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you wanted to go get a formal right-of-way or if you just wanted to have that conversation and say, hey, the bridge is out.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're going to replace it.
[SPEAKER_03]: We need to put some rock in the creek.
[SPEAKER_03]: Are you fine with us entering the property for the purpose of doing this and maintaining that?
[SPEAKER_03]: It doesn't need a formal decimate, unless you guys wanted a formal decimate.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because at the end of the day, it is just a signed letter.
[SPEAKER_03]: Moving on to that West 84th Street.
[SPEAKER_03]: So when I originally talked to you guys about this, we were looking at a
[SPEAKER_03]: How I got that is I looked up and downstream and looked at the natural bank and said, okay, well, this is the natural bank.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is what water frequently goes through and this is what the channel does.
[SPEAKER_03]: Once we completed the survey, we noticed this is a lot deeper than we thought.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is almost 18 feet deep.
[SPEAKER_03]: So standard practice when replacing a bridge is you don't want
[SPEAKER_03]: until you hit one foot below the bottom of your knee.
[SPEAKER_03]: So for this instance, it came out to about an 81, or what did it say?
[SPEAKER_03]: Your bearing length is about a 78, 78.5 foot structure.
And what we propose is a precast, precast NU, NU burger, which is,
[SPEAKER_03]: don't don't judge me too hard based on the plan profile to demonstrate that now pricing wise on the second page i i showed you a recent bid we had in monotone county of about the same size structure it's the 77th foot and you uh structure and i just wanted to kind of show you guys just what people are bidding on this so yeah
[SPEAKER_03]: about the same, $683,000, but the bids came in all across the board, from just under $410,000
[SPEAKER_03]: 682.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just wanted to show you guys, these things are wildly varied.
[SPEAKER_03]: It depends on if the contractor is hungry for work at the time, what their overhead is, how much they pay themselves, the profit margins.
[SPEAKER_08]: That amount was just for the construction.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, this would be just for the construction.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't believe it would be too different of a cost.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we're still, our estimate would be somewhere around $500,000 to $600,000 for construction.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I just wanted to show you there's the very real possibility that this comes under.
So with that being said, I just wanted to let you know that.
Our engineering costs
[SPEAKER_03]: It's still going to be the contract design, which is $130,000.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: So we're looking at the $130,000 plus whatever you're assuming.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, yeah, the first column is design professional, our estimate, and then after that it's in ascending order.
[SPEAKER_03]: with different bridge contractors, what they did on the project.
[SPEAKER_03]: And these items would be very similar to what we would do for your guys' project.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't see it being very different at all.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's just, I just wanted to show you, yeah, our estimate may be a little higher.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it's very rare.
Didn't you say it would be devices like from 29 to...
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm just saying, how does that, this is for us.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is an example of what bids have to come in and out.
[SPEAKER_03]: This isn't, no, I didn't bid you guys a bridge.
[SPEAKER_03]: But is it the same size?
[SPEAKER_03]: It would nearly be the same width.
[SPEAKER_03]: What we can do is we can bid our bridge.
[SPEAKER_10]: And we always have the option of rejecting all of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: You always have the option.
[SPEAKER_03]: And if that happens and we need to do value engineering, we can do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: We can switch to other less costly, but maybe not as durable design.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that is just what I wanted to definitely get this print off and show you how we came to that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because going from what 2981 is definitely, are you just planning to make a bigger structure?
[SPEAKER_03]: And I just wanted to show you how we came to that.
[SPEAKER_03]: We had a conversation with them.
[SPEAKER_03]: Luckily, we've gone through a very similar project where we don't build a bridge over the railroad just on the property.
[SPEAKER_03]: They still are a big pain.
[SPEAKER_03]: They still have... Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: But they have...
[SPEAKER_03]: They do have some minimum fees when it comes to easements.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know if you guys already have an easement on record with the railroad, with the road being on their property.
[SPEAKER_03]: Probably not because no one did and no one's going to do it.
[SPEAKER_03]: The railroad is
[SPEAKER_03]: So I don't think it'd be too hard, especially if we're keeping the road on the same alignment, just saying like, hey, we're building a new bridge.
[SPEAKER_03]: You guys do have statutory right-of-way.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're just mean about their property, and they still want you to sign these.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll go over that at that time.
[SPEAKER_10]: But they are the same people that we're going to be dealing with at the end of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Same people would be
[SPEAKER_08]: And that explains the questions we have on this.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because this is the basic services and this is what's been built.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I agree.
[SPEAKER_08]: Shall I just put our initials on this?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes please, so I can watch it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Zach is talking.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do we have anything else?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll blow over these really fast.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry about that.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, you're good.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wes, the other...
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, that's a typo, I apologize.
[SPEAKER_03]: We have the West 216th Bridge will be cleared doing some structure next to the one you're doing the box floors on.
[SPEAKER_03]: That report is due in Modoc by June 1st, and then after that we'll submit that to you guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: Lexington, Henrietta.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you guys wanted to move forward, or you guys wanted to pursue demolition.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just wanted to give you guys a few things.
[SPEAKER_03]: MoDOT technically allows for VROs.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just demoing a structure can count as a VRO.
[SPEAKER_03]: On the opposite side of that, we're going to explore it, but you guys should be able to get soft match credit just for demoing the structure.
[SPEAKER_03]: There is some language in the EPG, MoDOT may push back, but there is no reason why they shouldn't be able to, we should not be able to get you soft match credit for the demolition structure.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think we had a little bit of that discussion when we met with MoDOT down there, and they...
[SPEAKER_03]: They didn't say that?
[SPEAKER_08]: They acknowledged that that's what our thoughts were.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who said that?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I'm not going to lie.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was...
[SPEAKER_03]: But yes, I mean, I spoke at our audit this morning.
[SPEAKER_07]: We just talked about our overall claim.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: You guys should be able to get soft match for this.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then I just wanted to ask you what your guys' scope of this removal was.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we could explore just removing the beams and deck superstructure and leaving the substructure in place.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just visually observing it.
[SPEAKER_03]: The substructure doesn't appear like it's critically failing.
[SPEAKER_03]: it may be able to stand there for another 30 years because it hasn't been issued.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I think the price may be cut in half for doing something like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: But the price that was given was for the entire structure.
Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: We can talk about that later by kicking the can down the road a little bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I guess what is your guys' concern is if you are wanting the superstructure and substructure removed, which the difference is where the beams hit the concrete.
[SPEAKER_03]: because they're on rollers.
[SPEAKER_03]: So they're designed to kind of stand on their own.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they probably will stand on their own forever.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's plenty of other work to be done in the county.
[SPEAKER_03]: And there's plenty of other money.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's the thing that we can easily justify that.
[SPEAKER_03]: The money's not there to remove the substructure.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe we'll never remove the substructure in the future.
[SPEAKER_03]: But then also, with digging next to the railroad tracks, the contractor has to...
[SPEAKER_03]: The railroad doesn't care if you're digging.
[SPEAKER_03]: They want access to the track.
[SPEAKER_03]: So the contractor has to shore up next to the track and then excavate, support, and back to the excavation.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a lot.
[SPEAKER_03]: but safety aspect which we part of liability was one of the reasons why we so that liability you think by just doing the part of it that's that from what you guys tell me that's
[SPEAKER_03]: uh lastly i'm not going to go through all this with you but the last item is we are
[SPEAKER_03]: You guys, we need to discuss what is your number one and two bridges that you'd want us to go after to prepare applications for.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just letting you know, applications, we've done applications for you guys in the past.
[SPEAKER_03]: If we've already done for you one, the same bridge we're going to do again, but we don't have any new bridges.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that is April 1st that they're going to put that out.
[SPEAKER_03]: call for projects, either today or tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we need to do that.
[SPEAKER_10]: My question stands, though.
[SPEAKER_10]: How do you get bridges on and off of this list?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because there's stuff on here that I don't think should be on there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I think the Mary Lois Road was taken care of.
[SPEAKER_03]: What I see here is, and I'm sorry, I'll get this.
[SPEAKER_03]: ratings of each of these.
[SPEAKER_03]: And how you get on this list is if the deck, superstructure, substructure, or a culvert is rated in poor condition, that's a 4 or lower.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's 1 through 10, 10 is brand new, 4 is poor.
[SPEAKER_03]: So what I'm seeing here for the Mary Lewis Road, the substructure is rated a 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is from 2025.
[SPEAKER_03]: More than like, unless a bridge.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's created from the inspections by Mr. Nelson.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, it is created from those inspections.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, that's all I need to know.
[SPEAKER_03]: So if you guys want to.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we need to do that tomorrow?
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: We do not need to pick our two.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, we do not.
[SPEAKER_10]: We don't even have the list yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, once the list is released, I can send it to you guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it will be more than likely to come.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is a different topic.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's get to the question.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you for putting that on the camera.
Thanks a lot.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good work.
[SPEAKER_08]: Can you transfer Connie up here?
Good morning, Connie.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, so I am calling the follow-up on last week's bid opening for Holt College.
[SPEAKER_06]: What we'd like to do is have the commission waive the irregularity of the single bid being an hour late and allow for opening of said bid for consideration.
[SPEAKER_06]: This would just need to be somebody putting their meeting in it
[SPEAKER_06]: Travis Elliott, the attorney for Warren County, has said he thinks the wording is very low since we only had the one bidder.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you have the exact wording that we need to use?
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: The exact?
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Go ahead.
[SPEAKER_06]: So the wording is that the commission elects to waive the irregularity
and review the bid for consideration.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do I have a motion to?
[SPEAKER_08]: So moved.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do I have a second?
[SPEAKER_10]: Second.
[SPEAKER_08]: All those in favor?
[SPEAKER_08]: Aye.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, we will get that in our minutes and we did, you had talked
[SPEAKER_08]: That's the way to go.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is there anything else coming?
[SPEAKER_08]: That would be it for me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks for being here.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's pretty cute.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did you get on the new agenda for tomorrow that we were, okay, we got that, canceling the, we were going to wait until next week for the token, okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I think that is going to be all we have until we go into the closed session.
and I will go ahead.
[SPEAKER_08]: Next week we'll look at the Eagleton Agreement, the changes that we're going to have for rent there and we need to also talk about