Make sure this is pointed up there.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's pray.
[SPEAKER_01]: Dear God, we gather to begin this meeting.
[SPEAKER_01]: We ask for wisdom, understanding, and a shared commitment to work together in service of the common good.
[SPEAKER_01]: Help us to listen with open hearts, to respect one another, and to work together for the good of all the people we represent.
[SPEAKER_01]: Grant us patience in moments of disagreement, humility in leadership, and a shared commitment to what is right and just.
[SPEAKER_01]: May our efforts today reflect compassion, responsibility, and sincere desire to improve the lives of those in our county.
[SPEAKER_01]: Bless this time together and guide us in all that we do.
[SPEAKER_01]: In Jesus' name, amen.
[SPEAKER_02]: Amen.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: Do we have any comments from the public?
[SPEAKER_05]: Has everybody signed in that Cindy signed in?
[SPEAKER_05]: Nothing from anyone?
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, then I think we're going to need some time to look over the minutes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Are they here?
[SPEAKER_05]: You've got them, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll hand them first and then, Cindy, you were out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you have anything?
[SPEAKER_00]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_05]: And just to comment,
[SPEAKER_05]: work on them, the concrete work is going to be such an improvement.
[SPEAKER_05]: Big time.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's really going to be nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's coming around.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it really is.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's great extending that driveway and the concrete under the benches.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what I did.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just stopped.
[SPEAKER_05]: They said, you know those benches were kind of on top of a mud hole.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it is, they wish it would quit raining so they could get it done.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it will be really nice to be able to walk by the band when they're bringing.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're just making it wide enough that people can walk.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a great improvement.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: So anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: Baby steps.
[SPEAKER_05]: And we are recording.
[SPEAKER_02]: Brian Max Hockmeyer.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I told you I looked for locks, and I did, and I didn't find anything suitable, so why don't you just go ahead and do that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Right.
[SPEAKER_02]: and we're narrowing it down so you might be able to.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just wanted, that was as easy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, I haven't got that far.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just looked at, and did you, I didn't look any further.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you find exhibit C?
[SPEAKER_05]: With this?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that was one of my.
[SPEAKER_02]: With the opioid contract.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: It said C, exhibit C, and we couldn't find that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, that's on the other forms.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: All the forms that they filled out, that's attached to that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, and I think he typed that up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: We thought that was the case, but we weren't sure.
[SPEAKER_05]: Great, I have just a couple, just a couple little changes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Child abuse awareness.
[SPEAKER_04]: So the light's going to be on the courthouse the rest of the month.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was wondering, would you guys want to do like a proclamation, like awareness or awareness, and then maybe we could promote a Everybody Wear Blue Day?
[SPEAKER_04]: I did see a shelter here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Blue stuff on the hillside.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think we should do something.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that is an easy do.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, it's an easy ask, and it's making a statement.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's awareness.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a lot of times that people don't realize why.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll probably find somebody to put it in the paper.
[SPEAKER_02]: If we ask nicely.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that would be so good.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you could kind of lead us in what you think may be a proclamation for us to do maybe next week, or it's the whole month.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, but I was kind of thinking maybe on Friday the 24th, they get a blue day, everybody wear blue.
[SPEAKER_04]: But we won't be here, but that's okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: We can do a whole week, any time during the week we're blue.
[SPEAKER_05]: We will be Wednesday on the 22nd.
[SPEAKER_07]: I won't.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was thinking about contacting the schools and just seeing if they could get the kids to dress in blue and I would give like the biggest class an ice cream party or I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm trying, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or get a picture of who is a safe person or I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just think we should do something with it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is there...
[SPEAKER_05]: i think the answer to that is but i think we're interested in doing something if the county needs it i think it'll be a whole lot more than we just call out and asking yes and i think we are supportive of that so tell us what you would like to do for us you can tell them we're we're interested in doing something we'd like the school to participate
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know where they got them, but they had a whole bunch of blue whirligigs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I saw them on Amazon.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can get like 200 for like 30 bucks or 40 bucks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, they got your attention.
[SPEAKER_04]: So were they at the...
[SPEAKER_02]: They were stuck all over town.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it was at the... Joplin?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I did order some stickers, something about child abuse.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, people come in and give them stickers.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I ordered a banner.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't know... You know, people could like sign it.
[SPEAKER_04]: to come up with i know it's kind of like nose but i work less under pressure i guess do we want a motion that we're going to think so until we sign the law okay but we will leave that either but maybe we can get like some of the um community people like the sheriff's department or the yeah and the dare the you know the police department's sheriff department but i thought also about maybe
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, doing like a free lunch.
[SPEAKER_04]: Me and Mike can put some hot dogs and pack them out.
[SPEAKER_04]: People can come and hear the proclamation, get some balloons, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: But we will, if we want to do it tomorrow, so it can be in the paper for next week.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was just about to say, we need to take care of that proclamation tomorrow and get it on the agenda.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: because next week is it.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you can do it that quick.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can do it that quick.
[SPEAKER_05]: Would you put on the agenda for tomorrow that we will maybe recognize April as Child Abuse Awareness Month.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the county's support for that.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then you tell us what we need to do.
[SPEAKER_05]: We are only going to be here on Wednesday next week because we're going to Jefferson City on Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe we wear blue on Wednesday.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you'll be getting your eyes done, so don't add a lot of color because you won't be able to see.
[SPEAKER_04]: It would be great if we could get everybody to go and dress in blue and maybe go outside and take a picture or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: So let's do Wednesday as blue day.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: We can do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for bringing that to us.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you know, when we're signing this, I would like to just make a statement on behalf of the commission.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just a statement.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not a discussion point.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not anything that was on the agenda.
[SPEAKER_05]: But just we've had some discussions about recording and things that are tied to that.
[SPEAKER_05]: And first of all,
[SPEAKER_05]: This commission is certainly in support and compliant with the reporting issues.
[SPEAKER_05]: And we have been and continue to do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Miranda, we appreciate you're almost in that seat every meeting that we have so people in the community can follow that.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we've had some discussions about the video videoing and we've made some changes and thank everyone for complying with that.
[SPEAKER_05]: But we do need for everyone to know that any conversation that is being done in this courtroom, before meetings, after meetings, that
[SPEAKER_05]: is and can be recorded and done with whatever someone decides to do and you know it is legal i think sometimes there's pieces to that that's unfortunate because sometimes people are coming in because this is a small community and people are very caring and
[SPEAKER_05]: How's your daughter?
[SPEAKER_05]: How's your granddaughter?
[SPEAKER_05]: How they're doing?
[SPEAKER_05]: Or they had something going on.
[SPEAKER_05]: We think that's unfortunate if that is what is being reported.
[SPEAKER_05]: But we understand that if that's what people can do, they can do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: But we want the people sitting in this courtroom to know, if you're having a discussion with your neighbor,
[SPEAKER_05]: it could be seen on Facebook.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that is a statement from us and just so people know.
[SPEAKER_00]: Is that going to be listed in the paper?
[SPEAKER_05]: What do you mean?
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, just so that people know in the future if they come that they'll...
[SPEAKER_06]: I would say it will be.
[SPEAKER_06]: We have a reporter right here taking notes and recording us.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: She did a pretty good job.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, yes, yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: And if you need to do that at 10 o'clock before, I'm going to make that after.
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'm going to revise that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, don't do that because we're waiting on him.
[SPEAKER_05]: He has when he comes back.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll do that after he comes back.
[SPEAKER_02]: I might ask Heather.
[SPEAKER_02]: They assign it.
[SPEAKER_02]: She works for the head of the office.
[SPEAKER_02]: The head of the office.
[SPEAKER_02]: The free people sign it.
Everything is monthly.
Everything is quarterly except the general meeting.
Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: So we might need to do something different.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm just going to send it.
I'm confused.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm confused.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you were right on that.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the gas situation, of course, it's more likely to be surrounding the cars and things.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, when you think about how much we use.
[SPEAKER_05]: While we're doing this, we'd like to thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did we contract in?
I feel like it's new, but maybe not.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll check on that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I did talk to him.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will
[SPEAKER_07]: I think you could.
So I know that you have a tractor supply, and I know that you do that at work.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe we should give him one of those, and when his work is done, he comes back here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, we can hand him a copy of it and keep it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it's a lot.
[SPEAKER_02]: Per purchase.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Usually, I just copy it myself.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, we have reviewed the minutes.
[SPEAKER_02]: I make a motion to approve the minutes.
[SPEAKER_06]: I second.
[SPEAKER_06]: All those in favor?
[SPEAKER_07]: Aye.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's the only thing I had for you guys today.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wow, that was pretty easy, huh?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, listen, do you want me to?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, yes, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, no, you're good.
[SPEAKER_07]: um this is for the school this is for them i don't know what things cost when you get into this realm
[SPEAKER_05]: Marie, is our printer a contract printer?
[SPEAKER_05]: Or is it our printer?
[SPEAKER_02]: It is our printer.
[SPEAKER_02]: We own that.
[SPEAKER_02]: This one and here's our printer.
[SPEAKER_07]: So the last two questions.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Homestead's going to be here.
[SPEAKER_05]: They should be here in just a couple minutes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Someone better get donuts.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, that's right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_02]: Do we have any day-old donuts?
[SPEAKER_02]: Walmart.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hard to say.
[SPEAKER_02]: I noticed we took them all in there yesterday.
[SPEAKER_06]: They sure do look good.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you going to get one?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't understand what you're just looking at.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, good morning.
[SPEAKER_03]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_03]: Connie Walden.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi, Connie.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll grab Heather and...
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll go grab Heather.
[SPEAKER_02]: You sit there.
[SPEAKER_01]: Connie, you can come up here if you want.
[SPEAKER_01]: How are you today, Connie?
[SPEAKER_01]: Good.
[SPEAKER_04]: A little rainy Wednesday.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, overcast.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hi, how are you?
[SPEAKER_01]: Hi, good.
[SPEAKER_01]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_01]: Good.
[SPEAKER_02]: I set three aside to talk about before we do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: He said not quite.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that was kind of not good.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Morning, Connie.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm Max.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good morning, Max.
[SPEAKER_03]: How are you today?
[SPEAKER_03]: Good to see you.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've heard your name a million times.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm usually on the screen and my face isn't showing when I'm talking through the screen.
[SPEAKER_02]: I kind of like it that way.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good morning.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: This...
[SPEAKER_07]: That's something we probably need to wrap up on.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, you're all right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because she's the only one that hasn't come through.
[SPEAKER_07]: Everyone else has to.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, and that should come through here.
[SPEAKER_07]: And yes, that is...
[SPEAKER_02]: Who is CR?
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, so I'm going to keep this and you'll figure out contact on that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I put that in.
[SPEAKER_07]: We should be.
[SPEAKER_02]: We should be.
[SPEAKER_05]: We should be through now, I believe.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think we're ready for, we're going to have, we have some bids.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_03]: Has anybody brought in any bids?
[SPEAKER_03]: Shouldn't give me any bids.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hope we should.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, we should have.
[SPEAKER_03]: There was one from Mega KC they told me they were submitting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Another Dodge constructionist turned in all their documents, but I don't know if they were actually doing it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Have you worked with both of them before?
[SPEAKER_03]: I worked with Mega KC before.
[SPEAKER_03]: We didn't get to play.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think so, but.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, you don't have any bits open?
[SPEAKER_03]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_03]: None.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, that makes my job easy.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have nothing to do.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's not good news, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maggie Casey did say they were submitting.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I guess I would go out and give them a call and see if perhaps they submitted to Homestead Village on accident.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: And maybe reach out to the other one, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: Reach out to the other one, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: And if they were
[SPEAKER_03]: So, yeah, we really don't have time to go out for bid again.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll check with legal and see if we can just extend the bids again for another two weeks, make some phone calls, and see what happens.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I know Megan Casey has been very interested.
[SPEAKER_03]: They submitted last time.
[SPEAKER_03]: I find that very strange that they did not submit this time.
[SPEAKER_05]: So most likely I'll just extend it.
[SPEAKER_05]: let us know and then we'll put on the agenda in two weeks or whenever your deadline is.
[SPEAKER_05]: And be sure that they know where it's supposed to come to.
[SPEAKER_05]: If it's supposed to come here, maybe it went somewhere else.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, thanks for coming on.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: We haven't done that.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, that's okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Since I am here, though, I don't have the Forbis meeting on my calendar for this month.
[SPEAKER_03]: Has Cecilia sent out an invite for that?
[SPEAKER_01]: For what?
[SPEAKER_03]: For the Forbis meeting this month?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think she has sent that out yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, well, I'll go make some phone calls, and I'll keep you all in the loop.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, Tommy, the next meeting's not till May 13th.
[SPEAKER_03]: May 13th.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, not this month.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: She doesn't do it every month.
[SPEAKER_04]: They do it every other few months.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you're good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I'll make sure to email out a plan because last time we spoke she wanted a schedule.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I'll make sure to email out the updated schedule prior to that May meeting because I think it's better to have it laid out before another month goes by.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you all.
[SPEAKER_03]: Have a good afternoon.
[SPEAKER_01]: You too.
[SPEAKER_01]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_01]: Have a great morning.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, ma'am.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you so much.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_07]: That is so difficult to get bids.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bids, I know.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's the hardest thing.
[SPEAKER_00]: What is the Homestead Project?
[SPEAKER_00]: Is that the water thing?
[SPEAKER_00]: Homestead is water, correct?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_00]: And where is Homestead?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's on the west side of the county up that way as you head to the lawsuits.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess it's kind of lying on the left.
[SPEAKER_02]: Very small, very small room.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's located outside of a healthier spring.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, do you have a map there?
[SPEAKER_00]: It's right there.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, I thought you had it on your computer.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, I do, yeah.
Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_07]: I see you gained about five pounds because you
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you have to train in order to do that job.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have to have that qualification to get that job.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just like, it's the same training.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm just wondering if since we've kind of changed leadership there, if they've gone through it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: But they can do it online.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, yeah, okay.
Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that's just one of those things we can tell you about.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_02]: Those aren't the donuts I brought yesterday.
[SPEAKER_02]: Where'd these come from?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, on Monday.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Probably Monday.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cindy brought those.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cindy brought them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I don't need donuts either.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't need any one.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have gotten hooked on their little sandwiches over there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, at the donut shop over there?
[SPEAKER_05]: There.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like they have...
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like a Polish sausage or something inside the pastry.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is my favorite lunch.
[SPEAKER_05]: That sounds good.
[SPEAKER_05]: They have spicy and not spicy, it's very good.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, well I think we have gone through what we have to go through.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is there anything else that we need to address?
[SPEAKER_05]: Next week, we are going to be in Jefferson City on Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then on Wednesday, we will have session.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thursday, we will not.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to make sure I'll post that all on Friday.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do we want to stay open or do we want to?
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.