[SPEAKER_06]: I think it is time to hear a motion.
All in favor?
[SPEAKER_01]: I. I pledge allegiance to the flag of the United States of America and to the republic for which it stands, one nation, under God, indivisible, with liberty and justice for all.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's pray.
[SPEAKER_01]: Father God, thank you for the beautiful day outside and the changing weather.
[SPEAKER_01]: We pray that you would continue to guide and direct us
[SPEAKER_01]: in our walk daily, that we would honor and glorify you, one another, and encourage one another.
[SPEAKER_01]: We pray for our county, especially, that you would continue to grow and bless it.
[SPEAKER_01]: We pray that you would, Lord, just give wisdom to those making decisions on behalf of our county.
[SPEAKER_01]: We pray for all of our elected officials and workers that you would watch over them, keep them safe and healthy, and bless their families as well.
[SPEAKER_01]: Lord, we just look forward to the days ahead and all you have in store for us.
[SPEAKER_01]: May we honor you in all that we do.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's in Jesus' name we pray.
[SPEAKER_01]: Amen.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: And welcome everybody.
[SPEAKER_06]: Everybody's signed in and we are being recorded.
[SPEAKER_06]: And do we have any comments from the public?
[SPEAKER_11]: Kirk Croy, last week you guys tabled the discussion on the sunshine charges.
[SPEAKER_11]: Are you going to be talking about that today?
[SPEAKER_19]: The sunshine requests?
[SPEAKER_19]: The process.
[SPEAKER_19]: The process change.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't have it finished.
[SPEAKER_19]: We may discuss it a little bit, but I don't have it finished yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, I think there were some.
[SPEAKER_06]: need to discuss on how to do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: There are some things that we've grasped that we need to change for sure.
[SPEAKER_19]: But... We want to be sure we're following the statutes and that it's going to work for the county and the people.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: And then last week, one of you two said you would send me the budget and I'm still looking out for that.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't know that we said we would send it.
[SPEAKER_19]: We would look into that.
[SPEAKER_19]: If you want to bring us a
[SPEAKER_19]: Fresh thumb drive in a package, so we know we can plug it into our equipment.
[SPEAKER_19]: We'll be glad to load it in.
[SPEAKER_13]: Can't email it?
[SPEAKER_19]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_19]: No.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's a huge file, and we're not that good at it yet.
[SPEAKER_19]: We're working on all of that stuff.
[SPEAKER_19]: Isn't it 10 pages?
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm sorry?
[SPEAKER_11]: It's 10 pages, though.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's 327 pages.
[SPEAKER_11]: The document that I was asking for.
[SPEAKER_19]: The document that you're asking for would be mailed out.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's the one I want.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_19]: You want a 10-page document?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_19]: We'll get that done.
[SPEAKER_19]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_15]: Anybody else?
[SPEAKER_15]: I have some questions.
[SPEAKER_15]: Good morning.
[SPEAKER_15]: One of them is the bridge that's shut down on 216 and that bright lane in the road that connects to 216.
[SPEAKER_15]: That culvert is a problem.
[SPEAKER_15]: That road is washing out.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I understand that the commissioners went and said that we were going to fix that.
[SPEAKER_15]: And just wondering if we know what the fix is and when.
[SPEAKER_19]: Tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's going to be fixed tomorrow?
[SPEAKER_15]: What's happening?
[SPEAKER_19]: They're putting a new tube in.
[SPEAKER_15]: They are?
[SPEAKER_15]: And extending it out and everything?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: And then another thing is, do we have and where would we find any documentation concerning
[SPEAKER_15]: the bridge, when it was put in, what the agreement was with the railroad.
[SPEAKER_15]: Because I reached out to the railroad and they said that the bridge is theirs and there was never any agreement for them to maintain it or replace it.
[SPEAKER_15]: And so since it's their property, they don't have to rebuild it.
[SPEAKER_15]: But when we were here last week with the news station here, I heard someone on the commission say it's a Ray County bridge.
[SPEAKER_15]: So do we have any records?
[SPEAKER_19]: Can I ask who you contacted at the railroad?
[SPEAKER_15]: Ben Jones.
[SPEAKER_19]: Ben Jones and his position at the railroad?
[SPEAKER_15]: He is in...
[SPEAKER_15]: He's like a community person.
[SPEAKER_15]: Senior Director of Public Affairs.
[SPEAKER_06]: Legislative, he does.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've known Ben for a long time.
[SPEAKER_06]: We...
[SPEAKER_06]: We were in limbo of those two things, who owns it, and MoDoc found the document and said, it is our brief.
[SPEAKER_06]: That is what we were told.
[SPEAKER_06]: We didn't get a copy of that or anything?
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that this is something that is in the process of being a legal issue.
[SPEAKER_06]: In fact, I talked with Alex yesterday with MoDoc.
[SPEAKER_06]: And he said he was going to kind of carry the water on this and work with the railroad and see where we can be.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just hate for us to have a whole bunch of things going to him versus, you know, kind of a point person, I guess is what I'm saying.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: And then what was the other thing?
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, as far as Tim Rash and the wedding venue.
[SPEAKER_15]: I understand we sent out a cease and desist, and that was over a year ago, and he's still having weddings.
[SPEAKER_15]: So I was curious, did we ever send a probable cause statement?
[SPEAKER_15]: If there was a restaurant and it didn't have inspections and permits, we would go and shut that down.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't understand.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm sorry, but we're in a legal issue here.
[SPEAKER_15]: So let's just talk about generalities in terms of our process.
[SPEAKER_15]: If somebody's running a business when they shouldn't be, and we send a cease and desist,
[SPEAKER_15]: What is our next leg in that process?
[SPEAKER_15]: Do we allow businesses to continue in violation of our ordinances and laws without any repercussion?
[SPEAKER_15]: Or are there steps that we take to stop that from happening?
[SPEAKER_19]: As a commission, we turn it over to the legal department.
[SPEAKER_15]: So did a probable cause statement get sent to our prosecuting attorney?
[SPEAKER_15]: So we have to send something to them, and she's probably going to have to recuse herself.
[SPEAKER_15]: Has that been done?
[SPEAKER_19]: There are two attorneys.
[SPEAKER_19]: There is Presbyterian Attorney Bill Dobson, and then there is Travis Elliott in Springfield, who is probably handling that.
[SPEAKER_15]: Would we normally need an outside attorney to...
[SPEAKER_19]: It's not an outside attorney.
[SPEAKER_19]: He's contracted with many counties in the state, including Rain County, because he does different things than a prosecuting attorney does.
[SPEAKER_19]: He has vast knowledge on county law.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm just shocked that some business could be operating illegally in our county and continue to do so without any consequences for over a year.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't know why we haven't gone and
[SPEAKER_15]: boarded it up, locked and chained it, put a note, respond to the calls that the county's making that they're having events out there when they're not supposed to be.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm very curious why this is still continuing without those steps being taken or what our process is.
[SPEAKER_15]: Do we have a formal process about this?
[SPEAKER_15]: If somebody put up a strip club in their backyard and noise is going and partying is going and they're serving alcohol
[SPEAKER_15]: I mean, what I'm seeing from Tim Rash is that the county's not going to do anything about it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Law enforcement's not.
[SPEAKER_15]: Commissioners are not.
[SPEAKER_06]: Brianna, I'm not really sure where all of us were when the cease and desist.
[SPEAKER_06]: You said a year ago.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know if that was something we...
[SPEAKER_06]: It doesn't matter if you did it or not.
[SPEAKER_06]: This office did.
[SPEAKER_06]: Our county did.
[SPEAKER_19]: We're not allowed to discuss something that was important.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that's why we have just stayed away from that totally because it's in litigation.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that's all I can tell you.
[SPEAKER_15]: So can we request as citizens that the attorney be asked about an injunction and some enforcement on our laws while this is going on?
[SPEAKER_15]: Because I find it disappointing that the attorney that we're employing has taken all this time and he's still operating with no consequence.
[SPEAKER_15]: He is harassing this county.
[SPEAKER_15]: He's harassing the people in this county.
[SPEAKER_15]: And it's disgusting that we're not doing anything about it all this time.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I'd be curious how many hours are spent billed to this Travis and this is still going on.
[SPEAKER_15]: There should be an injunction.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm not in the lawyer, but I know there are things they can do.
[SPEAKER_15]: Why aren't they being done?
[SPEAKER_15]: What is our process?
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, we have planning and zoning and we use their expertise in what we can do best.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because we're a smaller county, you know, different classes of counties have a lot more resources to do things.
[SPEAKER_06]: Our planning and zoning, it kind of takes us to a certain point, but maybe not beyond that.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I cannot tell you the answer to that.
[SPEAKER_15]: So you don't know what our process is.
[SPEAKER_15]: You don't know why we're not enforcing.
[SPEAKER_15]: You're asking me to go back down to planning and zoning and have them enforce our laws?
[SPEAKER_06]: I am not sure.
[SPEAKER_06]: We've been told that we are not supposed to talk about the case because it is in litigation.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, so don't talk about the case.
[SPEAKER_15]: Talk about in general.
[SPEAKER_15]: If I find out I've got my neighbors running a strip club out of their barn.
[SPEAKER_06]: Then you would probably come to Planning and Zoning to see if they have the proper codes.
[SPEAKER_19]: We largely operate under state statutes.
[SPEAKER_19]: We have little to no power legally at the commission.
[SPEAKER_19]: other than on county property?
[SPEAKER_15]: So this is county property that we're talking about.
[SPEAKER_19]: And the county has been notified.
[SPEAKER_19]: County owned property like the courthouse and the Eagleton Center.
[SPEAKER_06]: But not the wedding venue.
[SPEAKER_06]: We don't have, you know, that's what he's saying.
[SPEAKER_15]: So we're referring this back to state statutes.
[SPEAKER_15]: So the county has a planning and zoning board.
[SPEAKER_15]: Ordinances have been put in place.
[SPEAKER_15]: Those are in violation.
[SPEAKER_15]: We sent a cease and desist saying you cannot operate this business.
[SPEAKER_15]: You are in violation.
[SPEAKER_15]: You don't have a permit.
[SPEAKER_15]: You have raw sewage pouring out of your place.
[SPEAKER_15]: Your septic failed.
[SPEAKER_15]: And we're going to notice on that, but then we're not going to do anything about it.
[SPEAKER_19]: I understand the frustration, but again, we can only go back to what we've been told, which is it's an orientation, and we're not allowed to go there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do you have the case number or any information about that case?
[SPEAKER_15]: I have the case number.
[SPEAKER_15]: He's suing saying his civil rights are violated because he didn't get a permit.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think we should discuss that in the following session.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you want to pass that along.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm talking about general...
[SPEAKER_06]: I saw a notice on the news, I think, about be careful with case net things right now, that there's a scam there.
[SPEAKER_06]: It looks like you're going to case net something and it's really a virus.
[SPEAKER_06]: So be careful if anybody's doing that or looking things up.
[SPEAKER_06]: So is there anything else?
[SPEAKER_15]: Not even general understandings of our processes in this county can be found at Planning and Zoning or the Commissioner is what I'm hearing.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I've asked about this since back in December.
[SPEAKER_15]: And you said you're going to talk to your council and get back with me.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I don't see a thing moving and happening.
[SPEAKER_15]: And he's still out here.
[SPEAKER_15]: running his wedding.
[SPEAKER_15]: So it sounds like anybody can do whatever in the hell they want to do because the county doesn't know who actually can do anything about it.
[SPEAKER_15]: That seems outrageous.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: Are citizens allowed to talk to this attorney?
[SPEAKER_15]: No.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, if it was our prosecuting attorney, we should be able to because we employ them.
[SPEAKER_15]: So if we've got somebody who we're using that's not our prosecuting attorney and we're not bouncing it to another prosecuting attorney, that's a conflict of interest.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not sure.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: We certainly aren't legal experts.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I can't imagine attorneys...
[SPEAKER_06]: opening themselves up to accountability.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm not suggesting that they spend hours and hours fielding questions from the community, but if I bring them here and they're not getting asked and answered, then... Why don't you send us an email with your specific questions?
[SPEAKER_15]: I will do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And we will forward that to Travis.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Specific.
[SPEAKER_06]: Specific what you want to know.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_15]: If you would do that.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_15]: What email should I send that to?
[SPEAKER_06]: Send it to Wright County Commission.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's so long.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll look it up.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have to look this up.
[SPEAKER_09]: It is so long.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is.
[SPEAKER_09]: It has like every letter in the book.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wright County Commissioners.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_06]: At commission.wrightcountymotor.gov.
[SPEAKER_15]: Do you have a card with the email address for the county commissioner?
[SPEAKER_15]: I do.
[SPEAKER_15]: Here's one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Make sure I didn't write on the back of it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sometimes I...
[SPEAKER_12]: saying his civil rights were violated, but I don't see a case where the county is suing him for being in violation.
It's going to ring around the rosies.
Are you done?
No, I'm so sorry.
He has some.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do I hear a motion to approve the minutes?
[SPEAKER_21]: All those in favor?
[SPEAKER_06]: Aye.
[SPEAKER_06]: And we'll sign them when you get them ready for us.
Oh, yeah.
We'll see.
I think I knew that.
Okay, so we're going to sign those.
And then I think we'll be ready for the diesel fuel.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's legal shenanigans.
[SPEAKER_06]: Was Tom and Amy going to come up and just let us know about, I mean, it's already in the budget, but they were just going to, we have to sign something.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's already in there.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's already approved in the budget.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's already approved.
Thank you.
[SPEAKER_12]: She gave it to me one day, and then I gave it yesterday.
[SPEAKER_07]: He'd done another comedy for me.
[SPEAKER_19]: ... ... ... ...
[SPEAKER_06]: I believe many of the judges suggested these people.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, take it in there so she can get the sign.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, that was so easy.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, perfect.
[SPEAKER_06]: While we have a little bit of time, and she's going to bring us the diesel thing, do you want to make any comments about this would be end of other business?
[SPEAKER_06]: We don't have any action to take, but where the org situation is on the battery.
[SPEAKER_19]: The city of Orich had a meeting Monday night, and there's a city council meeting with the public.
[SPEAKER_19]: It was standing room only, and they were discussing a possible annexation of the land adjacent to the city board for the battery operation systems.
[SPEAKER_19]: I thought it was a good meeting.
[SPEAKER_19]: They had three or four local people get up and give their opinion and speak.
[SPEAKER_19]: Then the council voted to entertain the idea of annexing these properties.
[SPEAKER_19]: and then the attorney informed the people in the meeting that they would have 14 days to petition the city council in opposition to annexation, and that if they would get 5% of the registered voters of the city of Warwick to sign the petitions, then that would go to the vote of the people, which all seemed like good, reasonable moves on a process and moves on their part, and I think the people were happy with that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Miranda, I hate to ask you a question that I didn't even tell you beforehand.
[SPEAKER_06]: Has Excelsior Springs, have they addressed this?
[SPEAKER_06]: The annex in Excelsior with Eidecker and all that, is that what you're talking about?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, this is the reason that I'm asking this.
[SPEAKER_06]: I received...
[SPEAKER_06]: a text that asked what we were doing on that project because they said it is a concern to us.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I wasn't sure who it was.
[SPEAKER_06]: It wasn't anyone I had on my phone.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I just said, you know, who is requesting this information?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, it was, I believe, the city manager.
[SPEAKER_06]: I worked with her before, and I obviously didn't have her on the phone.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just wondered if there had been a lot of discussion or any discussion if they were not supportive, supportive, what their position was.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mosby and Excelsior are currently in court over the annexation, so they're still waiting on a ruling for who gets it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Both Mosby and Excelsior approved it on their ballot, so now it's in the court's hands on who gets to.
[SPEAKER_06]: In the org, I'm talking about on the org,
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought you were talking about the other annex.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I'm saying that I felt like her message was if there was a fire, it certainly would affect them.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I just wondered if you have had any.
[SPEAKER_06]: I haven't.
[SPEAKER_06]: No one's talked about any meetings or anything.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: And maybe she's new, and I just got that yesterday.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry, I completely misunderstood what you were talking about.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anything else on that?
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you have the fuel?
[SPEAKER_07]: Reports for us?
[SPEAKER_20]: back to the battery thing do we need to do any more
[SPEAKER_18]: We're going to hold off on that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know we have sent a couple letters to Oregon.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do we need to do anything further to follow up for it?
[SPEAKER_06]: They know where we are.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yes, we've got that under control.
[SPEAKER_06]: And now for invoice number nine on the Myers Bridge.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, ma'am.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we will get reimbursement from MoDOT for $10,000, and then we will be apportioned back to Great River.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to have Great River's invoice in the back as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just one statement.
[SPEAKER_06]: to be here.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I think that was he.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think I remember it was just you guys were going to go over to him.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you guys want to.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just one signature.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yep, just one signature.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think we can table it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do I have a mistake?
Thank you.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, yeah.
And then we have additional work to do.
[SPEAKER_19]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Jeff is not going to be here from policy.
[SPEAKER_06]: So he came two weeks ago and gave us a proposal.
[SPEAKER_06]: We looked through it and it's time that we have to do something because our policy renews April 1st and that's around the corner.
[SPEAKER_06]: So do I have a motion to
[SPEAKER_06]: for us to approve this, and I sign it, send it back, and then they'll figure out.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'll make a motion to approve the Hollis and Akers bid for, what is it, liability?
[SPEAKER_19]: Liability and property.
[SPEAKER_06]: Property, liability.
[SPEAKER_21]: I second it.
[SPEAKER_06]: All those in favor?
[SPEAKER_06]: Aye.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, I will sign this, and it just takes one of us to sign this one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nineteen.
[SPEAKER_18]: Goodness.
[SPEAKER_06]: Somehow.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's twenty-six, not twenty-five.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, I'm going to go get this back for her because there's some other things that she has to do with this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you need something out of that packet?
[SPEAKER_14]: No, I just lost my ginger.
[SPEAKER_19]: That was what they went
We don't get to step in court.
Just to be sure.
[SPEAKER_06]: Marie, this letter, this was just a copy, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: It was on the battery.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, that was your copy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, ma'am.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think to cross some things off our list, we need to look forward to the tow process.
[SPEAKER_06]: So what I was thinking is if we could do in two weeks, if we could do tow, and then in maybe two weeks from there, what are we talking about?
[SPEAKER_06]: if we don't do it we're just going to keep it the same i will not
[SPEAKER_20]: We got adjusted in the 24th
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: We will.
[SPEAKER_06]: So let's just have our just sitting and that will be an official meeting because we will be all down together.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then do that Wednesday.
[SPEAKER_06]: You won't be here and I think that will be sufficient for that.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we don't want to do any of those big
[SPEAKER_06]: Ones that could take some time.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I would like to... To the end of April.
[SPEAKER_17]: What about the other one?
[SPEAKER_06]: I think I'm going to have some time to kind of figure out.
[SPEAKER_02]: I almost forgot.
[SPEAKER_02]: See, you have to remind me.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll try, but I also got the pregnancy brain, so...
[SPEAKER_10]: This isn't your first kid, is it?
[SPEAKER_10]: It is.
[SPEAKER_09]: My husband and I struggled for three and a half years doing fertility treatments and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then on our very last one, we were blessed.
[SPEAKER_09]: So we're just thankful and scared, but thankful.
[SPEAKER_15]: When are you due?
[SPEAKER_09]: September 10th.
[SPEAKER_09]: So it'll be perfect timing to get everything done.
[SPEAKER_15]: You're going to go through summer, girl.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know.
[SPEAKER_09]: And my mom just got rid of her pool, too.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was like, gosh dang it.
[SPEAKER_09]: So my husband was like, yeah, I'll get you a miniature pool in the backyard.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was like, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is more insurance.
[SPEAKER_11]: My wife's garden got so neglected when she was pregnant last summer.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was like, why did you even plant this?
[SPEAKER_04]: I've already started wearing dresses.
[SPEAKER_09]: Forget shoes.
[SPEAKER_12]: You can't expect me to come in here and shove these things in a field.
[SPEAKER_12]: Right.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's why you're probably wrapping them up with tape and trying to get them in there.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'll slip them on when a customer comes in and I'll take them to the meet.
[SPEAKER_12]: Other than that, I'll put them on the same way the rest of it is and I don't know.
[SPEAKER_19]: I am fine with whatever makes it safe.
[SPEAKER_19]: I just don't want us to have...
[SPEAKER_19]: I just want to be sure that it's... We'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: It just has to be safe.
[SPEAKER_19]: If we're going to do handrails for the courthouse, maybe we can include that.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_18]: Is that a word?
[SPEAKER_20]: No.
[SPEAKER_20]: And who does that?
[SPEAKER_20]: Well, we've been talking about it.
[SPEAKER_19]: And we have to clarify that when it came into being painted on the sidewalk, what it is we're actually doing with the magnets.
[SPEAKER_19]: Although we've discussed it, I don't know that we've had a definitive answer.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now see, I have not been out there to see it, but in my mind it was almost like a little deck, like a little porch.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it was the railing around that is what I thought and said they were great.
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, there's a landing and then there's a few steps down.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's six, eight feet off the ground
[SPEAKER_19]: Hi Wilbur.
[SPEAKER_19]: There he is.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, we all thought so.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's just for the rest of the insurance.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, it was just that.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: We haven't seen you for a while.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've been in Harvard Nation.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just hiding.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't blame you.
[SPEAKER_03]: It doesn't work as good as I want it to.
[SPEAKER_06]: What you got?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I guess I'm here to buy cameras.
[SPEAKER_19]: We had talked to him.
[SPEAKER_19]: I had talked to him recently about it.
[SPEAKER_19]: This bid that came in for cameras, and in it, it says that the conduct will be done by the county.
[SPEAKER_19]: And the internet connection will be provided by the county.
[SPEAKER_19]: So my question then is, what are we looking at?
[SPEAKER_19]: What's the cost involved with the money?
[SPEAKER_06]: So we have a bid.
[SPEAKER_19]: You have a copy of this?
[SPEAKER_19]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we have the bid for the cameras themselves and the installation.
[SPEAKER_06]: But then the other part of that is kind of like clocks.
[SPEAKER_06]: You would need to do the conduit and all of that.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then the other part of that is we haven't received any update on
[SPEAKER_06]: on what the partnership would be.
[SPEAKER_06]: Correct.
[SPEAKER_06]: And so while we have, while we're getting information, we still don't have anything that we can move forward with because we haven't.
[SPEAKER_19]: We need to know what the total package looks like.
[SPEAKER_19]: And on that, I gave a copy of that to Jeff Crowley to look at and
[SPEAKER_19]: Since we have to provide the Internet hookups also.
[SPEAKER_06]: What do you think that will be?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, the Internet hookup will be, it's got to be from the third floor computer room and then down to the desk.
[SPEAKER_19]: Now, I assume it will run through the same conduit.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_19]: No, no.
[SPEAKER_19]: Because they interfere with each other.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, okay.
[SPEAKER_19]: Is that right?
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't do the hardware stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think they interfere with each other.
[SPEAKER_06]: Most everything I do interferes with each other.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I think the cameras are even that cab five wire.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's basically the computer wire as the internet wire is the same thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: But what I need to get with is a victory that's going to furnish all the stuff, install and maintenance it, the cameras and
[SPEAKER_03]: That's the preferred bed right there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Victory technology.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, yeah, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I know that the desk downstairs, that's going to move over to the west entrance.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're discussing what's going to happen with it.
[SPEAKER_19]: We haven't
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_19]: We haven't solidified that yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then I got to know, I know where the cameras are going to go in the lobbies, but as of they're wanting four external cameras on each corner outside, and I got to know which way so I can...
[SPEAKER_03]: Officer Franklin should know all of that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: But as of for what I got a guesstimate at,
[SPEAKER_03]: If it took me two weekends to do this conduit, and whenever I turned in my proposal for all the other work I've been doing, and that all stands the same, but as of Saturday hours at time and a half, and Sunday hours at double time, for four days of that, two days at double time, or time and a half and two days at,
[SPEAKER_03]: Double time, that's $8,400.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'm guesstimating a material cost in the neighborhood of $1,000 just for conduit.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's $10,000.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: But that is if I can do it in those four days.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it has to be done on the weekend because everybody's using everything.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, well, just like right now, you don't want to hear a hammer drill going through that wall, these external walls, and
[SPEAKER_03]: and me moving ladders around people and working overhead.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I guess when I saw the bid, I think it was, what, $45,000 or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was pleasantly surprised.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought it would be more than that for what we were doing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is that just for their material?
[SPEAKER_03]: Is that cameras and monitors?
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's going to be $55,000 or $60,000, but we want to include that in the conversation with people
[SPEAKER_06]: the judges to see what part of that is.
[SPEAKER_03]: But to be safe with me, I'd say $15,000.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you know how I work.
[SPEAKER_03]: I keep my hours and I keep all the receipts.
[SPEAKER_03]: And there's no markup on what I buy.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'll tack on an hour to go get it or whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: I did have a question because when this had come up before there was kind of some concern on the backup and a third party monitoring and he said that would be a subscription and even law enforcement agreed that would be a good idea so
[SPEAKER_15]: Have we gotten pricing on that also?
[SPEAKER_19]: We're still in process.
[SPEAKER_19]: We feel we need to talk to the judge for the next step.
[SPEAKER_19]: Is that an integral part of this?
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, because if there is a subscription charge, would the judge also be on the hook for a portion of that is what I was wondering.
[SPEAKER_20]: We need to talk to the judge.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, we're hoping that...
[SPEAKER_06]: there will be some kind of agreement that it's done.
[SPEAKER_15]: But we would have to know how much before we asked, right?
[SPEAKER_15]: Or are we doing that part, or are we considering that part?
[SPEAKER_15]: Is it a yes, we're doing third-party monitoring and backup, or we're not, or we're considering it?
[SPEAKER_06]: We're working on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I think until we, I think Franken has some of the information that we can just sit down with him and talk.
[SPEAKER_06]: But what we wanted today was just that.
[SPEAKER_06]: figure that would give us something to work with.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, whenever she's mentioned third party monitoring, one here, and then say what, the Sheriff's Department?
[SPEAKER_15]: No, third party meaning not county connected.
[SPEAKER_15]: If you had someone within the county who knew where things were, they could shut it down or erase it or whatever.
[SPEAKER_15]: If you have it off-site, then if there is, or think about a catastrophe, if a tornado hits, well, all your footage is gone.
[SPEAKER_15]: So to have it just for redundancy for off-site.
Okay.
When can I go back to the jail?
[SPEAKER_03]: Are they done painting down there?
[SPEAKER_03]: I forgot to ask you about that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, the clock is over.
[SPEAKER_03]: I still got to get them cones out.
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, I don't know if you need to move the cones now anyway because they're going to be doing the concrete here in the next couple of weeks, I think.
[SPEAKER_19]: And what, they're going to take those out?
[SPEAKER_19]: They're going to take those concrete pillars out.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: They asked about everything's dead.
[SPEAKER_19]: They asked about the whole power out there.
[SPEAKER_19]: So you will be talking to them before they begin to work.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_19]: I can go contact you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I'm just shocked that we don't have a lot of people in the room for the bridge.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anticipating the discussion.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, I think it's gone on long enough.
[SPEAKER_19]: That they're just tired of it.
[SPEAKER_19]: So...
[SPEAKER_06]: to talk about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: That way it gives them a little bit more time.
[SPEAKER_07]: I figured that we would have another packed room.
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought we would have a packed room.
[SPEAKER_03]: Have a good day, guys.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do you have another copy of that handy by chance?
[SPEAKER_10]: That big?
[SPEAKER_19]: The big?
[SPEAKER_19]: No, I don't right now.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay.
Let's just say we'll wait for them.
[SPEAKER_19]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_19]: This is the hydrology study.
[SPEAKER_19]: The other piece of the board was closed by mobile after the inspection.
[SPEAKER_19]: Prior to figuring out how to fix it, I guess.
[SPEAKER_19]: What we're looking at is a double-sided box cover.
[SPEAKER_19]: Is that two-piece or one-piece?
[SPEAKER_19]: We think it's one-piece, but that's what we're going to have to talk to them about is get this, figure out how big it has to be, and then go to the concrete company and say, can you build it this size and drop it in there?
[SPEAKER_19]: Or do we have to do something else?
[SPEAKER_02]: The walls are going up at night.
[SPEAKER_19]: Are they?
[SPEAKER_02]: They'll see the size of that.
[SPEAKER_02]: It doesn't cost anything, does it?
[SPEAKER_06]: I am kind of impressed with you working with our right back, Clay.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think you're all working with him.
[SPEAKER_07]: He's done a good job at trying to check all the boxes.
[SPEAKER_19]: did we ever hear back from justin reisinger we have not when i emailed him you emailed him and asked him to put up
[SPEAKER_06]: Because we have to sign something before he can officially do work.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, he never got back to me on what I sent him from when you went to go speak with City Hall.
[SPEAKER_06]: Would you just say that if we want to move forward, he has the perimeters, but we would like to move forward.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is as good a time as any to try to sell it, I guess.
[SPEAKER_10]: No.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have a quick question.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is only for the courthouse cameras.
[SPEAKER_10]: Did you guys nix the other buildings?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, we didn't.
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know if there's more pages to that.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just that six cameras.
[SPEAKER_10]: Two on each floor, basically.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is going to help make sure it's working properly.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've got a bunch of server racks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do we need any?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't have any idea where we could use them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_19]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I like that he's on it, thinking about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you have any questions, I would like to meet with you guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Things just fall off the radar.
[SPEAKER_06]: We kind of do one step.
[SPEAKER_19]: I did not get that email.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me forward it to you again.
[SPEAKER_19]: Did you send it to my personal?
[SPEAKER_04]: Ah, your business.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, well.
[SPEAKER_04]: I could send it to your personal.
[SPEAKER_19]: Send it to my personal.
Bye, thank you.
Have a good day.
[SPEAKER_06]: You too.
[SPEAKER_06]: You sure you don't want that building?
[SPEAKER_01]: That's why I was moving.
[SPEAKER_01]: I heard you say something about donating.
[SPEAKER_01]: And that just gets into dangerous territory.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sure, sure.
[SPEAKER_01]: I have a hard time turning down a good deal.
[SPEAKER_06]: We might just, you know, we could put it.
[SPEAKER_06]: just a few dollars on it and then you might think you're getting a really good deal and you might just go for it and we wouldn't have to deal with it.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's not going to happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: I heard that they were going to dollars.
[SPEAKER_02]: I heard.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't hear it coming.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, it was reputable, but it wasn't in the paper.
[SPEAKER_18]: Fowler's Furniture.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fowler's Furniture.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I did see Fowler's Furniture sold.
[SPEAKER_06]: But they were going to go there and not over here, so that will be...
[SPEAKER_18]: So you need to jump on that and get the...
[SPEAKER_19]: Would you like to donate that block to us?
[SPEAKER_18]: No, just ask them.
[SPEAKER_19]: We've already reconfigured the carnival to the street, so I think we'll stay there for now.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're probably going to...
[SPEAKER_19]: I agree, that was a good place for it.
[SPEAKER_19]: Much better than blocking the street off.
[SPEAKER_19]: We got moved out.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, you know, they wouldn't like to do it anyway because they're going to want to sell that.
[SPEAKER_17]: They're going to want to sell it.
[SPEAKER_17]: They should use it until they sell it.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it would really be a nice big lot if the Humane Society was leveled and off the way around there.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't know how much longer Doc Stewart's going to be in business.
[SPEAKER_19]: That would be a large area.
[SPEAKER_19]: You could put a
[SPEAKER_19]: I think they still have it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't think there's much.
[SPEAKER_01]: Mike Green is Leslie Green.
[SPEAKER_02]: She's our executive director.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_19]: She won't be in for two weeks, but normally it comes in about 10 o'clock in the morning.
[SPEAKER_19]: So who can I talk to?
[SPEAKER_19]: Who do you want to talk to?
[SPEAKER_19]: See something.
[SPEAKER_19]: We'll be chatting on something.
[SPEAKER_18]: We'll be chatting on something.
Thank you.
[SPEAKER_01]: Color coded.
[SPEAKER_01]: We would like to ram it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll take the red.
[SPEAKER_01]: Have a great day.
[SPEAKER_06]: You too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: We are good on Tuesday, the 21st, to go to Trump City.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because you link 22nd.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it was in the minutes wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_05]: She was asking me, or the lady sent me an email, I don't know what it was, and I explained that there was a, you know, we were having a discussion about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: She said, do you know what that pertained to?
[SPEAKER_05]: I said, no, I just, no, I was told to hold off.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you don't want to get in the way of anything.
[SPEAKER_19]: We apply a prayer, we still pay it.
[SPEAKER_19]: So.
[SPEAKER_05]: Woodshed, there was clear tape in a drawer that was purchased.
[SPEAKER_05]: They had written that on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if it's appropriate to take from there.
[SPEAKER_05]: They said it was for painting the building room.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it has to be reserved for like, what does that say?
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't remember it.
[SPEAKER_18]: I think Heather did.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, I think we looked and it said Ray County already had the report in
[SPEAKER_06]: I assumed you did it because when we looked, it said to look and see, and it said it had been submitted.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I did not do anything.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who submitted it?
[SPEAKER_06]: It may have been me earlier, but the last report I got from them, it said, please look at your county and see if there's anything due.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it said Gray County was done.
[SPEAKER_06]: Would I bet my life on it?
[SPEAKER_05]: They sent an email.
[SPEAKER_05]: It went to Heather and me and you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently on the report there were two payments to Alice and Alice that it's got to be considered other uses.
[SPEAKER_05]: So apparently they sent instructions.
[SPEAKER_18]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who put them on there?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know who did report it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because that is an expenditure.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wouldn't have.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe Heather did.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: But they've given instructions on what...
[SPEAKER_05]: Whoever has access to the portal, I do not.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's under Heather's.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's under Heather's.
[SPEAKER_06]: What is it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Her email, I believe.
[SPEAKER_05]: So long story short, that's got to be listed under other uses.
[SPEAKER_05]: She got it, but I'll take a break.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: I got this from Lauren.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, is that the opioid?
[SPEAKER_05]: Strong?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, whatever it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think I remember you bringing something in for us to sign and you said this is I thought there was something that said maybe we were just signing off that we knew that there was a new company because that's not
[SPEAKER_06]: for us.
[SPEAKER_06]: Somebody talking about that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think Heather did that because it
[SPEAKER_06]: To get the number we needed, we had to use Heather's machine because there was some kind of...
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, so this was Cecilia's instructions, and she sent this to Heather, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you put it here, I will work with Heather to get it done.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't care to do it, but we went through that before, and we had to go over and use her...
[SPEAKER_05]: There was instructions like you need to mark a note, if it's your final report, and then here's your login instructions.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Cecilia did a really good job with step two, so it's on client report.
[SPEAKER_05]: Step three, so you just have to approve what board was put in.
[SPEAKER_05]: I sent them the numbers.
[SPEAKER_05]: They did the report.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll talk to Heather and see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: So can I have that so I know what to talk to her about?
[SPEAKER_06]: That and what about the other?
[SPEAKER_06]: Everything else is good.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is that opioid on that plan?
[SPEAKER_05]: This was...
[SPEAKER_05]: Depending on the time period, the reporting period, my assumption is probably June or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: There was a journal entry that was made for somebody.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you might get with me with the time frame because I was showing my records.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, those two payments did happen, but there was also a journal entry.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was a small amount.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it was for publications.
[SPEAKER_05]: Would that be an ad?
[SPEAKER_05]: An ad.
[SPEAKER_05]: But double check.
[SPEAKER_06]: It may have been the opioid.
[SPEAKER_06]: It may have been the opioid ad when we put it in the paper.
[SPEAKER_05]: And we don't have checks from that fund?
[SPEAKER_05]: And so it probably was paid there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because if it was a virtual move or something, they would give you their ACH information.
[SPEAKER_05]: So what do I?
[SPEAKER_05]: Just finding out, look at the report that whoever submitted.
[SPEAKER_19]: That report you're sending in from Lodi.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's here.
[SPEAKER_19]: Probably has 500 pages in it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you saying it's here?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, you'll have to get on this thing.
I don't even know who submitted the report.
Look at the report.
And just know that there's no payment besides this one.
[SPEAKER_19]: So the product came in.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but I'll also have to know the reporting period to know if that journal entry was included in this reporting period.
[SPEAKER_05]: Were you printing something?
[SPEAKER_05]: Anybody using the printer?
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't even think it was working.
[SPEAKER_21]: This one or that one?
[SPEAKER_08]: It was just printing.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was just printing aimlessly.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's being temperamental right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yesterday it was fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, if you want a second, I'll give you that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have one left.
[SPEAKER_06]: Max, I have a question for you.
[SPEAKER_06]: If there's people here, I know we have an estimate of what the situation is.
[SPEAKER_06]: But didn't we have, wasn't it a Beats report or something?
[SPEAKER_06]: And they gave us, it was from B-E-A-T. And it had...
[SPEAKER_06]: It had the different options.
[SPEAKER_06]: That would be good.
[SPEAKER_19]: That would be good to have here.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think we have it, but I didn't know what to ask her to look for.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: First check in on two gigabytes.
Thank you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Could you see if you could find, I think it may be in the Greg Rivers file, but it was a report of P-E-N-T-S. Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what I'm talking about.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it might, you can maybe put a search on it and find.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I think it gave us the option if we demolished it, if we did a new one, if we did in the different categories.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: They just left you over here, Bobby?
[SPEAKER_21]: All by yourself?
[SPEAKER_00]: They just left you all by yourself in here?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, Bobby.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you.
Amen.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you for that.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was exactly what I needed.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not email.
[SPEAKER_19]: Will you take a paper?
[SPEAKER_19]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_19]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, it's disappointing.
[SPEAKER_07]: You think you're going to have a party, and nobody comes.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I thought this place would be full.
[SPEAKER_19]: Because they didn't bring donuts.
[SPEAKER_06]: Really?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, well, now I'm upset.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, the next thing on the agenda is the discussion on the Henry Oliver Pass, which
[SPEAKER_06]: I've been here a year and three months, and it has been discussed several times.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's one of those things that I think, if you want to accuse yourself, if you say you wanted to, even in the discussion.
[SPEAKER_19]: I can leave.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, that's what they... Well, yeah, he didn't bring the donuts.
[SPEAKER_06]: Get on out.
[SPEAKER_06]: But you could go over and get us some.
[SPEAKER_19]: I could, yes, I could.
[SPEAKER_19]: Let me know when you're done.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Max, I just thought, that's what you said earlier.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, that's good.
[SPEAKER_06]: that Maddox recused himself.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we have discussed this over and over.
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course, if we had our wishes, we would build a new overpass in Henrietta, but it's $10 million to do that.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it doesn't seem likely for us to be able to do that.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the...
[SPEAKER_06]: We have a report where they gave us several different options.
[SPEAKER_06]: One was could we tear it down and then if something came up where we were able to get a grant,
[SPEAKER_06]: then we could do something but we have exhausted every we've had people looking for us to try to find a grant that we could get some dollars and do a partnership of some sort it's not there so at this time we feel like because it has been pointed out to us two or three times with pictures
[SPEAKER_06]: It is, there's some issues with some pieces falling.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we feel like the liability issue, which has been pointed out to us a couple times, that we need to proceed with the demolition of that overpass.
[SPEAKER_06]: I will tell you, and what we have now, it's been six months since we received this.
[SPEAKER_06]: The bid to demolish it that we have was $532,000.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I do have two resources that are looking at if they will partner with us some way to help us with that cost, with railroads, a different railroad than what we worked with last week, and also MoDOT, if there's any kind of program that we can do.
[SPEAKER_06]: So with that, could I have a motion that we proceed with, we've done our due diligence in trying to figure out what the best thing to do, and I think we're there.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm gonna go make a motion that we go ahead with the destruction of the Henrietta overpass.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, I second that.
[SPEAKER_06]: All those in favor?
[SPEAKER_06]: Aye.
[SPEAKER_06]: Aye, okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think we've probably had four meetings in a year to do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's a safety.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's not a lot, but all you need is one thing to go wrong.
[SPEAKER_21]: One brick to hit a train.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we're going to proceed with that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Any questions?
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's approved.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Max was not.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is there always who comes in?
I think they all do.
We were all convinced that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Lindsay, thank you so much.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Would you text him?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, there you are.
[SPEAKER_04]: We were about to text you.
[SPEAKER_04]: There he is.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just before we adjourned under other business.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Does anybody have any other business?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: But they were coming in.
[SPEAKER_04]: They were going to come.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me call Amy and see it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that was just for us to sign a contract.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it wasn't anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me call Amy.
[SPEAKER_19]: And so we need to ask him about pumping cameras up and... And that.
[SPEAKER_19]: And that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did we get the bedtime straight, Deb?
That's what that is.
[SPEAKER_19]: I mean, this is a good question.
[SPEAKER_19]: They were just wondering...
[SPEAKER_19]: This is boring.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is boring.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't know what we have on that either.
[SPEAKER_19]: I mean... That's boring.
[SPEAKER_19]: Those are still pretty high.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, ma'am.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_19]: And I don't know how this fits in with the budget.
[SPEAKER_04]: Amy said that she's going to give Tom a call.
[SPEAKER_04]: She thought he was on his way over.
[SPEAKER_21]: You take $10,000 a month.
[SPEAKER_19]: Pretty soon that adds up to real money.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yes, it does.
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, that's real money.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's like buying water.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's the same as buying water.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you ever figure out anything else on that switchbacks?
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, how does the water go?
[SPEAKER_06]: What's last?
[SPEAKER_06]: And now, the last time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, as I left, I'm going to go down to one of their council meetings on the front of mine.
[SPEAKER_21]: There's almost a 20,000-gallon difference in the same amount of prisoners.
[SPEAKER_19]: We've shut it off.
[SPEAKER_20]: Checked it.
[SPEAKER_20]: Checked it when we get a water bill.
[SPEAKER_20]: It's running pretty close.
[SPEAKER_20]: I didn't read it for a couple of months.
[SPEAKER_07]: to the park again today.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, nice.
[SPEAKER_07]: Have a great one.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm going to go in and work with Heather on those two reporting things, and if you all are okay, if he comes in.
[SPEAKER_06]: We have a close-up.
[SPEAKER_06]: If we need you, we'll call you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why don't we get that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Better use of our time.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've been looking again.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's kind of a neat little...
[SPEAKER_20]: I wonder if that's Tom coming to our meeting.
[SPEAKER_20]: He's like rushing to come over.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yes, sir.
[SPEAKER_21]: Good morning.
[SPEAKER_21]: How are you?
Good.
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_18]: I think we answered what I called you on.
[SPEAKER_21]: So I think we're okay.
[SPEAKER_21]: Probably until 1130 anyway.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right, get on up here.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, sir, thank you.
[SPEAKER_19]: What did you decide to pass on the election?
[SPEAKER_04]: I see what you're saying.
[SPEAKER_19]: You're right.
[SPEAKER_19]: And make a motion to pass it.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'll pick one.
[SPEAKER_12]: And then you can go and chin to the neck or the neck rest up there.
[SPEAKER_12]: Some of you are doing great.
Thank you.
[SPEAKER_18]: Max, I'm working on that.
[SPEAKER_21]: Hey, we looked at generator down in the jail.
[SPEAKER_21]: Do you remember how big of one we needed?
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, Max Hockmeyer here.
[SPEAKER_19]: Was it 15,000?
[SPEAKER_19]: Max Hockmeyer here.
[SPEAKER_19]: Commissioner Rickhead?
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm doing good.
[SPEAKER_19]: Road crew should be there tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_19]: To replace that.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you, sir.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't know what time I'll get up there.
[SPEAKER_19]: We start pretty early.
[SPEAKER_19]: He indicated to me that they'd probably be able to do that.
[SPEAKER_19]: Do one side at a time, perhaps, and keep it open most of the time.
[SPEAKER_19]: It shouldn't be closed very long.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay, thank you.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's meant to.
[SPEAKER_18]: Autograph again.
We were absent this day, but this was the open white day.
[SPEAKER_18]: Today improved on the floor, but we had to make sure.
[SPEAKER_18]: We had to make sure.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_18]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_17]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you have anything on opioid settlement forms?
[SPEAKER_06]: She doesn't have that on her opioid settlement reporting.
[SPEAKER_04]: She doesn't have it on hers.
[SPEAKER_04]: The one that was sent to Melissa and Heather?
[SPEAKER_06]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_06]: But we have reported.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm just not sure.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know we didn't do it from my computer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, you guys, you did it on Heather.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that's okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: She says no.
[SPEAKER_04]: The only thing that I've gotten recently is what Marissa said.
[SPEAKER_06]: Can you look at opioid settlement, what you've sent to somebody?
[SPEAKER_06]: We did a report in Senate.
[SPEAKER_06]: Opioid settlement.
Yeah.
I think this is it.
[SPEAKER_18]: Send that to Heather.
[SPEAKER_04]: But are these things that we sent back to them?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are those attachments?
[SPEAKER_04]: I bet they are because I see where the county payments are.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you don't have anything that says opioid password?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, that was all whatever, yeah.
[SPEAKER_18]: Thank you.
Thank you.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'll try.
[SPEAKER_19]: All right, thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: hi laurie this is commissioner's office um is
[SPEAKER_19]: After we had the motion for the demolition of the bridge, do we have a motion to
[SPEAKER_06]: work with Great Rivers Engineering to orchestrate that.
[SPEAKER_21]: Can I make a motion to work with Great Rivers Engineering?
[SPEAKER_06]: Is there a second?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, you can't.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, I will do that.
[SPEAKER_06]: All those in favor?
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's...
Thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think on the bottom it says if you don't have your PIN or subdivision's PIN number, she'll send the code.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I left her a voicemail to call me back and have her say, well, do you have time tomorrow?
[SPEAKER_04]: And she does call back.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I'm going to try.
Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: I probably come after lunch because I'm on the work outside.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or I'll come early and she couldn't come home.
[SPEAKER_19]: We're going to work outside.
[SPEAKER_19]: Can you come to my house?
[SPEAKER_19]: I need help.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'll text you if I hear back from Lori tomorrow or whenever she does call.
Okay, great.
I am so excited.
You know, I love our country.
I love it.
But it's just so amazing.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, we've been traveling a lot.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I've been on the other piece just kind of.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just with one thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm so excited.
[SPEAKER_19]: I always wanted to put a rock wall along there.
[SPEAKER_19]: So you dip it out and put all the dirt behind the rock wall.
[SPEAKER_19]: It would have raised the yard up and leveled things out.
[SPEAKER_19]: It would have been nice.
[SPEAKER_19]: But we didn't do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: The one thing that I really like is that he loves to just pull in.
[SPEAKER_06]: He drives down to that little dock and he fishes well.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just so...
[SPEAKER_06]: There's so much weed and junk in there.
[SPEAKER_06]: And he still catches a fish or two.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, the crappie are little.
[SPEAKER_06]: But there's some bass that he still, that people still catch.
[SPEAKER_20]: So it might just.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a different one.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's one over there by where Brian Calvert farms.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I'm so excited.
[SPEAKER_06]: I said I built this little porch.
[SPEAKER_06]: And in the summer, it's just ugly.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have to put a lot of pressure on him.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_18]: But he's happy he's done it.
When you're done, you'll never know it.
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, I've never worked with them, but they were certainly awesome guys.
[SPEAKER_19]: I've never even met them before.
[SPEAKER_19]: I mean, because
[SPEAKER_06]: you don't spend a penny that they didn't do.
[SPEAKER_06]: So they work through everything that they say they're gonna do and more.
[SPEAKER_19]: And if you count the swings Dave Paget gets with that, he'll do 30%, 40% more than anybody else.
[SPEAKER_19]: Anybody else?
[SPEAKER_19]: No.
[SPEAKER_19]: So, anyway, I'm just so excited to see a big machine like this.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know when that's gonna be.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't fish very much.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, I'm fine, but I don't do very much.
[SPEAKER_06]: But he enjoys it and he spends his time going to different parks because this one's not very good.
[SPEAKER_06]: He still ends up here a lot.
But
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, we have a fountain.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think we have three fountains.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because it gets all weedy, you know, stocked up.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I would pay a lot of money.
[SPEAKER_18]: We love property, and we haven't had any for a long time.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would eat it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would fix it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I said, I like all fish, but I love crawfish.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's hard too.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's hard.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're exactly right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Those two things.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm not big on fish.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't get crawfish for it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Marie, you were out of the room, but we had a motion to, let me see what I said.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bobby Don made the motion, and I seconded it, for us to work with Great Rivers Engineering on the demolition project.
[SPEAKER_18]: And Max Verkusen signed.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm a little disappointed in the seat, which is important.
[SPEAKER_19]: Ben's got that trunk on his own.
[SPEAKER_19]: Is it forward or?
[SPEAKER_19]: This is, no, he's got a ram.
[SPEAKER_19]: He's got three-quarter ram because of that.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_19]: And it was used.
[SPEAKER_19]: Maybe the seat just broke.
[SPEAKER_19]: I went up and got it.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's what caused me to start looking at it.
[SPEAKER_19]: I drove it back to the city.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_19]: And then it was way cheaper.
[SPEAKER_19]: And we made that discount.
[SPEAKER_19]: It cost about $25,000.
[SPEAKER_19]: I couldn't get Ford or GMC to knock anything off.
[SPEAKER_21]: I think I traded GMC for 26.
[SPEAKER_21]: I tried over here.
[SPEAKER_21]: I got it down to Alvarado Springs, Kansas.
[SPEAKER_21]: Really?
[SPEAKER_21]: Alvarado, Kansas.
[SPEAKER_21]: Did you guys know that she had somebody call from Wood Heights?
[SPEAKER_21]: She talked to you about the Wood Heights guy?
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_18]: Warning us to fire the police chief.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, sir.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because he had done this, this, and this, and called to brief, and was demanding that we fire the police chief.
[SPEAKER_06]: And she tried to, and he was not easily deterred.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, I'm going to call Pleasant Valley Church.
I have a certain message.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, absolutely.
[SPEAKER_18]: Have a great one.
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_19]: Mm-hmm.
Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, I'm trying to look for Jamie.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think he called it your car ministry.
[SPEAKER_06]: where people put their name on the list.
[SPEAKER_06]: What happened was we had several families that their homes all burned in this little development, but two of them had destroyed their homes and destroyed their vehicles.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they are really having some hard times.
[SPEAKER_06]: He told me I should call and talk to you, and maybe you can help me with this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, that's, yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, they have some real money.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, they're working through Red Cross and Salvation Army.
[SPEAKER_06]: And just, and I don't even know what your parameters are and what they need to do, but just trying to get a little bit more information.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, this morning I was at the Prairie County Commissioner's office.
[SPEAKER_04]: You had said something about the opioid form.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're a little confused about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, that's perfect.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is a long one, so I always look because if I don't, it gets incorrect.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it is...
[SPEAKER_06]: At commission.raycountymo.gov.
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_06]: And so basically then what we do is I could give them the email, but I could work with them to help them if they wanted to send something to you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you so much.
[SPEAKER_06]: You've been very helpful.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, thank you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, she was very nice.
[SPEAKER_07]: She was the perfect person in that position.
[SPEAKER_18]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_18]: She's going to sit with me now.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's time for the start.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not part of the church.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's all volunteer.
[SPEAKER_06]: But that's how we do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, how are you?
[SPEAKER_14]: Good afternoon.
[SPEAKER_14]: How's everybody doing?
[SPEAKER_06]: Good.
[SPEAKER_06]: How's our puppy?
[SPEAKER_16]: He's doing okay.
[SPEAKER_16]: on Thursday.
[SPEAKER_16]: Thanks.
[SPEAKER_16]: Have a great day.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, baby.
[SPEAKER_06]: Look what I got.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, you are a fine dog.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yes, you are.
[SPEAKER_18]: Good dog.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good dog.
[SPEAKER_19]: Guys, if I'm not here, they're in the bottom.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm sure you're out of your point of view.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if she can help us get into that.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, if we run, it's a little more expensive than probably labor-wise.
[SPEAKER_16]: Do you have that?
[SPEAKER_16]: Yes, I do.
[SPEAKER_16]: I think that's what we're doing.
[SPEAKER_16]: Do you want me to press it?
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_16]: that's more expensive but not it says please let's see what this is
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's have Heather look at it, and I think that's what it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: You didn't need a code, did you?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, they just sent the DocuSign, so it looks like I can go ahead.
[SPEAKER_06]: That may not be the report, but let's...
[SPEAKER_04]: I think Heather already left.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, she did?
[SPEAKER_16]: Show her that this afternoon.
[SPEAKER_16]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then if that isn't it, I will come in in the morning and work with her on what we have started.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah, we have that much paper.
[SPEAKER_16]: And we can get around it.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's just urgent files.
[SPEAKER_16]: So if you take 1805 or Base Rail, $36 a week.
[SPEAKER_16]: We have boxes of records and...
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah, any of them?
[SPEAKER_16]: Because they're going to bring two big ones, one on each side.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, that's okay.
[SPEAKER_16]: And they come every other month.
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, but I think the boxes are down.
[SPEAKER_19]: Some of it belongs to you.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm not sure if I can get rid of it.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_16]: So we can go through it.
[SPEAKER_16]: We can go through it and decide what we're going to do.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you ask him about this?
[SPEAKER_06]: The boarding?
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you also were going to look at the generic meds to see if we can, is that working?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, we're working with HCC, too.
[SPEAKER_16]: So Andre's going through and doing an analysis to make sure that everybody we got out still needs to be or can be housed.
[SPEAKER_16]: I know as we're getting some of those other things,
[SPEAKER_06]: Tom, this is for me here.
[SPEAKER_06]: It says for county jail, but you don't mind saying it?
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah, because it's a contract.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'll ask him.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah, check on that.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_16]: Especially now because our housing account's down right now.
[SPEAKER_16]: So we may be able to bring...
[SPEAKER_21]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it might be a way to ease into it, too.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah, absolutely.
[SPEAKER_21]: Our water bill went up to $2,000 again.
[SPEAKER_16]: which doesn't make sense because we're down on our inmate count.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'll be down to the next council meeting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, I think we need a signature once.
[SPEAKER_06]: This, this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, that's from Great River?
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not sure about this.
[SPEAKER_16]: Is there a signature one?
[SPEAKER_16]: That's the only go-on for the deal.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah, you just need a sign, yeah.
[SPEAKER_16]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_19]: a motion to hire them to do this work.
[SPEAKER_19]: So this is just the contract.
[SPEAKER_06]: For the...
[SPEAKER_19]: The little Calvary 216.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: The 216 or the...
[SPEAKER_06]: The 216.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_19]: We've got the big bridge over the railroad, but then you come back down.
[SPEAKER_19]: This is the one with the modem closed.
[SPEAKER_19]: And we are grateful that you do that.
[SPEAKER_19]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_16]: And I know max I know I owe you those two letters Just leave it alone for now
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's going to be on the ballot.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't you think it will pass?
[SPEAKER_06]: You don't think so?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what I hear from everyone.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, well, I think that concludes everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is there any other business?
[SPEAKER_06]: The number is right there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do I have a motion?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, gotcha.
[SPEAKER_07]: Give me one second, I'll turn this off for you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do we have a motion to adjourn the meeting?
[SPEAKER_07]: I second.
[SPEAKER_07]: All those in favor?
[SPEAKER_07]: Aye.