In the morning?
[SPEAKER_09]: You're doing great today.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're going to take a taxi into Barcelona.
Okay.
Very good.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm trying to read it.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're right.
[SPEAKER_09]: You should try to read mine.
[SPEAKER_11]: And they are very nice when they respond.
[SPEAKER_12]: And she says it's really bad.
[SPEAKER_12]: If you want to read that, you can tell us what it is.
[SPEAKER_12]: But remind me because I've been talking
[SPEAKER_12]: Let's pray.
[SPEAKER_12]: Father God, we thank you for another beautiful day to experience your goodness and grace, and we pray that your hand would be upon each and every one of us,
[SPEAKER_01]: Lord, that you would guide and direct our actions, our words, that they would be honorable in your sight.
[SPEAKER_01]: We pray, Lord, for the activity of our county.
[SPEAKER_01]: We pray for the work that's being done here in this building and in surrounding buildings for the benefit of this county and pray that you would give wisdom and discernment to all decisions made.
[SPEAKER_01]: We just pray that you'd keep your hand upon all of our elected officials as well as our workers and keep them safe and healthy.
[SPEAKER_01]: Bless their families and encourage them.
[SPEAKER_01]: continue to unite our county together in common good as we work together for the good of all.
[SPEAKER_01]: We thank you for your love and your presence and your watch and care over us.
[SPEAKER_12]: In Jesus' name we pray.
Amen.
[SPEAKER_12]: Everyone signed in.
[SPEAKER_08]: Any comments?
[SPEAKER_08]: I had a question.
[SPEAKER_08]: Max, last time I was here I was asking about the right lane and it was at Ray County.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just wanted to see if you had talked to...
[SPEAKER_09]: I did look at that and you're right.
[SPEAKER_09]: It is in Ray County.
[SPEAKER_09]: The line is just south of there.
[SPEAKER_09]: I talked to our road foreman and one of the problems we've run into with
[SPEAKER_09]: doing something like that when you totally reshape an area is when it rains.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because that's already the problem is water.
[SPEAKER_09]: And if you loosen it up and reshape it, then the water will take it all above the hill.
[SPEAKER_09]: So then it destroys everything you tried to do.
[SPEAKER_09]: So it's a long-term project.
[SPEAKER_09]: We just really gradually move it.
[SPEAKER_09]: But he's aware of it.
[SPEAKER_09]: We've talked about it.
[SPEAKER_09]: They repositioned that tube when they put it in so it would accept the water better.
[SPEAKER_09]: So we're gonna watch it for a while.
[SPEAKER_08]: And is that Clay?
[SPEAKER_08]: Is the foreman for our area?
[SPEAKER_08]: And then do we have a more experienced grader in Ray County or in Lawson or one of the others?
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you know who our best grader is?
[SPEAKER_08]: And could we get some of the newer, inexperienced guys to come when we do things like that to learn from the guys who...
[SPEAKER_08]: or trying through an experience to know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I understand what you're saying.
[SPEAKER_09]: And we're doing our best to train people as we go.
[SPEAKER_09]: But right now, we're just trying to ban the grades at this point.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because like yesterday, I had three different calls on roads that need to be maintained.
[SPEAKER_09]: And they were putting a tube in up north.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I was told that the majority of the people would be training because they're the ones that have the knowledge on how to do that.
[SPEAKER_09]: So we're trying to keep everything going.
[SPEAKER_09]: at the same time that you're training, that's a challenge.
[SPEAKER_08]: So someone had said that there had been like 15 or 16 and 40s on the great county roads, and now there's only like five.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, there used to be five.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're more, I'm not sure how many we have, but I think there's probably close to 10.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're looking for 12 right now as a start and see how that works for us instead of 16.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, so we're hiring.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that is almost all the time.
[SPEAKER_09]: We are hiring.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anything else from public comments?
We have questions about our bathroom.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because the day you came down, I had questions, and you said, ask him.
[SPEAKER_05]: But you didn't tell me who him was.
[SPEAKER_05]: So Chad Stockton was the only one I... We've been talking to Chad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, so I called him, and he didn't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: But he did tell me if it was him, what they would have to do, which it was... First off, it's going to take a minimum of a week to 10 days to do.
[SPEAKER_05]: During that time, my office will not have a bathroom.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's also going to be, both of those walls have to be cut out completely to be moved the two feet either direction.
[SPEAKER_05]: So what about all the asbestos and lead paint involved in that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I can't be around even sheetrock dust.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's one thing I'm severely allergic to.
[SPEAKER_05]: Angie has a medical condition.
[SPEAKER_05]: She cannot be around anything like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: My others, and I totally understand, don't want to be around any asbestos or lead paint dust.
[SPEAKER_05]: So how is all that going to be handled?
[SPEAKER_05]: And the asbestos is going to have to have special treatment.
[SPEAKER_09]: You came to us asking for a bathroom.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's how this all began.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, in 2017.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not us.
[SPEAKER_09]: We weren't here then.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've asked for it every year as well as the window repair.
[SPEAKER_09]: And we are doing our best to get that done for you.
[SPEAKER_09]: And this is the first time we've heard these issues.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm not aware of asbestos and lead paint.
[SPEAKER_09]: It may be there.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: But we'll have to look into it.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's pretty positive there will be because the building was built in 1954.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, he didn't mention it to us.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: So this is the first time we've heard it.
[SPEAKER_05]: So...
[SPEAKER_05]: Even taking that part out because if that's bound, he has to send it off to be tested.
[SPEAKER_05]: Then it has to be bagged separately and put in a separate dumpster and all of that.
[SPEAKER_05]: But what are we supposed to do with the bathroom for a week to ten days?
[SPEAKER_09]: There's a bathroom downstairs?
[SPEAKER_05]: There is.
[SPEAKER_05]: They don't always work, and they leak badly, which causes flooding down there.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we've got fixes on top of everything.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know yet.
[SPEAKER_09]: These are brand new to us today and we'll have to look at all these things.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I mean, these were some of the things that we haven't talked about before every time somebody... We have not talked about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have not talked about it.
[SPEAKER_12]: We thought it was just going to go in there and do a bathroom.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, he's taking out walls.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, every wall...
[SPEAKER_09]: He's taking out two walls of the bathroom.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: The current bathroom.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which also then what makes them two foot is going to cut into that office area where we do all the copying and everything like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have to have a huge table in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: I understand that.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have to have all kinds of stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: But for a week to 10 days, you want them to go down 20 concrete steps to use the bathrooms that don't currently work without leaking
[SPEAKER_09]: What would be your solution?
[SPEAKER_05]: You told me it was, what, $5,000 different?
[SPEAKER_05]: What happens if you get in there and there's asbestos and it's going to cost $10,000 to clean that up?
[SPEAKER_09]: Like I said, this is the first time we've had this discussion.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I do want that looked into.
[SPEAKER_05]: But during that whole time, if he tears this out and has to reconstruct, we're going to have to be completely out of our office.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not gonna risk anybody getting sick.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, we'll make plans.
[SPEAKER_12]: But it works right now.
[SPEAKER_12]: The bathroom upstairs works.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's just, you have to straddle the toilet to shut the door, okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're trying to get to the point where you have an ABA accessible bathroom.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, but I still think, considering after talking to him, all the issues...
[SPEAKER_05]: That could complicate that.
[SPEAKER_05]: It would have been easier just to move the bathroom, tear the toilet out of the old bathroom and be done.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because that was just, we were putting shelves in there, whatever's in that kitchen area goes in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: We still have the sink in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just not as big.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're not tearing down any walls.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're taking off the door.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's a new bathroom, so we wouldn't be out of a bathroom at any point in time.
[SPEAKER_05]: There wouldn't be any risk of asbestos dust or paint dust.
[SPEAKER_05]: We wouldn't have to shut the office down.
[SPEAKER_05]: When you think about the asbestos and the lead paint, just the cleanup part that has to be done.
[SPEAKER_05]: with that, that could end up costing so much more than $5,000.
[SPEAKER_09]: I understand, and right now we're talking about things we don't have answers to, so.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, those are some of the things that we are very concerned about.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: You had said, ask him those questions.
[SPEAKER_05]: He wasn't sure if it was him, but I went ahead and asked him, if you get it, what's this?
[SPEAKER_05]: He said, yes, those are great concerns.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, thank you.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll talk to him.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, can you all keep us in the loop so we kind of know what's going on?
[SPEAKER_09]: Until we get further down the road, there won't be much to share because they haven't made a decision yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, because I just, I want to be kept up to date on what's going on.
[SPEAKER_09]: When we get close to making a decision, I brought you the plans and the discussion and told you where we were at so that you could have comment.
[SPEAKER_09]: And we will do that again.
[SPEAKER_05]: You didn't bring me any plans.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, I didn't bring the plan.
[SPEAKER_09]: I told you what the plan was so that you could comment.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nothing had been written in stone.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nothing had been passed.
[SPEAKER_09]: And again, once we get closer and we discuss this, then we'll bring you in the loop.
[SPEAKER_09]: But right now, that's the question.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: And was he going to be replacing the hot water heater or something to get us hot water?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right now, we're lucky if we get warm water.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes.
in the loop.
Okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anyone else have any comments or any Eagleton, anything from you all?
[SPEAKER_06]: I would just here in case you have questions about the proposal.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: I saw it down at the bottom.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I didn't know if it was something that I needed to be here for or not.
[SPEAKER_09]: So you were here to talk about doors and windows?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, it was just on the proposal that I sent, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I just, if you had any other questions, why?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't think so at this time.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have not looked yet for locks, but I will be working on that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the other windows should be taken, and they're ordered.
[SPEAKER_06]: So he said three to five business days, so hopefully by the end of the week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, good.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then the other was on the rental, so I'll just wait until you get to that part of the agenda in case you have any questions on that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: We need to review the minutes, and I have not looked at that.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't either.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_12]: because the good news for the day is we are making progress on concrete around the coordinates.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you
[SPEAKER_11]: Ah.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't think we're making progress on this.
[SPEAKER_12]: When we finish up with this, we'll go down to the Eagleton so you won't have to waste your time waiting on us.
[SPEAKER_06]: Appreciate that.
Wow.
I can.
I absolutely will.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, thank you.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, I think we're ready to talk about the Eagleton.
[SPEAKER_12]: So I know you kind of went through this two weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_12]: Why don't you refresh our memory on everything?
[SPEAKER_12]: It's in the minutes, I think, of the discussion.
[SPEAKER_12]: But I'm also interested in what you think, how often is the Eagleton rented out?
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: I honestly don't, I can't tell you.
[SPEAKER_06]: From what I understand, about once a week.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: I wonder if it was once a week.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not sure that it's even that much.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is, what we're asking for is an increase, I believe right now it's at $175, and we're asking for an increase to 225, with 50 of that coming back to the senior board, which is what governs the spending for the Eagleton, or for the senior center.
[SPEAKER_06]: Reasoning is just to help with offset some of the costs that go along with maintaining the tables, chairs, ice machine, kitchen equipment, that kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: That 225 keeps it pretty well in line and competitive with other facilities like the Legion, or I think, yeah, VFW, I believe.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's 325, I think.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it's still, even at 225, it's a bargain.
[SPEAKER_06]: I called Lafayette County and talked to them at Lafayette County.
[SPEAKER_06]: I talked to...
[SPEAKER_06]: Higginsville their community center and most of those are rented by the hour Where ours is on a weekday you get it from like 4 to midnight all weekend you get it I think 8 to midnight so It's a it's a bargain even at 225 compared to other facilities
[SPEAKER_12]: My question would be, and it might be for Melissa, how do we do this if
[SPEAKER_12]: your board for $50?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I don't think you pay every time that you rent it.
[SPEAKER_06]: That would put just more workload on them.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, you could do it on a quarterly, on a biannually, on an annual basis, and then just cut a check.
[SPEAKER_06]: Kathy, as my understanding, Kathy tracks the rentals on it anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: And so then we would just have whatever those rentals are and calculate what and then pay it however you guys decide or they decide.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, however, whatever makes it easy.
[SPEAKER_06]: We don't want to be a problem with it.
[SPEAKER_06]: We just want to, we would like to be able to see some of that come back to us to help us.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like everyone else, we're budget constraints too.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I think that's good.
[SPEAKER_12]: We just want to be sure that we follow the right process for auditing purposes, whether it should be done two separate ways or we can do that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would say that the clerk's office probably has the best answer, what works best for them and what works best from a legal standpoint.
[SPEAKER_06]: How that would go.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I don't have a problem with the $50 going to the senior board.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think we should have some kind of agreement in writing.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't find that.
[SPEAKER_09]: That defines exactly what it is you're going to do with that money on the maintenance items.
[SPEAKER_09]: Right.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we don't have questions later.
[SPEAKER_06]: From our treasurer's standpoint, it would probably be easiest if it just went into our, for lack of a better term, general fund, the levy account.
[SPEAKER_06]: which is the same account that the money from the senior tax credit goes into.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anything outside of our mark payment goes into that account.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it would basically just go into general purpose because, I mean, that $50 for those rentals, it's not gonna cover, I mean, we just had to repair a refrigerator for $1,200, so that $50,
[SPEAKER_09]: What I am concerned about is who pays for the refrigerator?
[SPEAKER_09]: Would that be the county or is that the senior board?
[SPEAKER_06]: Anything that's a part of the building, like in the food room where it's the walk-in freezer, the walk-in cooler, the air conditioning, HVAC systems, that kind of thing, that is county.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's part of the building.
[SPEAKER_06]: And anything that is...
[SPEAKER_06]: the tables, the chairs, the kitchen utensils, I mean the kitchen appliances, that comes to us.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's my understanding.
[SPEAKER_09]: Where I'd like to get to with that is put it in writing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Those are the things you maintain.
[SPEAKER_06]: I got that information from the
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe we have that.
[SPEAKER_06]: At one time you gave me, I think it was you that gave me a list of what all the county covers on the Eagleton.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I believe so.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you guys have that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Is that what you're talking about?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that's what I'm talking about.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: We should do that sometime.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: That'll help us work through the issues with the senior board.
[SPEAKER_12]: So do we want a motion that we're going to have before us at a later date an agreement for us to sign to raise this and how the funds will be handed?
[SPEAKER_09]: We don't need a motion.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Table it until we get to that point.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll make a motion to table it until we get to that point.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: So do I need to talk to...
[SPEAKER_06]: You guys, about how that needs to be written up, who do I, or do you guys want to write it up and send it to us?
[SPEAKER_12]: We'll talk to Melissa and the clerk's office, but I think both of them will have it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then let us know, and Sherry and probably myself would sign it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't have a problem with it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just want to get the paperwork in order, and then we'll go from there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: All those in favor of taking it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Very good.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just let me know.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, did you have something on the cart agreement?
Yes, ma'am.
Okay, so this is the CACAT 8 road truss that we did last year.
[SPEAKER_04]: These are in conservation.
[SPEAKER_10]: Kurt, I got an email from you.
[SPEAKER_10]: Is this a new email address?
[SPEAKER_10]: KurtCroy at PM.me?
[SPEAKER_01]: It's KurtCroy at PM.me.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was just, because this is a new email address, so I just wanted to make sure if this was a good one for you.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
I know.
[SPEAKER_12]: Thank you guys.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: So we got that taken care of.
That's table 10.
[SPEAKER_12]: Then we have Stacy and then they should be coming up.
Yeah.
What is the card?
I'm sorry.
What is the cart?
It's a county aid trust agreement with the Missouri Conservation.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there's some roads that we will go and put rock down for them.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then we get reimbursed a portion of the work.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's every year we do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: We reach out and...
[SPEAKER_09]: This is a conservation area.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let me do it right now.
Thank you.
[SPEAKER_12]: And, Lorraine, did you have asked us a couple weeks ago about bids and when we received them?
[SPEAKER_12]: And we will start announcing what those bid numbers are during the session, and then you don't have to chase that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Perfect.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you so much.
[SPEAKER_12]: Did you see the piece on the insurance where you asked the question that we were changing it from
[SPEAKER_12]: That's what we thought the process was like.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's what we were thinking too, but I wanted to double check.
[SPEAKER_10]: And we're going to call all of the neighbors and make sure.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay.
They may never need us, but today they need us.
And today they need us.
No alternatives.
[SPEAKER_12]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_12]: Good.
[SPEAKER_12]: With all that work, how long did the meeting go the other night?
[SPEAKER_12]: Was it a long one?
[SPEAKER_12]: No, it was quick.
[SPEAKER_12]: Really?
[SPEAKER_12]: You all must have handled it well.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'll ask you guys, do you know what the meaning of Berberka is?
[SPEAKER_02]: Berberka?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, I learn something every day here, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: Squirrel.
[SPEAKER_02]: Squirrel?
[SPEAKER_02]: In Croatian?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what I was told.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't Google it to verify, but it's the name of one of the flats.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: So thought I'd share a little tidbit of nothing.
You know, that's interesting.
One of the...
[SPEAKER_12]: understand why, because we have squirrels just... You want some more?
[SPEAKER_12]: No.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, we have lots of squirrels.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you hear what just happened in my car?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not good.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: It makes me want to...
[SPEAKER_02]: I sat out on my front porch with a .22 and took them off.
[SPEAKER_02]: Twice.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had screws in my house.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I will tell you, they tore.
[SPEAKER_12]: I just pulled in the driveway and I could see my big window.
[SPEAKER_12]: The curtains were hanging down.
[SPEAKER_12]: I thought somebody had broken in.
[SPEAKER_12]: So I called the neighbor because Ted was out of town.
[SPEAKER_12]: they got inside they had gotten i mean it was awful had to call the neighbor he had to come down and we trapped it in the towel we were running around trying to okay now that would have been worth the video
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, the rest of the story, the second time I had one, and my family all teases me.
We couldn't find it.
We knew it was in there.
[SPEAKER_12]: And so a day later, I cleaned up everything.
[SPEAKER_12]: The day later, I thought maybe it went back up the...
[SPEAKER_12]: and the squirrel died under a bed.
[SPEAKER_12]: I saw it and my kids always said, that squirrel looked out and saw mom going crazy and said, I'm out of here.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hey, we've learned some new things today.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, good.
[SPEAKER_02]: I put them on the ververka.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's it mean?
[SPEAKER_13]: What's it mean?
[SPEAKER_02]: Swirl?
[SPEAKER_13]: Apparently.
[SPEAKER_13]: I didn't verify it.
I forgot how to do it.
Brian, catch.
[SPEAKER_13]: Is this your method, Adamus?
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, you don't get them one at a time when they do an assembly line because otherwise they'd mess.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: Do you want us to come down there or do you want to... Y'all got room up there.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, we have pretty much... We have pretty good space.
Let's see.
Shake and bake acres.
That was Gary Baker.
Cut off some acres.
[SPEAKER_13]: because Baker, everything with Baker had been taken, because we've got like a Baker's 80 and a Baker, Baker 80.
[SPEAKER_13]: We've got like, yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, they wasn't shaking anybody.
[SPEAKER_13]: We're getting some pretty creative ones sometimes.
[SPEAKER_13]: None was better than the Wise Arse Farms.
[SPEAKER_13]: I thought that was hilarious.
[SPEAKER_13]: What is it?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: It spells his name W-Y-S-E. Yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: Wise Arse.
[SPEAKER_13]: this guy bought some lots down here off of the Wallace Circle and he put them all together.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think at some point he's hoping he'll be able to get his hands on this one to make one big lot for himself.
[SPEAKER_13]: He's getting ready to build a house up on this floor.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm trying to think, where's Wallace Circle?
[SPEAKER_13]: South of, you know, the infamous Clatt Road 10.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Did you say Clatt?
[SPEAKER_13]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a little one too.
[SPEAKER_13]: You're going to have your hands full.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the reflat of New Garden.
[SPEAKER_13]: So this one, this lot was two separate lots.
[SPEAKER_13]: They put it together.
[SPEAKER_13]: This lot was two.
[SPEAKER_13]: And they put it back together and zoned it back to agricultural.
[SPEAKER_13]: So it doesn't make much of a lot out of it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Same type of water.
There we go.
I have no idea.
[SPEAKER_13]: It would be a dream come true, but that would be getting every surveyor to...
[SPEAKER_13]: It's more of a headache than...
[SPEAKER_02]: I did.
[SPEAKER_02]: I said, so what's the deal behind the name?
[SPEAKER_02]: And she said, well, it's my husband's last name.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it means squirrel in Croatian.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I was like, I will forever remember that.
[SPEAKER_02]: So hopefully it's not false.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: It wasn't April Fool's Day.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm not sure, Heather, but you didn't tell us something like that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Where were we?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, where you thought you were funny.
[SPEAKER_13]: I thought Paula was really funny on April Fool's Day when she came down.
[SPEAKER_13]: But we're not sharing that.
[SPEAKER_13]: You are recorded.
[SPEAKER_13]: Exactly.
Sorry, I'm crowding you.
It was because of you.
You were the reason.
You said, I think this is a good idea.
And her face was just priceless.
[SPEAKER_13]: I know, it's just hard to get back into the same thing.
Give me a paperweight.
I smashed my finger in that.
It doesn't feel good, does it?
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh my Lord.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's a learning curve when you first start using the same weapon too.
[SPEAKER_13]: Say yes.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: Give me a black fingernail.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, that was smooth.
[SPEAKER_13]: Good thing is we don't have to do all of them.
[SPEAKER_13]: One goes to this, that's our one goes to mapping.
It looks like shorting.
Yes, it does.
Most people don't even know what shorting is.
I know.
[SPEAKER_13]: So there's been all
because we don't have the ability to scan things this size.
[SPEAKER_13]: An existing car dealership on their property.
[SPEAKER_13]: And then I don't have pepper acres up here for signature because I knew you were planning on abstaining in that one.
[SPEAKER_13]: So they'll probably be later in the week.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think after Bob's gone, he gets back, so yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you.
or not to be in the order that's on there?
[SPEAKER_12]: We've already made the motion, so we don't have to .
Absolutely, I think we've completed that, and now Melissa's going
[SPEAKER_02]: of my job is spent battling these.
Do you know why?
I don't either.
Down from last year.
Quite a bit.
There you go, man.
Fine.
This is the Distorted History.
I don't know what that means, but...
Thank you.
[SPEAKER_13]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, I do not know if we have anything from Great Rivers.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, we've asked them for an email to
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what was forwarded to me.
[SPEAKER_09]: We have money left to mark the funds due to Homestead.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's the only project left.
[SPEAKER_12]: But let's hold this.
This one here is for technical improvement.
I'm a service officer for .
This is for the phase two improvement.
This is for the day.
Yes.
I'm attached.
Is there actually a voice?
This is for the day.
Thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: How about that?
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey, that works for me.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hello, are you working?
[SPEAKER_11]: Perfect, thank you.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm not going to sign it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think we had a conversation before.
[SPEAKER_09]: We had that, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm not going to sign it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because he's getting it.
[SPEAKER_12]: He's paying.
[SPEAKER_12]: He's paying tax.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's supposed to be charged to the county.
[SPEAKER_09]: So there's no tax.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that we don't talk to him when we talk to him about it.
[SPEAKER_09]: We've had the discussion.
[SPEAKER_09]: There are ways to do it.
[SPEAKER_09]: We've had accounts in many places.
[SPEAKER_03]: Same time that the conversation was had with him about the individual ambulances and all the way to see those.
[SPEAKER_12]: Which he finally did that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Which he did that.
[SPEAKER_12]: So all this may be changing.
[SPEAKER_12]: But we're going to have to.
[SPEAKER_03]: And one last one.
[SPEAKER_03]: This has been capital improvement to woodshed.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is for paint and stuff that was purchased for the phase two as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that concludes everything I have.
Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I probably had that discussion.
[SPEAKER_03]: We can air it again.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's our best member.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, so the only one you guys want me to hold this off then and say you all talk to him.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think we're good.
I think we're good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Does anybody have anything else?
[SPEAKER_03]: Green?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_12]: I do have some things that I want to point out.
[SPEAKER_12]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_09]: These are all highlighted.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're not closed, and they don't have to be closed anytime soon, but they do need some attention.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I've got three of them.
[SPEAKER_09]: One, two, three of them have been slated to be removed.
[SPEAKER_12]: Obviously, it's only for cars.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's not.
[SPEAKER_12]: Could that be done like the one that we just put in?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm comparing this to the Henrietta Williams.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Myself.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's kind of where I look at this one.
[SPEAKER_09]: This may be at the end of the triangle.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because it's a long ridge.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's across Fishing River, which is wild.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it's only a period of time.
[SPEAKER_09]: Not up to us, up to them.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm just telling you what I look at.
[SPEAKER_09]: So if you took that path, how does that affect those cars?
[SPEAKER_11]: Well... Is it...
[SPEAKER_09]: It's all farm traffic.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's all down in the bars.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's south of the railroad factory.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's down in that area.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it's... You can get to all of these areas, but you have to, you know, you have to go back to the other.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sure it's convenient for some people.
[SPEAKER_09]: But again, it's not taking trailer trucks.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's not taking farm equipment.
[SPEAKER_12]: But it's not closed now.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's open.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a three-time limit, which is cars and pickups.
[SPEAKER_09]: Even a heavy service truck probably shouldn't be driving across the bridge.
[SPEAKER_09]: So that's going to be slated.
[SPEAKER_09]: This one probably.
[SPEAKER_09]: As you're heading on board, the 210, you turn left on T and you grab a road right there that goes out to the floor.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what the floor is?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's right there in front of us.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's that floor.
[SPEAKER_09]: And you grab the road that goes through it.
[SPEAKER_09]: The 210, all that floor.
[SPEAKER_09]: And as you cross the ditch, this is on the right, it's a shortcut into town.
[SPEAKER_09]: So that's how it was used.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know that it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, it doesn't go to the grain vans.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm just telling you that when you talk about where it's at, it's south of 210, and you drive by it, you get to Floyd, but if you turn right, you go into Oregon.
[SPEAKER_12]: And all of these are in the Oregon special?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: And there's even one more I haven't looked at yet.
[SPEAKER_09]: So we've got five that we've worked on in the past.
[SPEAKER_09]: All of us.
[SPEAKER_09]: They've got time on the news, but they're coming.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know, I found it interesting when we had an election yesterday and there were special roads on there.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, we live in the country.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: I know that there's always... We are on a line where there's special on this side of the driveway and county on that side of the driveway.
[SPEAKER_12]: So I...
[SPEAKER_12]: and Heather told me something that I didn't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's where you,
[SPEAKER_12]: by your head.
[SPEAKER_12]: So your head, you know, and it wasn't, it was counting instead of like where your, that is straight out from there on your ground is which district you're in.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because I thought it was, I thought we were the other way.
[SPEAKER_12]: So it's very confusing.
[SPEAKER_12]: People that live in those places don't know even.
[SPEAKER_09]: You mean if I move my bed, then I'm in a different district?
[SPEAKER_12]: Maybe, maybe.
[SPEAKER_12]: But, I mean, we will get where roads will be done this way, but it won't be done this way.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, we have tractors.
[SPEAKER_12]: We can do whatever.
[SPEAKER_12]: But I do want you to read this message for me so you will understand the people, what they're needing.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anything else?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes, we sign it.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is just what we did.
[SPEAKER_12]: And next, I wondered, and you may already have done this because you've been working on this, but when we're looking at putting together the qualifications for that bridge out on, what is it, 180?
[SPEAKER_12]: 84?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, down there where we're wanting to do a new bridge there.
[SPEAKER_12]: Do you have any more?
[SPEAKER_12]: You may know exactly how to do that.
I thought we had to put that out to the engineer.
[SPEAKER_09]: To do that part of it.
[SPEAKER_12]: But not for the bridge itself.
[SPEAKER_12]: needed too.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, different bridge.
[SPEAKER_12]: Lots of bridges, lots of bridges, lots of issues.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: I thought they would be a good go-to person when we talked about doing something a little different where we're asking, what are your qualifications for representatives?
[SPEAKER_12]: I thought MoDOT might be a good resource for us.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: Is there anything else?
[SPEAKER_12]: No questions?
[SPEAKER_07]: I did have a...
[SPEAKER_07]: So when you sell the old Humane Society building, those funds, do they go to help fix the admin building?
[SPEAKER_07]: Or does it go in a different fund?
[SPEAKER_12]: Since I've been here, we have not sold anything like that, so I'm not sure.
[SPEAKER_12]: I would say it's different.
[SPEAKER_12]: That is.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then it would probably be dispersed to...
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, that's basically what we did on the auction, right?
[SPEAKER_12]: Right.
[SPEAKER_09]: We, you know, we sold all the old equipment and that went into the... Where the equipment was purchased from, that money went back into that fund.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, so we thought we were happy with that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Makes sense.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll be here again tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_12]: I make a motion to adjourn.
Okay, I second.
[SPEAKER_09]: The meeting is adjourned.
[SPEAKER_00]: The sign was posted right before the meeting.
[SPEAKER_00]: If you're video recording, you need to video record from the back pew of the commissioner's office per state statute 610.020.