[SPEAKER_03]: Howdy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good, hurry.
So I go over just to see if the stick would be stable.
And it's still there.
All of a sudden, my fingers are like, I'm going to toss it all over.
You have to keep doing it.
But the only time I have is on acetone.
Shit.
I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I get the full acetone one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, it dries my heels out so much.
Hi.
[SPEAKER_04]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_04]: Good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, how are you?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I have such a tough on my hands now.
It's feeling a little bit better.
I mean, I was pretty in this thing.
It was too weird.
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I didn't want to make a contact.
[SPEAKER_04]: I appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I need a finger.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wasn't going to go in there if nobody was in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: She might not have those minutes down.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, Sal, we tabled the museum roof.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, it is on there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Made a motion to table the roof beds for the museum.
[SPEAKER_02]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_02]: And made a motion to table the museum roof beds for further review.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we did that, but I wanted to make sure that we did that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Did you get it somewhere?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: All the way down to that roof shelf.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh wow.
[SPEAKER_03]: My parents do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Kind of travel a lot.
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought that was my schedule 13 at first.
[SPEAKER_02]: It might be, but it said commissioners.
[SPEAKER_02]: Say that again.
[SPEAKER_02]: My schedule 13 for railroad utilities.
[SPEAKER_02]: That envelope, it may be.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's mine.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just have commissioners, so I wanted to...
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know what this... Is that something to do with...
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't see...
It's nothing that I know anything about.
[SPEAKER_04]: I am not crying, you guys, but I have something in my eye and have it in my eye for
[SPEAKER_04]: I have some eye drops in the car.
[SPEAKER_04]: I put some in and I still can't feel I'm getting them out.
[SPEAKER_04]: It probably felt like cheese.
Yeah, give me that humble.
Where's the humble?
There's one.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, it's not enough.
All right, let's pray.
Dear God, we thank you for this county and the people that get to call it home.
We lift up our county officials and leaders to you.
[SPEAKER_00]: Grant them wisdom, integrity, and a heart for those who serve.
[SPEAKER_00]: Help us to act with respect, compassion, and unity, working together for the good of every neighbor.
[SPEAKER_00]: We ask for your blessings for this county and all who serve it.
[SPEAKER_00]: In Jesus' name.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, do we have any comments?
[SPEAKER_03]: Kirk Croy, I guess the first one was where can I find the contact emails for the road districts like Lawson and all of that?
[SPEAKER_04]: We have that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it'd probably wait until Brig comes back because she's worked on updating that.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's a process every time.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then I wanted to ask if you could explain the process from meeting one of these meetings ends all the way through with the minutes to the minutes getting released.
[SPEAKER_04]: How long is it before we get the minutes?
[SPEAKER_03]: like they're handwritten so somebody else typing them up and like what the whole process is from a meeting is ended to the minutes being released i'm just trying to so the meeting so she types them today and tomorrow and then the commissioners approve them the next week
[SPEAKER_03]: minutes okay so that's it so usually on thursday she works on it thursday and friday and then when we come back in on wednesday the next week okay so there's like some inaccuracies in them and i'm wondering what the like where those are coming from because um like multiple times it says in several times it says like
[SPEAKER_03]: she and I announce that we're recording, which we never do, or it will say, like, for example, on the 1st or 2nd of April, it says that Heather was in attendance, but she wasn't, so, like, these, I'm just curious why these inaccuracies have been made.
[SPEAKER_04]: Probably because we're in perfect bad time.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I'm not sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not, I...
[SPEAKER_04]: usually do not say you all specifically are recording.
[SPEAKER_04]: I usually say we're recording today.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I don't know that I call you all by name, but I can't.
[SPEAKER_01]: It is in the minutes.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's.
[SPEAKER_04]: Specifically?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it says we announced that we're recording instead of you announced that we are being recorded.
[SPEAKER_03]: And these are just like little things, but it's important.
[SPEAKER_01]: And just as Ray County resident Kirk Croy and Richmond News reporter Marina Jameson were recording at the State of the Commission meeting.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's that one, that minute, the minutes you're reading from in the past.
[SPEAKER_03]: In other minutes it says that we announced that we're recording.
[SPEAKER_03]: So these are like my...
[SPEAKER_01]: But you had a podcast, so why...
[SPEAKER_03]: What the words are, and the words are not true, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: So like, that's an inactivity.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm trying to figure out where this can introduce that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Where what?
[SPEAKER_03]: Where this, these like mistakes in the minutes are getting introduced and why that's happening.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then what was the other one?
[SPEAKER_02]: Why I'm not in here?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, on one of them it says you're in attendance, but you're not.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's not about that you weren't here.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's about the mistakes and the inaccuracies and the minutes and where that is coming from.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what I'm asking.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think sometimes she is in and out.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if she is in at all...
[SPEAKER_04]: We put the cheese in attendance.
[SPEAKER_04]: But when she's out, Bree is doing the recording.
[SPEAKER_04]: When Bree is here and Heather is here, they're both writing minutes and then they compare them.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: But since you brought that up, I do have something I wanted to talk with, I guess, everyone about.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: You actually put on Facebook the minutes.
[SPEAKER_04]: You write the minutes and put it on Facebook, correct?
[SPEAKER_03]: I have the recording transcribed and then a summary produced from that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have both the summary from the news and your summary.
[SPEAKER_04]: And this was from...
[SPEAKER_04]: And your minutes say the commissioners acknowledge they're violating state statute by closing, for the third time, by closing the building on Friday without publishing it in the paper.
[SPEAKER_04]: And let's be clear, that was not true.
[SPEAKER_04]: We never at any point said that we acknowledge that.
[SPEAKER_04]: We called legal.
[SPEAKER_04]: And legal backed us up and said, as long as we have it on the board, we were fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the other is a person.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I understand that you want to write these minutes, but certainly, I mean, we don't want you to put in
[SPEAKER_04]: something that was absolutely positively not true because we had discussion about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: You do know there is a state statute that says you have to publish that in the newspaper, correct?
[SPEAKER_04]: We have talked with our legal, and he read it, and so we're not going to go through it again.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is final.
[SPEAKER_04]: He says we're doing the right thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: and that's what we will continue to do until someone else is here to do it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, so you are saying that there is no state statute that says that you have to do that?
[SPEAKER_04]: I am saying we're following our legal counsel.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you get into that statute, and our legal told us this, if you keep reading, there are things that you can do, and we are fulfilling all those things.
[SPEAKER_04]: So acknowledge that we were violating.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is untrue.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you continue to do minutes and record, we would ask that you would go for accuracy also.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was probably before the transcription and description were automated.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a different process now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, so just wanted to be clear on that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do we have any other comments?
[SPEAKER_00]: I just have a really quick question.
[SPEAKER_00]: The child abuse awareness, she didn't say, is that Julie Nelson who brought it to you?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, Julie Chapman.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, I can fix it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And she is the collector.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's the collector?
[SPEAKER_04]: She's the collector.
[SPEAKER_04]: And she does, she is kind of in charge of the lights and she tries to make it appropriate for whatever time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: We probably need to review the minutes.
[SPEAKER_01]: We probably won't accept those until Max gets back tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because he was gone.
[SPEAKER_04]: So let's just table the minutes until next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do we have a motion to table?
[SPEAKER_04]: And I second that.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we'll address it because we're not having a session tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_04]: We did and Heather if we could
[SPEAKER_04]: maybe do a little summary of what we did and we had we had a good trip we spent about an hour at the modoc with the director of modoc and we talked about processes and things that we
[SPEAKER_04]: can do to maybe further some of our projects, et cetera.
And that was a good session.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we asked them what their suggestions were.