[SPEAKER_03]: But I think that's kind of subsided.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I believe that you were going to look over that, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's on the table.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I think.
[SPEAKER_06]: We didn't decide a date.
[SPEAKER_03]: for us to talk about the toe.
[SPEAKER_03]: We haven't.
[SPEAKER_03]: We just know we need to do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: At some point.
[SPEAKER_06]: We've already reviewed it with them.
[SPEAKER_06]: They come back up here.
[SPEAKER_06]: We can discuss and add a couple more things to it with Mike.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to have them back up here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_03]: We need to have some discussion with them.
Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think there's one more thing that we were going to.
[SPEAKER_05]: That takes us out of that because we don't know the intimate details there that probably needs to be known.
I am not stressed at all.
Perfect.
Thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, absolutely.
[SPEAKER_06]: I do think we have some good stuff at the time.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't think I did, but I need to do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then I just looked and I thought, yeah, you did.
[SPEAKER_05]: No worries at all.
[SPEAKER_05]: Are you good on your Vantage?
[SPEAKER_05]: You good on your Vantage?
[SPEAKER_06]: Your Vantage report.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll fill it out.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just fill it three months at a time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I'll fill it out at the end of this month.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, perfect.
[SPEAKER_05]: Perfect.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just damp and ugly.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just ugly.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's depressing.
[SPEAKER_00]: Good morning.
[SPEAKER_03]: calendar and see what we have put on for the next couple weeks for agenda items.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just want to look at that to see what we're missing.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's some topics that we maybe should that we haven't put on.
[SPEAKER_03]: I haven't told you that, so if you would give me that list, that would be great.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll have 216 next week.
[SPEAKER_03]: On Thursday.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then Wednesday, any time you're going to be here, we're going to add something on the agenda to discuss a jail increase system.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're putting that on, so that's fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: And now on the 18th, we're going to... No, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: The April 1st ethics commission.
[SPEAKER_05]: For us, that's just for us to do a report.
[SPEAKER_03]: But didn't we do something on the other, the overpass?
[SPEAKER_03]: Didn't we talk about putting that on for a meeting?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, we'll talk about some of that tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_03]: So the only thing you have on there really is the 260.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, well, we've got some other things we need to put on there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just letting you know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: And we want to thank you all for coming.
[SPEAKER_05]: He came in a couple months ago about making part of his road and he had to put it in five public places.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I did forward it to you guys as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just going to be easier.
[SPEAKER_05]: So he'll be on the agenda April 1st.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, he's forwarded or put it in five different places.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, all the residents are forwarded in that little area.
[SPEAKER_05]: So he'll be back on April 1st.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's done it all the time.
Excuse me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, so you can shut it.
It's cooled down enough.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, so Sandy had called Heather, I think it was last week or the week before.
[SPEAKER_04]: looking at the budget, the huntress that was like $6,000 was not in that line item that you guys had put when you cut the budget on my budget, hunters and stuff was not put in.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that was one thing that I don't know if you voted on the budget yesterday.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to I think I mean,
[SPEAKER_03]: I knew why you were coming, so I thought with that change, if we could table it until tomorrow when Max is here, all of us would be here.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just feel better to put on that with all of us here.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was the budget.
[SPEAKER_03]: If we table it to as far as, but.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was one thing, because I, you know, the last time I went, we had just got the changes or whatever, so once we looked at it, and then you guys were gone or whatever, so I was like, well.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't do anything unless you're here, so I wanted to tell you about that, which is not in one of the light items.
[SPEAKER_04]: My salary, which was set for statutory, you guys put it as the same as last year, but it's actually going to be different because it's set annually to increase based off of statute.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that was something that...
[SPEAKER_04]: So those two things need to be changed.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, and then my other question was, since you're making me do the 20% COLA or whatever, you still put the same amount as last year, so should that be increased?
[SPEAKER_04]: on the full-time salary and the logger and Medicare stuff and Social Security because everybody got the 3%, but it's not put in here.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they just put the same, so if I have to do the 3%, shouldn't that raise by 3%?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because we're doing the COLA or whatever?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because that's what was last year, so shouldn't that bump up the 3% since we have to do the COLA?
[SPEAKER_04]: That was just my understanding, so I didn't know if you were doing the colon.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that 3% has to be given, but the way I understood it, you could manage the numbers, however, to make that work.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that's what I'm asking.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm following what you said, which is the 3%, but when you're doing that, did you take that into consideration?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because that's exactly what I had to do before, so that's what I was wondering.
[SPEAKER_04]: How much is that?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what it was last year, so it wouldn't include the 3% COLA.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think it... Because it also changed the water and everything else.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I have a sheet of...
[SPEAKER_04]: Like I had seen you do like the increase on there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I brought that.
[SPEAKER_04]: So she did a 3%.
[SPEAKER_04]: So yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess I'm trying to think about what you have to do to that budget to make the changes.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, I just got to make the changes.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's not approved.
[SPEAKER_03]: So whether you do one line or ten lines, it's okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hadn't signed the sheet yet because I wanted to make sure the salary increases and stuff, but that line doesn't really show the increase.
[SPEAKER_03]: So what was the second thing?
[SPEAKER_03]: The one thing was the interest.
[SPEAKER_03]: The second thing was salary.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't really deal with that because it's statutory.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't have anything to do with that, but it's still set as what it was last year.
[SPEAKER_04]: The number that I have on that sheet should be calculated for half the year of what I get paid now, and then in July it changes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Make sure I'm looking at this right.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is what right now is, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is this what it would go to?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but different.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have to see what the...
[SPEAKER_04]: I think this is the 3%.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll double check, but the $30,000 should just...
[SPEAKER_03]: 279 would go to 264.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you subtract 11,000 off of that and add it up there.
[SPEAKER_04]: So then that would be 30,000.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's almost $100,000 difference, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: 279 to 64?
[SPEAKER_04]: You do the 3% on this, Sandy, on this COLA.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what it says.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the difference of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know that's what she had on the 3% goal.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've got, I don't know if your numbers are the same, but this is what Kathy did up too.
[SPEAKER_01]: So this is what we got here with everybody with a 3%.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's almost 100 grand.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, hers is going up to what?
[SPEAKER_03]: What is your salary from and to?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not going to be that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mine's not 3%.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like a 1% raise, but it's only halfway through, so it doesn't even matter.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, I have that right here, which is...
[SPEAKER_03]: So this one, though, doesn't.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're not even talking about that.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're talking about the difference between these two.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, I mean, we can, I can sit down and do the numbers.
[SPEAKER_06]: Heather, what did Kathy figure?
[SPEAKER_06]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_06]: What did Kathy figure?
[SPEAKER_00]: As far as what?
[SPEAKER_00]: 30%.
[SPEAKER_00]: On what?
[SPEAKER_00]: So security, Medicare, all of that?
[SPEAKER_00]: All of that.
[SPEAKER_00]: 759-4-1680.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's why I was...
[SPEAKER_03]: concerned because of that if you had to do the COLA then it changes the significance so I wanted to make you aware of that so I'm not being problematic I'm just saying that in discussing it I think the thought was I don't know how many people you have five, six, five people that it might have to go
[SPEAKER_03]: to make these numbers that we talked about where it might have to be half a person less or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: So even though we didn't change these numbers, it would come out by going down in a person.
[SPEAKER_04]: But still, if you still have to give 3% to those people, it's going to raise it still.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, that's what I'm saying.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can't say your goal of a business doesn't come out of that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's why when I did mine, I didn't do everybody with the 3%.
[SPEAKER_04]: But since you're saying that I need to, that's why I was concerned about that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my goodness, we sat down on a session on that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it was, the room was big eyes and you know,
[SPEAKER_03]: and the gears listening because it's just an issue.
[SPEAKER_03]: They basically said if you do one, you have to do everybody.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's nothing with you.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's why I'm like, okay, but if you're going to do it the same amount, that would mean you just have to help explain to me what you want me to do on that because either way, even if it's some one way or whatever, it's still...
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess the issue that I have, and we need to look at the numbers better, but this number versus this number, it is $90,000 that...
[SPEAKER_03]: the 364 and the 279.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know if that's exactly right.
[SPEAKER_03]: 279.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had her do this this morning and I hadn't had a chance to look, but I can double check it and I can come back really tomorrow and we can work on it and I can come over today and talk to Heather about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that's what, because I was just like, okay, well.
[SPEAKER_03]: So can we table this discussion and then talk again tomorrow without putting it on the agenda?
[SPEAKER_03]: This was on the agenda.
[SPEAKER_03]: So can we table this discussion with Camille until tomorrow?
[SPEAKER_03]: And maybe if you look at those numbers again, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can tell you why.
[SPEAKER_04]: Probably it's a little more because I moved.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the $11,000 from part-time came up here, one, and then two, that number that was there, I didn't hire Rachel until August, so that's why it was only paid that, but her salary is 70, so that's why there's a difference.
[SPEAKER_04]: Didn't get started.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that 70s part of that 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's why this total is so different is because, okay, she had a $70,000 salary, but she didn't start until August, and that's why those numbers are lower, but they were set up in that one.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's why that is so different.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's why I was...
[SPEAKER_03]: So why don't you...
[SPEAKER_03]: Find out if you could kind of come up with a sheet that kind of shows that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then could we have a motion to table the discussion with Camille until tomorrow?
[SPEAKER_03]: Are you available tomorrow?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sure I am.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think our session is easy tomorrow, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Three?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you just say what time.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can show you how it came up to this, but it was set with these numbers, or this number, because she didn't start in August.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, let me look at something.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm looking at, what, $90,000?
[SPEAKER_03]: $90,000 would mean in our expenses...
[SPEAKER_03]: on the expense side too, and probably a little bit more than that, because this one will also change.
[SPEAKER_03]: So about $100,000.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that is, I mean, it shouldn't be that much different, I don't think, because you'll be able to move some of that around.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can do, I can make that.
[SPEAKER_04]: manipulate and give you a bottom number of what like i can take this and then write in what we have and show you what the bottom number is so you can see the difference except i mean because i think it's not it's not going to be 90 that it might be because of the three percent but i don't think it will be okay but i can do something what shows what the three percent is if you would bring that in and then
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's a $6,000, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's $6,000.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm still looking at, we're trying to do a ballot.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll go talk to you later or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll get your budget and see if we can figure something out.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just figuring, I think.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because that's why that was lower than when I projected it to start in August.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think that's right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Can we keep this, or you keep, you want that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's have, let's have.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: We got saved on this thing, but that's what I was trying to explain.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then the also, she didn't start until then, but I also took the $25,000 off at the beginning of the year in 25 so that we could make the budget, which was out of the salaries too.
[SPEAKER_04]: So the 25 plus, she didn't start until August, so that, I can write up a little
[SPEAKER_04]: Just to show you, just because when we cut at the beginning of 25, it was $25,000, but I think I got $26,000, but it came out of people's salaries, but it didn't come out of their pay whenever they started.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, do we have a motion to table Camille's?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll make a motion to table Camille's budget until tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_03]: I second the motion.
[SPEAKER_03]: All those in favor?
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: We will discuss it tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you'll just come over at some point?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I'll figure what I got.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll probably come by this afternoon, today, and we'll get what she has with the budget, and then we can figure it out.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then we will address approving the budget after we talk.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: What time do you want me to come over tomorrow?
[SPEAKER_02]: Probably between 10 and 10.30 if you want, because Jeff Monster's
[SPEAKER_03]: 10 30 yeah whatever works yeah 10 o'clock's good yeah that's good yeah okay thanks good thank you you're welcome and then we do have the budget on the agenda so we also need a motion to table the budget
[SPEAKER_03]: Approval until tomorrow after we figure out these other expenditures.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll make a motion to approve.