[SPEAKER_14]: We have two minutes.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, tech will be their distribution.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's why we hired engineering companies.
[SPEAKER_07]: Work on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I am very good.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I know it's kind of frustrating, but this is generally what I've been doing.
[SPEAKER_05]: So the contract, the current contract needs to go, and then we're just going to look at it, and then we will call into action.
Good, how are you?
[SPEAKER_14]: Good, how are you, Bobby?
[SPEAKER_14]: If you just send me something first, let me look at it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, because I, yes, because, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to give you his direct number, and actually, if you could call her yourself, maybe today is your time.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have spoken to Judge Baskins yesterday, and she doesn't find me as a bad, but it is something that has to go through Judge Walton.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I would, I can definitely give you his direct number if you'd like.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you so much.
[SPEAKER_05]: I look forward to hearing from you soon and meeting in person.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good morning, everyone.
Good morning.
You got it.
Okay.
Sorry about that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, do we have a motion to call the meeting to order?
[SPEAKER_14]: I'll make the motion to call the meeting to order.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I will second this meeting to call to order.
[SPEAKER_09]: And let's start with the pledge, please.
[SPEAKER_08]: I pledge allegiance to the flag of the United States of America and to the republic for which it stands, one nation, under God, indivisible, with liberty and justice for all.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's pray.
[SPEAKER_08]: Father God, we thank you for another day and we thank you for the needed rain.
[SPEAKER_08]: We pray Lord that you would guide and direct all the events and activities of this office throughout this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: We pray for our county that you would continue to unite our county together, that you would bless the members of the county.
[SPEAKER_08]: Lord, just watch over the elected officials as well as the employees of our county and help them to work together.
[SPEAKER_08]: For the good of the county, pray that you would just put a hedge of protection around them, keep them safe and healthy during this season.
[SPEAKER_08]: Lord, we just look forward to what you have in store in the coming days as a community, what we're going to be doing and how you're going to be working through us.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just continue to bless the activities going on here.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's in Jesus' name we pray.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, thank you and thanks everybody for being here.
[SPEAKER_10]: We are being recorded.
[SPEAKER_10]: So we have, didn't we have someone here for public comments or did you already taken care of that?
Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do we have anybody else that is wanting to make some comments this morning?
[SPEAKER_09]: We are working on the documents that we need to sign.
[SPEAKER_09]: And first of all, welcome to four of our county superintendents.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're glad that you're here with us.
[SPEAKER_09]: And we are looking forward as we move forward to try to provide something that will be really a good thing for the students of Wright County.
[SPEAKER_09]: And we are working on a document right now that we
[SPEAKER_09]: figured out that we need to have signs so anyway we will wait till they come back with it with that because there's like three different parts that we need to do to work through this and we appreciate you all being willing to collaborate with each other and I think that's a really really good thing for our County that you all are going to work together to
[SPEAKER_09]: work to provide some awareness on the drug situation that we know is facing all of our kids.
[SPEAKER_09]: And you all can do that together.
[SPEAKER_09]: And with all of your expertise putting that together, I think we will provide some really good things for our kids.
[SPEAKER_09]: So this is something new for us.
[SPEAKER_09]: We have, as you know, we talked a little bit about in our previous meetings, the opioid settlement that was to be used, given to counties to be used for
[SPEAKER_09]: prevention and awareness and we have not used any of those funds at all because we've just been kind of looking at where can we do the most good to touch the most people and we felt like
[SPEAKER_09]: Where you all are, we thought that was a good option for us.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I know Richmond has already had the DARE program in place for many years, but this is an opportunity for that to expand and for the other districts, for you all to get started and dig in and see what you can provide for the students.
[SPEAKER_09]: So we're excited about that.
[SPEAKER_09]: So if you all would just kind of,
[SPEAKER_09]: they come back in with those documents, we'll be ready to sign that.
[SPEAKER_09]: And for people that aren't aware of it, the amount that we are passing along to each district is $20,000 for this year to be reviewed at the end of 26.
[SPEAKER_09]: So you can continue into next year on a positive evaluation.
[SPEAKER_09]: So
[SPEAKER_09]: We know many times people come to you all and say, let's do this program, and we're going to give you $5 to do this on, and then next year they take it away from you, and you spend all this time and effort in developing something that's good, and then you can't move forward with it.
[SPEAKER_09]: So we're wanting to give you some tools that will help you, and it will be a positive for the county.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do you all have any questions?
[SPEAKER_14]: Just that we appreciate your support.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I think it's a really exciting thing for us.
[SPEAKER_09]: And when you mention the DARE program, which has been around for a long time, you don't ever hear negative about that.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, the people that the kids, grown kids that have gone through the program now.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, it gave them a base.
[SPEAKER_09]: It gave them kind of a figure sometimes to look towards.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I think anything we can pass to our kids to make their life easier, I think it's a good thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, I'm going to go through signing some invoices.
[SPEAKER_09]: And they'll be here in just a second.
[SPEAKER_14]: They're working on it.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll just sign them until tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_09]: You all must be getting excited.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're mid-March.
[SPEAKER_09]: You all are working through the year.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're just about there.
[SPEAKER_01]: We decided that was okay, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: We decided that was okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm not sure who's there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do we have a motion to approve the minutes?
[SPEAKER_14]: I second.
You're here, man.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, don't get yourself into trouble.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you.
Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: So spring is the best time.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know about it.
Thank you.
[SPEAKER_09]: What did you sign up for?
I mean, he's good.
He's good.
[SPEAKER_10]: He's good.
He's the best.
Let's just put it with those bills.
Right here.
So this is for tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was going to take them in there, but then sometimes I get confused who the different colors go to.
[SPEAKER_09]: That made a big difference, I guess.
Thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: Melissa, will you help us when we have the three things to go through, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: We have the motion, we have the agreement, and we have the distribution.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is that true?
[SPEAKER_04]: The award letter.
[SPEAKER_09]: The award letter.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I guess we've talked about it a little bit.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're waiting for her to bring the agreements in.
[SPEAKER_09]: We can go ahead and do the motion.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or do you want to sway?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, have you formally in a meeting approved the use for the opioid fund yet for the school district?
[SPEAKER_09]: That's what we were going to do this morning.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's why we put it on the agenda for today.
[SPEAKER_09]: So that motion specifies that.
[SPEAKER_09]: So do I hear a motion for us to move forward?
[SPEAKER_14]: I make a motion to enter into partnership with our four school superintendents, Richmond, Warwick, Hardin, and Lawson, to establish and strengthen a school-based drug awareness and prevention program known as D.A.R.E.
[SPEAKER_14]: The program will use the opioid settlement funds
[SPEAKER_14]: for this program.
[SPEAKER_14]: There will be a review of the partnership on December 26th.
[SPEAKER_14]: Upon a positive review, there will be a continuance through 2027.
[SPEAKER_09]: Shall we specify the amount in that motion?
[SPEAKER_09]: And could you specify that $20,000 to each district?
[SPEAKER_14]: Specify the amount to each district for $20,000.
[SPEAKER_09]: You made the motion.
[SPEAKER_09]: I will second it.
[SPEAKER_14]: All in favor?
[SPEAKER_09]: All in favor.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is there any discussion?
[SPEAKER_09]: So I guess we don't have Commissioner Hockmeyer with us today.
[SPEAKER_09]: So all those in favor?
[SPEAKER_09]: Aye.
[SPEAKER_09]: The motion is true.
[SPEAKER_09]: So the next step is the agreement, correct?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes, I've got them right here.
[SPEAKER_13]: We need to fill out the top part and then the recipient will fill out the bottom part.
[SPEAKER_13]: And then we get a notary signature.
[SPEAKER_13]: So Richmond, Ward, Lawson.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I need to go through and put my information and then pass it out to each of them?
[SPEAKER_13]: I'll have them come up here and we'll sign them.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
Thank you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mrs. Tracy, I have a question.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just to clarify that motion.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: You mentioned D.A.R.E.
[SPEAKER_07]: specifically.
[SPEAKER_07]: Does it have to be D.A.R.E.
[SPEAKER_07]: specifically?
[SPEAKER_07]: Could it be another prevention awareness educational program for drug awareness?
[SPEAKER_09]: It has to deal with D.A.R.E.
[SPEAKER_09]: programs.
[SPEAKER_09]: I thought that we had circled back around from that question that everyone was going to participate with D.A.R.E.
[SPEAKER_09]: And that's how we moved through it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know what was typed in the contract is what was on their applications, not just D.A.R.E., but also the drug prevention programs.
[SPEAKER_04]: So basically the description that they put on their applications is what was typed in the contract.
[SPEAKER_09]: But all of them was involving D.A.R.E.?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, all of them, Heather, correct?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes, they were, yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: So that is...
[SPEAKER_09]: Because I know some of you have not gotten involved with getting the license and things, and that's what part of these funds will do is to help you acquire that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay?
[SPEAKER_12]: If you've got one on hand, I'll start on one here.
[SPEAKER_09]: Today's date is March 4th.
[SPEAKER_13]: Terry, if you want to come on up and sign this for me.
[SPEAKER_13]: And just for your all's just FYI,
[SPEAKER_09]: I know you all deal with your local police departments, and they probably will help you with this, but if you do not have that resource, the sheriff's office said they are willing to help you do whatever needs to be done to move this program forward, and they were excited about it.
[SPEAKER_09]: So don't be afraid to ask for their help, because they...
[SPEAKER_08]: Sheila, I think it would be great if we could partner with our local and with the county.
[SPEAKER_09]: I do, too.
[SPEAKER_09]: Can I get you to make copies for me?
[SPEAKER_09]: I think it says a big thing about collaboration from your group, collaboration from the county.
[SPEAKER_09]: And the cities.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just think that there's a lot of positive that can happen.
[SPEAKER_13]: We're going to get those to you after I've got Pegapro.
[SPEAKER_12]: Do you have another one going for you, Borg?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_04]: Org?
Excuse me.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's a good idea.
[SPEAKER_13]: You're going to sign, and then just put your name and title, and then your dating address to the orgs to go through and talk to them.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, very good.
[SPEAKER_12]: I had to mark this out, sorry.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, Lawson?
[SPEAKER_12]: You're going to sign here.
[SPEAKER_13]: Current title date.
[SPEAKER_07]: Melissa, do we need a motion that says we're signing these agreements?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Probably yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do we have a motion?
[SPEAKER_14]: I make a motion.
[SPEAKER_14]: We are signing an agreement with Walsh.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're really good.
[SPEAKER_09]: I second that.
[SPEAKER_10]: What schools did he say?
[SPEAKER_10]: Did he say Harvard Center?
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, I didn't hear you.
[SPEAKER_13]: I need your address, sorry.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's right there to the superintendent's office.
[SPEAKER_13]: Now you're really testing me.
[SPEAKER_01]: If you don't, that's okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't put the address.
[SPEAKER_01]: We moved our office.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right, thank you.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now, Melissa, on the award, tell me what needs to be included in that, if there's a motion that says we are awarding this.
Yes.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: We need a motion for the award ladder for each of the districts for $20,000.
[SPEAKER_14]: I make a motion for each of the award districts for $20,000.
[SPEAKER_09]: I second that.
[SPEAKER_09]: All those in favor?
[SPEAKER_09]: Aye.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: I thought I gave you the last one.
[SPEAKER_04]: The funds will be discharged via ACH like I do on Monday night.
[SPEAKER_04]: And also the receipt like I always do.
[SPEAKER_13]: Just need your signature, name, title, date, and address.
[SPEAKER_04]: It should be today.
[SPEAKER_04]: Once we get the approval from the attorney, it's executed by Monday.
[SPEAKER_10]: Miranda, could we maybe get a picture up there?
[SPEAKER_10]: I was just going to ask you.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or maybe either up here or how you...
[SPEAKER_10]: Probably up there.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's probably our best option.
[SPEAKER_10]: You tell us.
[SPEAKER_09]: So when he signs, if you all want to come up here, Miranda is going to... Take a picture.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, that's yours.
[SPEAKER_12]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, if you all want to come up here.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do you want us sitting down and them standing up?
[SPEAKER_09]: However you want to do it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think that's fine.
[SPEAKER_09]: We might have to move that chair.
[SPEAKER_13]: Which one you got?
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's scoot over this way a little bit.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll be kind of in the back.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Trey, do you need to speak to him?
Thank you, Miranda.
[SPEAKER_09]: I saw you look up when I took it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sorry, you're right there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you guys for doing that.
[SPEAKER_10]: We wanted to do it.
[SPEAKER_10]: And you all were.
[SPEAKER_10]: You all.
[SPEAKER_13]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_13]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was our first time that they were doing that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's exciting.
[SPEAKER_04]: The first table that I have is for the Historical Society, their monthly allocation.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is for LSLS Hamilton Johnson for $42 for December's LATCF consulting.
[SPEAKER_04]: ARPA fund for
[SPEAKER_04]: Earthworks Excavation for $130,000 to $49.65 for the Woodville project.
[SPEAKER_04]: And this is our final payment.
[SPEAKER_04]: This completes our portion of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will send notice of payment to T&E.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is to Diamond Bowers for $120,000.
[SPEAKER_04]: room kit on equipment number 40 from the Noxious Week.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a small amount.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you do anything with it, it's only up to $34.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Noxious Week to Woodshed for $13.49 for the aluminum screen for the exhaust pipe on number 40.
[SPEAKER_04]: Capital improvement to card services for $269.91 for the vinyl floor tiles of the jail for the phase two of the improvements coming.
[SPEAKER_04]: Capital improvement to card services for paint, mix and contain, or work coverage trailer in the 79's back room for phase two of the jail improvements.
[SPEAKER_04]: $245.83.
[SPEAKER_04]: $711.28 for February's materials and labor to repair the water lines, sinks, ceiling, and shower valves.
[SPEAKER_14]: And he is separate.
[SPEAKER_04]: Materials and labor, yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I would prefer, he did it once, but there's no receipts of the materials.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I know that Max has asked him for that before, and I got it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But he's not sending it again.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'll come take it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Capital improvement to Wichita, $215.91 for wool spackle, wool paint, brushes, colors, for the jail.
[SPEAKER_04]: For the jails, improvement to $15.91.
[SPEAKER_04]: These are all from the opioid settlement which you all just approved for Richmond School District to receive $20,000.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pardon?
[SPEAKER_09]: I think we are caught up until we do approved class.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_09]: Pastor, I met yesterday with City Hall about the property over here that we talked about a lot.
[SPEAKER_09]: And FYI, they thought your idea was a great one.
[SPEAKER_09]: They thought we should pursue your interest in the escape room.
[SPEAKER_09]: I told them it's a little weird.
[SPEAKER_09]: it was interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's a lot of issues over there.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was interesting to hear her perspective because she thought it was a cool building.
[SPEAKER_09]: There was just a lot of pieces to it that could be really fun in that kind of setting.
[SPEAKER_09]: ... ... ...
[SPEAKER_02]: Good, good, good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, that was a new chapter.
[SPEAKER_03]: So thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for your help.
[SPEAKER_03]: But we'll get it approved.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, I thought it was the application, but there were three steps.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's lots of steps to everything.
[SPEAKER_09]: We could go down to the approving the request for Richmond Parks and Rec.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's on the bottom of that.
[SPEAKER_05]: For the practices.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rhonda across the hall is going to come in here.
[SPEAKER_05]: She just needs you to sign something.
[SPEAKER_05]: Pardon me?
[SPEAKER_05]: Rhonda in the recorder, she's going to come right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: She just needs you to sign something.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Shall we go ahead and do the request for the soccer?
[SPEAKER_09]: You have something there.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is something we do every year.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do you want to make a motion to have that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, just approve the soccer league too.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, I'll make a motion.
[SPEAKER_14]: I second that motion.
[SPEAKER_14]: All those in favor?
[SPEAKER_14]: Right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Can we sign something for you?
[SPEAKER_00]: I just wanted to bring it over because I didn't know what you were doing.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, thank you.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's where you guys got it in both your names.
[SPEAKER_00]: The other one was with Ted and his brother.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay, thank you.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I was like, oh, shoot, I better give that to you because that's a more recent.
[SPEAKER_09]: So then they were
[SPEAKER_09]: but people would have room to walk on the side of it.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right, Chad.
[SPEAKER_14]: Chad?
[SPEAKER_14]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, you know, we're circled around like this.
[SPEAKER_09]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_09]: It just goes, like, double back in the middle.
[SPEAKER_14]: Right, to increase that here, where the bus could actually park here.
[SPEAKER_14]: You'd still get around.
[SPEAKER_09]: If we do that, we're going to have to change that scope of work.
[SPEAKER_09]: And interestingly enough, on my way home Friday, he called me wanting to start this week on the concrete.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I said, no, we've got, I said I wanted to talk over with you all.
[SPEAKER_14]: Right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because I can't remember, how did we talk again on the initial?
[SPEAKER_14]: You just wanted to talk.
[SPEAKER_09]: there is a program through the city of Richmond that we could participate in and you have to do an application before you do the project and a max amount of $3,000 so they told me that a lot of people will just do a part of a project and let that happen on it on a sidewalk program and you know
[SPEAKER_09]: that I wondered if we could wait until next year to do just like a parking lot that you almost just pulled right up to, to where we could next year plan on doing that and get that help on it.
[SPEAKER_09]: If we change it,
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm not sure what that entails.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's just, I don't know the technical, that was just a solution I thought might work.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think there is.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because when I came up this morning, I was walking up with somebody, and we all had to walk out in the mud, because you can't get by that.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, I had no issues with expanding the scope of the thing, but we're going to have to go in and change the whole thing if we do that.
[SPEAKER_09]: This I thought maybe we could do as an add-on next year.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm just...
[SPEAKER_14]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_14]: There you are.
[SPEAKER_14]: I listen to the receipt for all the stuff you bought in February.
[SPEAKER_14]: $1,111.28.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, if you, because she's going to need that every month, Chad.
[SPEAKER_14]: So if you can send that to her, I'd sure appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: And is everything going good?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, boy.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: And how long do you think it's going to take?
[SPEAKER_14]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: That'd be great.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
Okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay, sounds good, man.
[SPEAKER_14]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_14]: I need a copy.
[SPEAKER_13]: I just need a copy.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hang it on your wall.
[SPEAKER_13]: Thank you, sir.
[SPEAKER_09]: I gave you mine.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yep, they're not yours.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you for doing all that.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know that was, it was way more than what I thought my expectation was.
[SPEAKER_13]: But I understand why it would be.
[SPEAKER_13]: I guess you're just too exciting in here.
[SPEAKER_09]: We are pretty exciting, aren't we?
[SPEAKER_13]: Wait, no one plots, it's like.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's exciting.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: That is exciting.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's going to get exciting, just got to hang out, you know.
[SPEAKER_13]: Everything's always exciting up here.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, sitting back there just thinking what you could do to that building over there would be just such a time-lost thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's all my money.
[SPEAKER_01]: Right?
[SPEAKER_01]: Mm-hmm.
All right.
I'm trying to stay out of trouble.
Well...
[SPEAKER_09]: Surely our chances are good.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's nothing very confrontational right at this moment, so surely.
[SPEAKER_07]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_07]: Paul?
[SPEAKER_07]: Before the storm?
[SPEAKER_09]: Before the storm, yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's like a shoe.
[SPEAKER_13]: It just ties up.
[SPEAKER_13]: And so she's going to be excited.
[SPEAKER_13]: Get that stupid thing off.
[SPEAKER_13]: No.
[SPEAKER_13]: And she said it never did because it's the outside, the outside bone.
[SPEAKER_13]: So it's not like it wasn't on like the bottom of her foot where she walks or anything.
[SPEAKER_13]: So she's doing really good.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know Kelly very well, but I've known Brody Smith forever.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just got the biggest kick out of those two, of that wrestling match, because it's first like, he's just a little kid to me.
[SPEAKER_09]: And they were kind of boyfriend-girlfriend sitting there.
[SPEAKER_09]: They are, yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: They were just talking, and I kept saying, oh my God.
[SPEAKER_13]: He's been over a couple of times, and he is so funny, because...
[SPEAKER_13]: Ron loves to cook.
[SPEAKER_13]: My husband loves to cook all the time.
[SPEAKER_13]: So every time he comes over, he's like, Brody, you want something to eat?
[SPEAKER_13]: And Brody is not shy at all.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, no, no.
[SPEAKER_13]: And Brody will eat.
[SPEAKER_13]: And so it's kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_13]: We just laugh and...
[SPEAKER_09]: And what's funny is moms love that for the most part.
[SPEAKER_09]: When kids came to my house, they could tell me to fix something, and I loved that.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're cooking, and they're in the kitchen telling you all kinds of stuff that you never know.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, you hear all kinds of things.
[SPEAKER_09]: I can remember Kyle looking at one of his friends and just saying,
[SPEAKER_09]: You want another pancake?
[SPEAKER_13]: What else can you tell me?
[SPEAKER_14]: We enjoy him over there.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's nice.
[SPEAKER_14]: Really?
[SPEAKER_13]: That's funny.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, I was big on cooking.
[SPEAKER_09]: I did a lot of cooking, but I was never, we never had snacks at our house, so I never did snacks.
[SPEAKER_09]: And Kristen tells the story with her girlfriends being out there having to open a can of green beans for snacks.
[SPEAKER_09]: I said, you're making me feel terrible as a mom, but it was healthy.
[SPEAKER_13]: Right.
[SPEAKER_13]: And that's why everybody comes to our house, because we have, obviously, all the junk food.
[SPEAKER_13]: So they all come over and...
[SPEAKER_13]: Of course, Ron being the only male in the house, it's like he loves having other guys up there talk to him.
[SPEAKER_09]: And Brody's got a good sense of humor.
[SPEAKER_09]: He's just witty.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was so funny.
[SPEAKER_13]: She had put on fake eyelashes.
[SPEAKER_13]: They're really cute.
[SPEAKER_13]: And she goes, they're a little too long.
[SPEAKER_13]: And Brody goes, well, just cut them.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm like, Brody knows anything about fake eyelashes.
[SPEAKER_13]: He's like, just cut them.
[SPEAKER_01]: You can't just cut them.
[SPEAKER_01]: Makes sense.
[SPEAKER_13]: He's so funny.
[SPEAKER_13]: Just cut them.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, Latimer's going to be 16 tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, my gosh.
[SPEAKER_13]: Does he have a vehicle yet?
[SPEAKER_13]: Is he the youngest?
[SPEAKER_13]: I was going to say, this evening, Kimberly's the oldest because she'll be 16 in June.
[SPEAKER_09]: She will?
[SPEAKER_09]: And she's a year younger than him, class-wise.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_13]: I could have done either way, but I held her back.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because Will, you know, so Will can have his senior year by himself.
[SPEAKER_13]: But, gosh, she'll be 16 in June.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm like, oh my gosh, it doesn't seem possible.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're going to celebrate tonight at Texas Roadhouse.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, how fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: Of course, he's enjoying life because he's eating now, because he's cut weight so much, and he is.
[SPEAKER_13]: So I text Heather and I said, the boy's eating like pigs now?
[SPEAKER_13]: She goes, yeah, well, they're almost going to puke.
[SPEAKER_13]: I said, I bet.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, Lord, you've got a bunch.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, his back's here?
[SPEAKER_13]: No.
[SPEAKER_09]: Can it just be two of us?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, they can.
[SPEAKER_15]: I just always question myself when I go back and look at it, and there's a signature missing.
[SPEAKER_15]: Like, did I forget somebody?
[SPEAKER_09]: Hello.
I know.
[SPEAKER_15]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_07]: Good.
[SPEAKER_15]: I know, I do.
[SPEAKER_15]: This is how I feel like I come and go every place I go in and out of.
[SPEAKER_10]: You want to sign them up there?
[SPEAKER_10]: That's up to you guys.
[SPEAKER_15]: I mean, if you're comfortable signing them up there, I'm fine with that.
[SPEAKER_15]: Packing stuff is hard work.
[SPEAKER_15]: It is.
[SPEAKER_15]: I take a laundry basket in and out of Oak Ridge about every other day.
[SPEAKER_15]: Some days I feel like it needs wheels on it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, they got some now.
[SPEAKER_15]: I know.
[SPEAKER_15]: seems to be sleeping, which makes the day better.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyone that tell us about this?
[SPEAKER_15]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_15]: Jay and Jay, who have we got here?
[SPEAKER_15]: Sundance Ranch.
[SPEAKER_15]: This is out off of Highway O.
[SPEAKER_15]: They just cut a corner of the property off for her sister and brother-in-law to build on.
[SPEAKER_15]: Stay's ag.
[SPEAKER_15]: No zoning on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: Stays.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, that fan makes a very strobe-like effect.
[SPEAKER_15]: It does.
[SPEAKER_15]: On the paper.
[SPEAKER_15]: You can turn it off for me.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's weird.
[SPEAKER_15]: My eyes are having trouble.
[SPEAKER_15]: What's going on in there?
[SPEAKER_15]: Is it warm in here?
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, the one you're signing, Bobby Dawn, is off of Atkins, I think.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's on the south side of... See?
[SPEAKER_15]: They own...
[SPEAKER_15]: All of this acreage back in here, this part of Atkins Road is private for whatever reason.
[SPEAKER_15]: I guess it's probably just never put in.
[SPEAKER_15]: And they just have continued to maintain it themselves.
[SPEAKER_15]: They owned all of this.
[SPEAKER_15]: They just reconfigured the interior part of it.
Thank you guys for signing this.
[SPEAKER_09]: Say that again.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you guys for signing it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, thanks.
[SPEAKER_15]: This one is Robbie and Erin Hewlett.
[SPEAKER_15]: They bought a couple of lots in Tony Ellis' subdivision, and they're putting the lots together because they wanted to build kind of in the center of it, so.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: They haven't built, I thought they already started.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_15]: They build a house about every five, six years.
[SPEAKER_15]: And they may have, because this was just kind of a familiarity sort of thing.
[SPEAKER_00]: But it didn't look, I honestly don't even know.
[SPEAKER_15]: We talked about it for years and now it's like, yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: What's the point?
[SPEAKER_15]: No.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just a lot.
It is a lot.
[SPEAKER_01]: Four more years.
[SPEAKER_13]: we're moving you know my dad used to always say he was a car guy if you would say that's
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, it was that way with pets.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's the last one we're having.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: I've got my belly full of this place.
[SPEAKER_15]: Puts Ranch, that is some ground that Art Inslee bought off of South Point Drive.
[SPEAKER_15]: And this guy's just, it's just compliance flat so he can build on it at some point.
[SPEAKER_15]: So I was kind of excited yesterday when I was using AI and asked for the inception date of Ray County, Missouri Planning Commission.
[SPEAKER_15]: Did you have a chance to look in 1968?
[SPEAKER_15]: Nothing?
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm thinking it's before that again.
[SPEAKER_11]: You think?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, because there's another letter I found in there.
[SPEAKER_11]: Really?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's very interesting.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'll let you look at it and see what you... Yeah, it's...
[SPEAKER_12]: It's actually...
[SPEAKER_12]: I think I kind of wrote them in the book in there.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: I was all excited.
[SPEAKER_15]: I know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Man, I hit the jackpot.
[SPEAKER_09]: I thought you did too.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is amazing though.
[SPEAKER_15]: It is.
[SPEAKER_16]: It really is.
[SPEAKER_16]: And the hard part is when you don't know the gear, you don't know where to even start.
[SPEAKER_16]: Uh-uh.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, because I honestly thought it was 71, but that's when those ordinances actually were put into place for the subdivision stuff and everything, and that's what I've got in my book down there, the comprehensive plan.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know what I'm doing.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's yours.
[SPEAKER_15]: You haven't signed it yet.
[SPEAKER_15]: I know, because I was writing a date on it and talking.
[SPEAKER_15]: Sea Hill Acres.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's Mark Hill on some ground.
[SPEAKER_15]: I know.
[SPEAKER_15]: On Highway U and his son lives in the house out there.
[SPEAKER_15]: For whatever reason years ago I guess the house was too close to the property line and he was cutting off some acreage for his son so he purchased a strip from the neighbor to get everything squared up there.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: And you're not done yet, are you?
[SPEAKER_09]: One more.
[SPEAKER_09]: Two more.
[SPEAKER_15]: Two more and a few witnesses.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's just a flower.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now, Stacey, did we make a decision that we'll be doing the ordinance when you can have a motion?
[SPEAKER_15]: I think we were just going to do, I think last time y'all just did two motions, one for the class and one for the witnesses.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: There was some discussion that our signatures wasn't enough, but we felt like that we would be better if we did that.
[SPEAKER_15]: I can't believe it's already March.
[SPEAKER_15]: And time change this weekend.
[SPEAKER_15]: I know.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm excited.
[SPEAKER_13]: We definitely need some sun.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think Sunday it's busted.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, Saturday too, but I think it's just going to be cloudy though.
[SPEAKER_13]: Partly cloudy.
[SPEAKER_15]: And they did not have enough frontage, so they had to have a variance.
[SPEAKER_15]: Shared entrance on the property line, so it won't add any more driveways than it would have originally.
[SPEAKER_10]: Bill and Joe would be happy with that situation, wouldn't he?
[SPEAKER_10]: His whole family.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who took the house?
[SPEAKER_15]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_15]: Who took the house?
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't know, but I think they're going to sell it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, are they?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, they're selling it with three acres.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: So he had quite a bit out there then.
[SPEAKER_15]: 17 or 18 acres.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, I didn't know that.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: I think I saw 17.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, because there's 10, a little over 10 acres with Rittmiller's lot.
[SPEAKER_16]: Now, I don't know what his name is.
[SPEAKER_16]: The daughter.
[SPEAKER_16]: There's Tammy Clark and Lisa Rittmiller.
[SPEAKER_16]: Is Tammy on the farm too?
[SPEAKER_16]: Is that part of his, where her house is?
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't know because that's under Tammy and Kelly Clark.
[SPEAKER_15]: So I don't know if that was part of this to begin with or not.
[SPEAKER_15]: This was all along the frontage there where his house was that faces the gravel road.
[SPEAKER_15]: And these are all rezonings from plaques we signed last month Do we have a motion to approve the
[SPEAKER_09]: and the ordinances that's been provided to us.
[SPEAKER_15]: Those are just ordinances from PLAAF that were signed last month.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, at our conference, of course, we saw a lot of Travis, and Paige was there, too, as a presenter.
[SPEAKER_09]: I will tell you, he has her...
[SPEAKER_15]: And she's quick.
[SPEAKER_15]: She gets right back with you.
[SPEAKER_15]: I mean, we always CC her.
[SPEAKER_12]: She never comes to the conference with him.
[SPEAKER_12]: I see her one time because she did come up and do a report up here.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, no kidding.
[SPEAKER_09]: She's pretty young, isn't she?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: it was now it was pretty it was really kind of cool to watch that because she is so young and i mean she okay yes
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think they always put partners' names on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're probably the family names.
[SPEAKER_16]: It says Ellis, Ellis, Ellis, Ellis.
[SPEAKER_15]: And to watch him down there when there's 300 people.
[SPEAKER_09]: And he just, you go out for coffee and you can just get in to talk to him and he'll just, you know, he will just help you get in.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, thank you, Charles, and I hope you have a great day.
[SPEAKER_05]: Call back anytime.
[SPEAKER_13]: Excuse me.
[SPEAKER_13]: I've got the book open in there.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think it's open to that page.
[SPEAKER_12]: If it's not, then it's back just a little bit.
[SPEAKER_09]: He is.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do you know something that, it wasn't him, but one of the things that I thought we'd done something right was we had a session on Robin Bridge and a young guy,
[SPEAKER_09]: He had done it forever.
[SPEAKER_09]: He said, I mean, 25 years, so he didn't look that old.
[SPEAKER_09]: But anyway, he said the one thing that he would encourage counties to do to get that right person to leave their road and bridge was farm porters that want to raise cattle and want to do all these things, that they can do that and run the crew.
[SPEAKER_09]: So it makes it, they have something to provide for their families, but it makes it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I realized I'm going to talk to her with my hands.
[SPEAKER_06]: I had no idea I was doing it.
[SPEAKER_06]: She was talking with her hands.
[SPEAKER_06]: I looked at her.
[SPEAKER_06]: She was.
[SPEAKER_16]: She's going.
[SPEAKER_16]: That's a good follow.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hey.
[SPEAKER_14]: He was impressive and had a lot of good information.
[SPEAKER_14]: I went back and talked to him about, you know, we were talking about his plan.
[SPEAKER_14]: Can you explain that to me?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: You may have some hot spots you have to do.
[SPEAKER_05]: last one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're talking about storms on Friday.
[SPEAKER_15]: On Friday, yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: Like severe storms.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's what I thought they were talking about.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I thought today, too.
[SPEAKER_15]: I know they were talking about anything severe today, but like possible fun or like tornado type stuff on Friday.
[SPEAKER_15]: I thought it was only one o'clock today.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll put it in your chair.
[SPEAKER_16]: Let me get that for you.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is therapy.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's good for you.
[SPEAKER_06]: My mom, boy, if you got up from the table and you didn't put your chair in, it was you again.
[SPEAKER_06]: Very proper.
[SPEAKER_06]: Had to do the whole pageant crap, you know.
[SPEAKER_06]: The things people do not know about me.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's scary.
[SPEAKER_09]: What time do we have the next one?
[SPEAKER_09]: I think.
[SPEAKER_09]: 10.30.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is it 10.30 or what?
[SPEAKER_03]: 10.30.
[SPEAKER_01]: 10.30.
[SPEAKER_01]: Good.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you just let me know when Judge Walden is going on with that commission.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't have any issues calling because I just got off the phone with him this morning.
[SPEAKER_05]: much yeah absolutely anytime all right bye
[SPEAKER_01]: We don't need to do anything with this, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks for doing all that shredding.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was a lot.